const questions = {
            "level 1": [
  
  { "Question": "haqida", "RightAnswer": "о", "options": ["by","from","at"] },
  { "Question": "qila olmoq, mumkin", "RightAnswer": "мочь", "options": ["ought","must","might"] },
  { "Question": "qaysi", "RightAnswer": "который", "options": ["mine","neither","none"] },
  { "Question": "u yerda", "RightAnswer": "там", "options": ["instead","down","out"] },
  { "Question": "bilmoq", "RightAnswer": "знать", "options": ["go","say","do"] },
  { "Question": "ko'proq", "RightAnswer": "больше", "options": ["as","hence","otherwise"] },
  { "Question": "olmoq", "RightAnswer": "получать", "options": ["know","go","say"] },
  { "Question": "kim", "RightAnswer": "кто", "options": ["she","I","we"] },
  { "Question": "yoqtirmoq", "RightAnswer": "нравиться", "options": ["swear","damn","prompt"] },
  { "Question": "qachon", "RightAnswer": "когда", "options": ["so","badly","abroad"] },
  { "Question": "o'ylamoq", "RightAnswer": "думать", "options": ["get","know","go"] },
  { "Question": "qilmoq, yaratmoq", "RightAnswer": "делать", "options": ["think","get","know"] },
  { "Question": "vaqt", "RightAnswer": "время", "options": ["can","ought","must"] },
  { "Question": "ko'rmoq", "RightAnswer": "видеть", "options": ["make","think","get"] },
  { "Question": "nima", "RightAnswer": "что", "options": ["which","mine","neither"] },
  { "Question": "yuqoriga", "RightAnswer": "вверх", "options": ["back","nowadays","aside"] },
  { "Question": "ba'zi", "RightAnswer": "некоторые", "options": ["all","this","either"] },
  { "Question": "boshqa", "RightAnswer": "другой", "options": ["some","all","this"] },
  { "Question": "tashqarida", "RightAnswer": "снаружи", "options": ["up","back","nowadays"] },
  { "Question": "yaxshi", "RightAnswer": "хороший", "options": ["bad","young","large"] },
  { "Question": "odamlar", "RightAnswer": "люди", "options": ["time","can","ought"] },
  { "Question": "yil", "RightAnswer": "год", "options": ["people","time","can"] },
  { "Question": "olmoq", "RightAnswer": "брать", "options": ["see","make","think"] },
  { "Question": "yo'q", "RightAnswer": "нет", "options": ["several","few","every"] },
  { "Question": "yaxshi", "RightAnswer": "хорошо", "options": ["faithfully","gently","subsequently"] },
  { "Question": "chunki", "RightAnswer": "потому что", "options": ["if","or","but"] },
  { "Question": "juda", "RightAnswer": "очень", "options": ["not","cool","tender"] },
  { "Question": "faqat", "RightAnswer": "только", "options": ["very","not","cool"] },
  { "Question": "kelmoq", "RightAnswer": "приходить", "options": ["take","see","make"] }
            ],
            "level 2": [
                {
                    "Question": "oxirgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "last",
                    "options": ["first","ashamed","lazy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bola",
                    "RightAnswer": "child",
                    "options": ["thing","day","way"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aytmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "tell",
                    "options": ["find","give","want"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqatan",
                    "RightAnswer": "really",
                    "options": ["here","even","how"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'ng'iroq qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "call",
                    "options": ["need","use","work"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldin",
                    "RightAnswer": "before",
                    "options": ["after","inside","alongside"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kompaniya",
                    "RightAnswer": "company",
                    "options": ["child","thing","day"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "orqali",
                    "RightAnswer": "through",
                    "options": ["over","near","unlike"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pastga",
                    "RightAnswer": "down",
                    "options": ["out","up","back"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rsatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "show",
                    "options": ["call","need","use"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayot",
                    "RightAnswer": "life",
                    "options": ["company","child","thing"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "erkak",
                    "RightAnswer": "man",
                    "options": ["life","company","child"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "change",
                    "options": ["show","call","need"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joy",
                    "RightAnswer": "place",
                    "options": ["sir","outside","tonight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzun",
                    "RightAnswer": "long",
                    "options": ["last","first","ashamed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "orasida",
                    "RightAnswer": "between",
                    "options": ["into","about","by"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "his qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "feel",
                    "options": ["tell","find","give"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ham, juda",
                    "RightAnswer": "too",
                    "options": ["really","here","even"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hali ham",
                    "RightAnswer": "still",
                    "options": ["only","well","faithfully"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muammo",
                    "RightAnswer": "problem",
                    "options": ["man","life","company"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yozmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "write",
                    "options": ["feel","tell","find"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bir xil",
                    "RightAnswer": "same",
                    "options": ["new","good","bad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'p",
                    "RightAnswer": "lot",
                    "options": ["problem","man","life"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajoyib",
                    "RightAnswer": "great",
                    "options": ["same","new","good"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harakat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "try",
                    "options": ["change","show","call"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tark etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "leave",
                    "options": ["write","feel","tell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqam",
                    "RightAnswer": "number",
                    "options": ["lot","problem","man"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ikkisi ham",
                    "RightAnswer": "both",
                    "options": ["such","many","any"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ega bo'lmoq, o'zi",
                    "RightAnswer": "own",
                    "options": ["latter","sharp","round"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qism",
                    "RightAnswer": "part",
                    "options": ["number","lot","problem"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nuqta",
                    "RightAnswer": "point",
                    "options": ["place","sir","outside"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oz, kichkina",
                    "RightAnswer": "little",
                    "options": ["long","last","first"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yordam bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "help",
                    "options": ["try","change","show"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'ramoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "ask",
                    "options": ["leave","write","feel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uchrashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "meet",
                    "options": ["ask","leave","write"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "start",
                    "options": ["help","try","change"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gaplashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "talk",
                    "options": ["start","help","try"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nimadir",
                    "RightAnswer": "something",
                    "options": ["who","she","I"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'ymoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "put",
                    "options": ["meet","ask","leave"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yana bir",
                    "RightAnswer": "another",
                    "options": ["both","such","many"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "become",
                    "options": ["put","meet","ask"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiziqish",
                    "RightAnswer": "interest",
                    "options": ["point","place","sir"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mamlakat",
                    "RightAnswer": "country",
                    "options": ["part","number","lot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eski, qari",
                    "RightAnswer": "old",
                    "options": ["great","same","new"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "har biri",
                    "RightAnswer": "each",
                    "options": ["another","both","such"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maktab",
                    "RightAnswer": "school",
                    "options": ["country","part","number"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kech",
                    "RightAnswer": "late",
                    "options": ["little","long","last"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baland",
                    "RightAnswer": "high",
                    "options": ["late","little","long"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshqacha",
                    "RightAnswer": "different",
                    "options": ["old","great","same"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'chirilgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "off",
                    "options": ["through","over","near"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keyingi",
                    "RightAnswer": "next",
                    "options": ["high","late","little"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oxir",
                    "RightAnswer": "end",
                    "options": ["interest","point","place"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yashamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "live",
                    "options": ["become","put","meet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nima uchun",
                    "RightAnswer": "why",
                    "options": ["too","really","here"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "paytda",
                    "RightAnswer": "while",
                    "options": ["whilst","whenever","nevertheless"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dunyo",
                    "RightAnswer": "world",
                    "options": ["school","country","part"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hafta",
                    "RightAnswer": "week",
                    "options": ["world","school","country"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'ynamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "play",
                    "options": ["talk","start","help"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mumkin",
                    "RightAnswer": "might",
                    "options": ["may","should","could"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kerak",
                    "RightAnswer": "must",
                    "options": ["might","may","should"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uy",
                    "RightAnswer": "home",
                    "options": ["bottom","compound","fat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hech qachon",
                    "RightAnswer": "never",
                    "options": ["why","too","really"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'z ichiga olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "include",
                    "options": ["live","become","put"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kurs",
                    "RightAnswer": "course",
                    "options": ["week","world","school"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uy",
                    "RightAnswer": "house",
                    "options": ["course","week","world"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisobot",
                    "RightAnswer": "report",
                    "options": ["play","talk","start"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "guruh",
                    "RightAnswer": "group",
                    "options": ["house","course","week"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "holat",
                    "RightAnswer": "case",
                    "options": ["group","house","course"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ayol",
                    "RightAnswer": "woman",
                    "options": ["case","group","house"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "atrofida",
                    "RightAnswer": "around",
                    "options": ["off","through","over"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kitob",
                    "RightAnswer": "book",
                    "options": ["end","interest","point"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oila",
                    "RightAnswer": "family",
                    "options": ["woman","case","group"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rinmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "seem",
                    "options": ["include","live","become"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ruxsat bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "let",
                    "options": ["seem","include","live"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yana",
                    "RightAnswer": "again",
                    "options": ["never","why","too"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tur, xushmuomala",
                    "RightAnswer": "kind",
                    "options": ["criteria","thirst","hunger"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "keep",
                    "options": ["let","seem","include"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eshitmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hear",
                    "options": ["keep","let","seem"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tizim",
                    "RightAnswer": "system",
                    "options": ["family","woman","case"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "har",
                    "RightAnswer": "every",
                    "options": ["that","than","while"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "savol",
                    "RightAnswer": "question",
                    "options": ["book","end","interest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davomida",
                    "RightAnswer": "during",
                    "options": ["between","into","about"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "har doim",
                    "RightAnswer": "always",
                    "options": ["again","never","why"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "katta",
                    "RightAnswer": "big",
                    "options": ["different","old","great"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rnatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "set",
                    "options": ["report","play","talk"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kichik",
                    "RightAnswer": "small",
                    "options": ["big","different","old"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rganmoq, o'qimoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "study",
                    "options": ["set","report","play"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ergashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "follow",
                    "options": ["hear","keep","let"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "begin",
                    "options": ["follow","hear","keep"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhim",
                    "RightAnswer": "important",
                    "options": ["small","big","different"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dan beri",
                    "RightAnswer": "since",
                    "options": ["before","after","inside"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yugurmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "run",
                    "options": ["study","set","report"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ostida",
                    "RightAnswer": "under",
                    "options": ["during","between","into"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "burilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "turn",
                    "options": ["run","study","set"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ozchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "few",
                    "options": ["every","that","than"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olib kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bring",
                    "options": ["begin","follow","hear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "erta",
                    "RightAnswer": "early",
                    "options": ["next","high","late"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "hand",
                    "options": ["question","book","end"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davlat",
                    "RightAnswer": "state",
                    "options": ["hand","question","book"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'chmoq, harakatlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "move",
                    "options": ["turn","run","study"]
                }
            ],
            "level 3": [
                {
                    "Question": "pul",
                    "RightAnswer": "money",
                    "options": ["system","family","woman"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqat",
                    "RightAnswer": "fact",
                    "options": ["money","system","family"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ammo",
                    "RightAnswer": "however",
                    "options": ["where","when","so"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hudud",
                    "RightAnswer": "area",
                    "options": ["fact","money","system"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqdim etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "provide",
                    "options": ["bring","begin","follow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ism",
                    "RightAnswer": "name",
                    "options": ["state","hand","question"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'qimoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "read",
                    "options": ["provide","bring","begin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "do'st",
                    "RightAnswer": "friend",
                    "options": ["area","fact","money"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oy",
                    "RightAnswer": "month",
                    "options": ["friend","area","fact"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "katta",
                    "RightAnswer": "large",
                    "options": ["important","small","fat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "biznes",
                    "RightAnswer": "business",
                    "options": ["month","friend","area"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "siz, ega emas",
                    "RightAnswer": "without",
                    "options": ["under","during","between"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma'lumot",
                    "RightAnswer": "information",
                    "options": ["business","month","friend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ochmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "open",
                    "options": ["own","latter","sharp"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "buyurtma",
                    "RightAnswer": "order",
                    "options": ["name","state","hand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hukumat",
                    "RightAnswer": "government",
                    "options": ["information","business","month"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'z",
                    "RightAnswer": "word",
                    "options": ["government","information","business"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "masala",
                    "RightAnswer": "issue",
                    "options": ["order","name","state"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bozor",
                    "RightAnswer": "market",
                    "options": ["word","government","information"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'lamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pay",
                    "options": ["move","turn","run"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "build",
                    "options": ["read","provide","bring"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ushlab turmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hold",
                    "options": ["build","read","provide"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xizmat",
                    "RightAnswer": "service",
                    "options": ["market","word","government"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarshi",
                    "RightAnswer": "against",
                    "options": ["without","under","during"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishonmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "believe",
                    "options": ["hold","build","read"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ikkinchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "second",
                    "options": ["master","fashion","spring"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "garchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "though",
                    "options": ["whereas","unless","nor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ha",
                    "RightAnswer": "yes",
                    "options": ["always","again","never"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sevgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "love",
                    "options": ["issue","order","name"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oshmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "increase",
                    "options": ["pay","move","turn"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ish",
                    "RightAnswer": "job",
                    "options": ["service","market","word"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "reja",
                    "RightAnswer": "plan",
                    "options": ["love","issue","order"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "natija",
                    "RightAnswer": "result",
                    "options": ["plan","love","issue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzoqda",
                    "RightAnswer": "away",
                    "options": ["yes","always","again"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "misol",
                    "RightAnswer": "example",
                    "options": ["job","service","market"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sodir bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "happen",
                    "options": ["believe","hold","build"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "offer",
                    "options": ["increase","pay","move"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "young",
                    "options": ["large","important","small"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "close",
                    "options": ["mean","insure","compute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dastur",
                    "RightAnswer": "program",
                    "options": ["result","plan","love"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshqarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "lead",
                    "options": ["offer","increase","pay"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sotib olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "buy",
                    "options": ["happen","believe","hold"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushunmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "understand",
                    "options": ["buy","happen","believe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rahmat aytmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "thank",
                    "options": ["lead","offer","increase"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "far",
                    "options": ["still","only","well"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bugun",
                    "RightAnswer": "today",
                    "options": ["home","bottom","compound"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soat",
                    "RightAnswer": "hour",
                    "options": ["example","job","service"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "talaba",
                    "RightAnswer": "student",
                    "options": ["hour","example","job"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuz",
                    "RightAnswer": "face",
                    "options": ["program","result","plan"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "umid",
                    "RightAnswer": "hope",
                    "options": ["thank","lead","offer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'oya",
                    "RightAnswer": "idea",
                    "options": ["student","hour","example"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "narx",
                    "RightAnswer": "cost",
                    "options": ["face","program","result"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamroq",
                    "RightAnswer": "less",
                    "options": ["most","more","as"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xona",
                    "RightAnswer": "room",
                    "options": ["idea","student","hour"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gacha",
                    "RightAnswer": "until",
                    "options": ["since","before","after"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sabab",
                    "RightAnswer": "reason",
                    "options": ["room","idea","student"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shakl",
                    "RightAnswer": "form",
                    "options": ["cost","face","program"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sarflamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "spend",
                    "options": ["understand","buy","happen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "head",
                    "options": ["form","cost","face"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mashina",
                    "RightAnswer": "car",
                    "options": ["reason","room","idea"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rganmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "learn",
                    "options": ["spend","understand","buy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daraja",
                    "RightAnswer": "level",
                    "options": ["kind","criteria","thirst"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shaxs",
                    "RightAnswer": "person",
                    "options": ["car","reason","room"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tajriba",
                    "RightAnswer": "experience",
                    "options": ["head","form","cost"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bir marta",
                    "RightAnswer": "once",
                    "options": ["however","where","when"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "a'zo",
                    "RightAnswer": "member",
                    "options": ["person","car","reason"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "enough",
                    "options": ["much","no","several"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yomon",
                    "RightAnswer": "bad",
                    "options": ["young","large","important"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shahar",
                    "RightAnswer": "city",
                    "options": ["member","person","car"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tun",
                    "RightAnswer": "night",
                    "options": ["city","member","person"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qodir",
                    "RightAnswer": "able",
                    "options": ["bad","young","large"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'llamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "support",
                    "options": ["hope","thank","lead"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "...mi yoki",
                    "RightAnswer": "whether",
                    "options": ["because","if","or"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiziq",
                    "RightAnswer": "line",
                    "options": ["experience","head","form"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqdim etmoq, namoyish qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "present",
                    "options": ["tall","opposite","left"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tomon",
                    "RightAnswer": "side",
                    "options": ["night","city","member"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "juda",
                    "RightAnswer": "quite",
                    "options": ["away","yes","always"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "garchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "although",
                    "options": ["whether","because","if"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "amin bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sure",
                    "options": ["able","bad","young"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muddat",
                    "RightAnswer": "term",
                    "options": ["side","night","city"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eng kam",
                    "RightAnswer": "least",
                    "options": ["enough","much","no"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "age",
                    "options": ["term","side","night"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "past",
                    "RightAnswer": "low",
                    "options": ["early","next","high"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gapirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "speak",
                    "options": ["learn","spend","understand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ichida",
                    "RightAnswer": "within",
                    "options": ["against","without","under"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jarayon",
                    "RightAnswer": "process",
                    "options": ["line","experience","head"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jamoat",
                    "RightAnswer": "public",
                    "options": ["tight","wild","quiet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tez-tez",
                    "RightAnswer": "often",
                    "options": ["quite","away","yes"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "poezd",
                    "RightAnswer": "train",
                    "options": ["process","line","experience"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mumkin",
                    "RightAnswer": "possible",
                    "options": ["sure","able","bad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aslida",
                    "RightAnswer": "actually",
                    "options": ["often","quite","away"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaxshiroq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rather",
                    "options": ["actually","often","quite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rinish",
                    "RightAnswer": "view",
                    "options": ["train","process","line"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birga",
                    "RightAnswer": "together",
                    "options": ["rather","actually","often"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisobga olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "consider",
                    "options": ["speak","learn","spend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "narx",
                    "RightAnswer": "price",
                    "options": ["view","train","process"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ota-ona",
                    "RightAnswer": "parent",
                    "options": ["age","term","side"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiyin",
                    "RightAnswer": "hard",
                    "options": ["low","early","next"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bazm",
                    "RightAnswer": "party",
                    "options": ["parent","age","term"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mahalliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "local",
                    "options": ["possible","sure","able"]
                }
            ],
            "level 4": [
                {
                    "Question": "nazorat",
                    "RightAnswer": "control",
                    "options": ["support","hope","thank"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "allaqachon",
                    "RightAnswer": "already",
                    "options": ["together","rather","actually"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashvish, qiziqish",
                    "RightAnswer": "concern",
                    "options": ["price","view","train"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mahsulot",
                    "RightAnswer": "product",
                    "options": ["party","parent","age"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'qotmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "lose",
                    "options": ["consider","speak","learn"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hikoya",
                    "RightAnswer": "story",
                    "options": ["product","party","parent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "deyarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "almost",
                    "options": ["already","together","rather"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davom ettirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "continue",
                    "options": ["lose","consider","speak"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "turmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stand",
                    "options": ["control","support","hope"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "butun",
                    "RightAnswer": "whole",
                    "options": ["public","tight","wild"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hali",
                    "RightAnswer": "yet",
                    "options": ["once","however","where"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baholamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rate",
                    "options": ["concern","price","view"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "parvarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "care",
                    "options": ["rate","concern","price"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kutmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "expect",
                    "options": ["continue","lose","consider"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'sir",
                    "RightAnswer": "effect",
                    "options": ["care","rate","concern"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tur, nav",
                    "RightAnswer": "sort",
                    "options": ["effect","care","rate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qachondir",
                    "RightAnswer": "ever",
                    "options": ["almost","already","together"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "istalgan narsa",
                    "RightAnswer": "anything",
                    "options": ["something","who","she"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sabab",
                    "RightAnswer": "cause",
                    "options": ["sort","effect","care"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fall",
                    "options": ["stand","control","support"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kelishmoq, bitim",
                    "RightAnswer": "deal",
                    "options": ["cause","sort","effect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suv",
                    "RightAnswer": "water",
                    "options": ["deal","cause","sort"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yubormoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "send",
                    "options": ["expect","continue","lose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ruxsat bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "allow",
                    "options": ["send","expect","continue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tez orada",
                    "RightAnswer": "soon",
                    "options": ["ever","almost","already"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soat , kuzatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "watch",
                    "options": ["fall","stand","control"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asos",
                    "RightAnswer": "base",
                    "options": ["water","deal","cause"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtimol",
                    "RightAnswer": "probably",
                    "options": ["soon","ever","almost"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "suggest",
                    "options": ["allow","send","expect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'tmish, o‘tmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "past",
                    "options": ["east","plenty","west"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuch, hokimiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "power",
                    "options": ["base","water","deal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "test, sinov",
                    "RightAnswer": "test",
                    "options": ["power","base","water"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashrif buyurmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "visit",
                    "options": ["watch","fall","stand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "markaz",
                    "RightAnswer": "center",
                    "options": ["test","power","base"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'smoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "grow",
                    "options": ["suggest","allow","send"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hech narsa",
                    "RightAnswer": "nothing",
                    "options": ["anything","something","who"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qaytmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "return",
                    "options": ["visit","watch","fall"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ona",
                    "RightAnswer": "mother",
                    "options": ["story","product","party"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yurmoq, sayir",
                    "RightAnswer": "walk",
                    "options": ["return","visit","watch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "masala, muhim",
                    "RightAnswer": "matter",
                    "options": ["center","test","power"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aql, fikr",
                    "RightAnswer": "mind",
                    "options": ["matter","center","test"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiymat",
                    "RightAnswer": "value",
                    "options": ["mind","matter","center"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ofis",
                    "RightAnswer": "office",
                    "options": ["mother","story","product"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yozuv, rekord",
                    "RightAnswer": "record",
                    "options": ["value","mind","matter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qolmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stay",
                    "options": ["walk","return","visit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuch",
                    "RightAnswer": "force",
                    "options": ["record","value","mind"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'xtamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stop",
                    "options": ["stay","walk","return"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bir necha",
                    "RightAnswer": "several",
                    "options": ["few","every","that"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yorug', yengil",
                    "RightAnswer": "light",
                    "options": ["past","east","plenty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rivojlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "develop",
                    "options": ["grow","suggest","allow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eslamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "remember",
                    "options": ["develop","grow","suggest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oz, bo'lak",
                    "RightAnswer": "bit",
                    "options": ["office","mother","story"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'lishmoq, ulashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "share",
                    "options": ["stop","stay","walk"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "real",
                    "options": ["local","possible","sure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "javob",
                    "RightAnswer": "answer",
                    "options": ["force","record","value"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'tirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sit",
                    "options": ["remember","develop","grow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqam",
                    "RightAnswer": "figure",
                    "options": ["answer","force","record"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maktub, harf",
                    "RightAnswer": "letter",
                    "options": ["bit","office","mother"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qaror qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "decide",
                    "options": ["sit","remember","develop"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "til",
                    "RightAnswer": "language",
                    "options": ["letter","bit","office"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavzu, fan",
                    "RightAnswer": "subject",
                    "options": ["blog","rose","slice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sinf",
                    "RightAnswer": "class",
                    "options": ["level","kind","criteria"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rivojlanish",
                    "RightAnswer": "development",
                    "options": ["language","letter","bit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shahar",
                    "RightAnswer": "town",
                    "options": ["development","language","letter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yarim",
                    "RightAnswer": "half",
                    "options": ["class","level","kind"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daqiqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "minute",
                    "options": ["town","development","language"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oziq-ovqat",
                    "RightAnswer": "food",
                    "options": ["minute","town","development"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanaffus, sindirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "break",
                    "options": ["share","stop","stay"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq, tozalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "clear",
                    "options": ["open","own","latter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kelajak",
                    "RightAnswer": "future",
                    "options": ["half","class","level"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoki, har ikkisi",
                    "RightAnswer": "either",
                    "options": ["least","enough","much"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldin",
                    "RightAnswer": "ago",
                    "options": ["probably","soon","ever"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "har",
                    "RightAnswer": "per",
                    "options": ["within","against","without"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qolmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "remain",
                    "options": ["decide","sit","remember"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tepa, eng yuqori",
                    "RightAnswer": "top",
                    "options": ["future","half","class"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "orasida",
                    "RightAnswer": "among",
                    "options": ["per","within","against"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yutmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "win",
                    "options": ["break","share","stop"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rang",
                    "RightAnswer": "color",
                    "options": ["figure","answer","force"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jalb qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "involve",
                    "options": ["remain","decide","sit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetmoq, erishmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reach",
                    "options": ["win","break","share"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ijtimoiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "social",
                    "options": ["real","local","possible"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davr, muddat",
                    "RightAnswer": "period",
                    "options": ["food","minute","town"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'ylab",
                    "RightAnswer": "across",
                    "options": ["around","off","through"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eslatma, qayd",
                    "RightAnswer": "note",
                    "options": ["color","figure","answer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarix",
                    "RightAnswer": "history",
                    "options": ["period","food","minute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaratmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "create",
                    "options": ["involve","remain","decide"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haydamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "drive",
                    "options": ["reach","win","break"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'ylab",
                    "RightAnswer": "along",
                    "options": ["across","around","off"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tur, tip",
                    "RightAnswer": "type",
                    "options": ["note","color","figure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tovush",
                    "RightAnswer": "sound",
                    "options": ["type","note","color"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'z",
                    "RightAnswer": "eye",
                    "options": ["sound","type","note"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "musiqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "music",
                    "options": ["history","period","food"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'yin",
                    "RightAnswer": "game",
                    "options": ["music","history","period"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "siyosiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "political",
                    "options": ["social","real","local"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bepul, ozod",
                    "RightAnswer": "free",
                    "options": ["rough","soft","fair"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "receive",
                    "options": ["create","involve","remain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "lahza",
                    "RightAnswer": "moment",
                    "options": ["game","music","history"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "savdo, sotuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "sale",
                    "options": ["moment","game","music"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "siyosat",
                    "RightAnswer": "policy",
                    "options": ["sale","moment","game"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shimcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "further",
                    "options": ["free","rough","soft"]
                }
            ],
            "level 5": [
                {
                    "Question": "tana",
                    "RightAnswer": "body",
                    "options": ["policy","sale","moment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "talab qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "require",
                    "options": ["receive","create","involve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kutmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wait",
                    "options": ["drive","reach","win"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "umumiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "general",
                    "options": ["whole","public","tight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rinmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "appear",
                    "options": ["require","receive","create"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tomon",
                    "RightAnswer": "toward",
                    "options": ["among","per","within"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jamoa",
                    "RightAnswer": "team",
                    "options": ["body","policy","sale"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oson",
                    "RightAnswer": "easy",
                    "options": ["political","social","real"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shaxsiy, individ",
                    "RightAnswer": "individual",
                    "options": ["top","future","half"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'la",
                    "RightAnswer": "full",
                    "options": ["easy","political","social"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qora",
                    "RightAnswer": "black",
                    "options": ["general","whole","public"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma'no, sezgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "sense",
                    "options": ["eye","sound","type"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtimol",
                    "RightAnswer": "perhaps",
                    "options": ["ago","probably","soon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "add",
                    "options": ["appear","require","receive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qoida",
                    "RightAnswer": "rule",
                    "options": ["sense","eye","sound"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'tmoq, o'tish joyi",
                    "RightAnswer": "pass",
                    "options": ["wait","drive","reach"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishlab chiqarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "produce",
                    "options": ["add","appear","require"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sotmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sell",
                    "options": ["produce","add","appear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qisqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "short",
                    "options": ["hard","low","early"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rozi bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "agree",
                    "options": ["sell","produce","add"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qonun",
                    "RightAnswer": "law",
                    "options": ["team","body","policy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamma narsa",
                    "RightAnswer": "everything",
                    "options": ["nothing","anything","something"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tadqiqot",
                    "RightAnswer": "research",
                    "options": ["rule","sense","eye"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qoplamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cover",
                    "options": ["pass","wait","drive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qog'oz, hujjat",
                    "RightAnswer": "paper",
                    "options": ["research","rule","sense"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pozitsiya, lavozim",
                    "RightAnswer": "position",
                    "options": ["paper","research","rule"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "near",
                    "options": ["unlike","via","onto"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "insoniy",
                    "RightAnswer": "human",
                    "options": ["individual","top","future"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kompyuter",
                    "RightAnswer": "computer",
                    "options": ["law","team","body"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vaziyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "situation",
                    "options": ["computer","law","team"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xodimlar",
                    "RightAnswer": "staff",
                    "options": ["situation","computer","law"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faoliyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "activity",
                    "options": ["staff","situation","computer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "film",
                    "RightAnswer": "film",
                    "options": ["position","paper","research"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ertalab",
                    "RightAnswer": "morning",
                    "options": ["activity","staff","situation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "urush",
                    "RightAnswer": "war",
                    "options": ["morning","activity","staff"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisob",
                    "RightAnswer": "account",
                    "options": ["film","position","paper"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "do'kon",
                    "RightAnswer": "shop",
                    "options": ["account","film","position"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "major",
                    "options": ["black","general","whole"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kimdir",
                    "RightAnswer": "someone",
                    "options": ["everything","nothing","anything"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuqorida",
                    "RightAnswer": "above",
                    "options": ["along","across","around"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dizayn, loyihalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "design",
                    "options": ["shop","account","film"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "voqea",
                    "RightAnswer": "event",
                    "options": ["war","morning","activity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maxsus",
                    "RightAnswer": "special",
                    "options": ["full","easy","political"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ba'zida",
                    "RightAnswer": "sometimes",
                    "options": ["perhaps","ago","probably"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "holat, shart",
                    "RightAnswer": "condition",
                    "options": ["event","war","morning"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olib yurmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "carry",
                    "options": ["agree","sell","produce"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "choose",
                    "options": ["carry","agree","sell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ota",
                    "RightAnswer": "father",
                    "options": ["condition","event","war"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qaror",
                    "RightAnswer": "decision",
                    "options": ["father","condition","event"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "stol",
                    "RightAnswer": "table",
                    "options": ["decision","father","condition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq, ba'zi",
                    "RightAnswer": "certain",
                    "options": ["special","full","easy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldinga",
                    "RightAnswer": "forward",
                    "options": ["far","still","only"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "main",
                    "options": ["certain","special","full"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vafot etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "die",
                    "options": ["choose","carry","agree"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ayiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bear",
                    "options": ["cover","pass","wait"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kesmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cut",
                    "options": ["bear","cover","pass"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasvirlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "describe",
                    "options": ["die","choose","carry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zi",
                    "RightAnswer": "himself",
                    "options": ["someone","everything","nothing"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavjud",
                    "RightAnswer": "available",
                    "options": ["main","certain","special"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ayniqsa",
                    "RightAnswer": "especially",
                    "options": ["sometimes","perhaps","ago"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuchli",
                    "RightAnswer": "strong",
                    "options": ["available","main","certain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'tarilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rise",
                    "options": ["cut","bear","cover"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "girl",
                    "options": ["table","decision","father"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "balki",
                    "RightAnswer": "maybe",
                    "options": ["especially","sometimes","perhaps"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamjamiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "community",
                    "options": ["girl","table","decision"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "else",
                    "options": ["maybe","especially","sometimes"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma'lum, alohida",
                    "RightAnswer": "particular",
                    "options": ["strong","available","main"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rol",
                    "RightAnswer": "role",
                    "options": ["community","girl","table"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "join",
                    "options": ["describe","die","choose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiyin",
                    "RightAnswer": "difficult",
                    "options": ["particular","strong","available"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iltimos, mamnun qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "please",
                    "options": ["join","describe","die"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "detal, tafsilot",
                    "RightAnswer": "detail",
                    "options": ["design","shop","account"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "farq",
                    "RightAnswer": "difference",
                    "options": ["role","community","girl"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harakat",
                    "RightAnswer": "action",
                    "options": ["difference","role","community"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sog'liq",
                    "RightAnswer": "health",
                    "options": ["action","difference","role"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yemoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "eat",
                    "options": ["please","join","describe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qadam",
                    "RightAnswer": "step",
                    "options": ["detail","design","shop"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rost",
                    "RightAnswer": "true",
                    "options": ["difficult","particular","strong"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "telefon",
                    "RightAnswer": "phone",
                    "options": ["step","detail","design"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zlarini",
                    "RightAnswer": "themselves",
                    "options": ["himself","someone","everything"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chizmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "draw",
                    "options": ["eat","please","join"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oq",
                    "RightAnswer": "white",
                    "options": ["major","black","general"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sana, uchrashuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "date",
                    "options": ["phone","step","detail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mashq, amaliyot",
                    "RightAnswer": "practice",
                    "options": ["date","phone","step"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "model",
                    "RightAnswer": "model",
                    "options": ["practice","date","phone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'tarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "raise",
                    "options": ["rise","cut","bear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mijoz",
                    "RightAnswer": "customer",
                    "options": ["health","action","difference"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "old qism",
                    "RightAnswer": "front",
                    "options": ["human","individual","top"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushuntirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "explain",
                    "options": ["draw","eat","please"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eshik",
                    "RightAnswer": "door",
                    "options": ["customer","health","action"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashqarida",
                    "RightAnswer": "outside",
                    "options": ["tonight","tomorrow","yesterday"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "orqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "behind",
                    "options": ["above","along","across"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iqtisodiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "economic",
                    "options": ["true","difficult","particular"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sayt, joy",
                    "RightAnswer": "site",
                    "options": ["door","customer","health"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yondashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "approach",
                    "options": ["raise","rise","cut"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'qituvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "teacher",
                    "options": ["site","door","customer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yer, qishloq",
                    "RightAnswer": "land",
                    "options": ["model","practice","date"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zaryad, jarima",
                    "RightAnswer": "charge",
                    "options": ["land","model","practice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nihoyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "finally",
                    "options": ["else","maybe","especially"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "belgi, imzolamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sign",
                    "options": ["charge","land","model"]
                }
            ],
            "level 6": [
                {
                    "Question": "da'vo qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "claim",
                    "options": ["sign","charge","land"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "munosabat",
                    "RightAnswer": "relationship",
                    "options": ["teacher","site","door"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sayohat",
                    "RightAnswer": "travel",
                    "options": ["claim","sign","charge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rohatlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "enjoy",
                    "options": ["explain","draw","eat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'lim",
                    "RightAnswer": "death",
                    "options": ["relationship","teacher","site"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoqimli",
                    "RightAnswer": "nice",
                    "options": ["economic","true","difficult"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "miqdor",
                    "RightAnswer": "amount",
                    "options": ["travel","claim","sign"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaxshilamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "improve",
                    "options": ["enjoy","explain","draw"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rasm",
                    "RightAnswer": "picture",
                    "options": ["amount","travel","claim"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bola, o'g'il",
                    "RightAnswer": "boy",
                    "options": ["death","relationship","teacher"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hurmat, e'tibor",
                    "RightAnswer": "regard",
                    "options": ["picture","amount","travel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashkilot",
                    "RightAnswer": "organization",
                    "options": ["boy","death","relationship"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baxtli",
                    "RightAnswer": "happy",
                    "options": ["nice","economic","true"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "juft",
                    "RightAnswer": "couple",
                    "options": ["regard","picture","amount"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harakat",
                    "RightAnswer": "act",
                    "options": ["couple","regard","picture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "diapazon",
                    "RightAnswer": "range",
                    "options": ["act","couple","regard"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sifat",
                    "RightAnswer": "quality",
                    "options": ["organization","boy","death"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "loyiha",
                    "RightAnswer": "project",
                    "options": ["range","act","couple"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "doira, atrof",
                    "RightAnswer": "round",
                    "options": ["abstract","concrete","parallel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imkoniyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "opportunity",
                    "options": ["quality","organization","boy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "road",
                    "options": ["opportunity","quality","organization"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kelishuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "accord",
                    "options": ["project","range","act"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ro'yxat",
                    "RightAnswer": "list",
                    "options": ["accord","project","range"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tilamoq, orzu",
                    "RightAnswer": "wish",
                    "options": ["list","accord","project"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shuning uchun",
                    "RightAnswer": "therefore",
                    "options": ["though","whereas","unless"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kiymoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wear",
                    "options": ["approach","raise","rise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mablag'",
                    "RightAnswer": "fund",
                    "options": ["wish","list","accord"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dam olmoq, qolgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "rest",
                    "options": ["fund","wish","list"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bola ",
                    "RightAnswer": "kid",
                    "options": ["rest","fund","wish"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sanoat",
                    "RightAnswer": "industry",
                    "options": ["road","opportunity","quality"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'lim",
                    "RightAnswer": "education",
                    "options": ["industry","road","opportunity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'lchov, o'lchamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "measure",
                    "options": ["kid","rest","fund"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'ldirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "kill",
                    "options": ["improve","enjoy","explain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xizmat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "serve",
                    "options": ["kill","improve","enjoy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtimol",
                    "RightAnswer": "likely",
                    "options": ["short","hard","low"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "albatta",
                    "RightAnswer": "certainly",
                    "options": ["finally","else","maybe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "milliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "national",
                    "options": ["happy","nice","economic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zi",
                    "RightAnswer": "itself",
                    "options": ["themselves","himself","someone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rgatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "teach",
                    "options": ["serve","kill","improve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soha, dala",
                    "RightAnswer": "field",
                    "options": ["measure","kid","rest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavfsizlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "security",
                    "options": ["education","industry","road"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "havo",
                    "RightAnswer": "air",
                    "options": ["field","measure","kid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foyda",
                    "RightAnswer": "benefit",
                    "options": ["air","field","measure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "savdo",
                    "RightAnswer": "trade",
                    "options": ["benefit","air","field"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavf",
                    "RightAnswer": "risk",
                    "options": ["trade","benefit","air"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yangilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "news",
                    "options": ["security","education","industry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "standart",
                    "RightAnswer": "standard",
                    "options": ["front","human","individual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ovoz bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "vote",
                    "options": ["risk","trade","benefit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "percent",
                    "options": ["news","security","education"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "diqqat markazi",
                    "RightAnswer": "focus",
                    "options": ["vote","risk","trade"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosqich",
                    "RightAnswer": "stage",
                    "options": ["focus","vote","risk"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fazo",
                    "RightAnswer": "space",
                    "options": ["subject","blog","rose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rniga",
                    "RightAnswer": "instead",
                    "options": ["down","out","up"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "anglamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "realize",
                    "options": ["teach","serve","kill"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "usually",
                    "options": ["certainly","finally","else"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma'lumot",
                    "RightAnswer": "data",
                    "options": ["percent","news","security"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yakka, yolg'iz",
                    "RightAnswer": "single",
                    "options": ["white","major","black"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "manzil",
                    "RightAnswer": "address",
                    "options": ["stage","focus","vote"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ijro",
                    "RightAnswer": "performance",
                    "options": ["data","percent","news"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imkoniyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "chance",
                    "options": ["address","stage","focus"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qabul qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "accept",
                    "options": ["realize","teach","serve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jamiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "society",
                    "options": ["performance","data","percent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "texnologiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "technology",
                    "options": ["society","performance","data"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tilga olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "mention",
                    "options": ["chance","address","stage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanlov",
                    "RightAnswer": "choice",
                    "options": ["technology","society","performance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saqlamoq, tejamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "save",
                    "options": ["wear","approach","raise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "umumiy, keng tarqalgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "common",
                    "options": ["single","white","major"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "madaniyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "culture",
                    "options": ["choice","technology","society"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "umumiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "total",
                    "options": ["common","single","white"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "talab",
                    "RightAnswer": "demand",
                    "options": ["mention","chance","address"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "material, ashyo",
                    "RightAnswer": "material",
                    "options": ["standard","front","human"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chegaralamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "limit",
                    "options": ["demand","mention","chance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tinglamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "listen",
                    "options": ["accept","realize","teach"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kerak, sabab",
                    "RightAnswer": "due",
                    "options": ["total","common","single"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noto'g'ri",
                    "RightAnswer": "wrong",
                    "options": ["right","alright","okay"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oyoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "foot",
                    "options": ["culture","choice","technology"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sa'y-harakat",
                    "RightAnswer": "effort",
                    "options": ["foot","culture","choice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'tibor",
                    "RightAnswer": "attention",
                    "options": ["effort","foot","culture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ustida",
                    "RightAnswer": "upon",
                    "options": ["toward","among","per"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tekshirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "check",
                    "options": ["limit","demand","mention"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'liq, yakunlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "complete",
                    "options": ["clear","open","own"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yolg'on, yotmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "lie",
                    "options": ["save","wear","approach"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pick",
                    "options": ["lie","save","wear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamaytirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reduce",
                    "options": ["listen","accept","realize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shaxsiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "personal",
                    "options": ["national","happy","nice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yer, asos",
                    "RightAnswer": "ground",
                    "options": ["check","limit","demand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayvon",
                    "RightAnswer": "animal",
                    "options": ["attention","effort","foot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetib kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "arrive",
                    "options": ["reduce","listen","accept"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bemor, sabrli",
                    "RightAnswer": "patient",
                    "options": ["material","standard","front"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joriy",
                    "RightAnswer": "current",
                    "options": ["due","total","common"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asr",
                    "RightAnswer": "century",
                    "options": ["animal","attention","effort"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dalil",
                    "RightAnswer": "evidence",
                    "options": ["century","animal","attention"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavjud bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exist",
                    "options": ["arrive","reduce","listen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'xshash",
                    "RightAnswer": "similar",
                    "options": ["personal","national","happy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jang qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fight",
                    "options": ["ground","check","limit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetakchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "leader",
                    "options": ["evidence","century","animal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaxshi, jarima",
                    "RightAnswer": "fine",
                    "options": ["present","tall","opposite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'cha",
                    "RightAnswer": "street",
                    "options": ["leader","evidence","century"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sobiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "former",
                    "options": ["similar","personal","national"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aloqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "contact",
                    "options": ["fight","ground","check"]
                }
            ],
            "level 7": [
                {
                    "Question": "ayniqsa",
                    "RightAnswer": "particularly",
                    "options": ["usually","certainly","finally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xotin",
                    "RightAnswer": "wife",
                    "options": ["street","leader","evidence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sport",
                    "RightAnswer": "sport",
                    "options": ["contact","fight","ground"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayyorlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "prepare",
                    "options": ["exist","arrive","reduce"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhokama qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "discuss",
                    "options": ["prepare","exist","arrive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "javob",
                    "RightAnswer": "response",
                    "options": ["wife","street","leader"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ovoz",
                    "RightAnswer": "voice",
                    "options": ["sport","contact","fight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "parcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "piece",
                    "options": ["response","wife","street"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tugatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "finish",
                    "options": ["pick","lie","save"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxmin qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "suppose",
                    "options": ["discuss","prepare","exist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'llamoq, ariza bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "apply",
                    "options": ["suppose","discuss","prepare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "prezident",
                    "RightAnswer": "president",
                    "options": ["piece","response","wife"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olov, ishdan bo'shatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fire",
                    "options": ["voice","sport","contact"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqqoslamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "compare",
                    "options": ["apply","suppose","discuss"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sud",
                    "RightAnswer": "court",
                    "options": ["fire","voice","sport"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "politsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "police",
                    "options": ["president","piece","response"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "do'kon, saqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "store",
                    "options": ["court","fire","voice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kambag'al",
                    "RightAnswer": "poor",
                    "options": ["former","similar","personal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bilim",
                    "RightAnswer": "knowledge",
                    "options": ["police","president","piece"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kulmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "laugh",
                    "options": ["store","court","fire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'l, qurol",
                    "RightAnswer": "arm",
                    "options": ["laugh","store","court"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yurak",
                    "RightAnswer": "heart",
                    "options": ["knowledge","police","president"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "manba",
                    "RightAnswer": "source",
                    "options": ["heart","knowledge","police"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xodim",
                    "RightAnswer": "employee",
                    "options": ["source","heart","knowledge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshqarmoq, uddalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "manage",
                    "options": ["compare","apply","suppose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oddiygina",
                    "RightAnswer": "simply",
                    "options": ["particularly","usually","certainly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bank",
                    "RightAnswer": "bank",
                    "options": ["arm","laugh","store"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "firma, qattiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "firm",
                    "options": ["patient","material","standard"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hujayra, katak",
                    "RightAnswer": "cell",
                    "options": ["employee","source","heart"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqola, band",
                    "RightAnswer": "article",
                    "options": ["cell","employee","source"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tez",
                    "RightAnswer": "fast",
                    "options": ["wrong","right","alright"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hujum qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "attack",
                    "options": ["bank","arm","laugh"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xorijiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "foreign",
                    "options": ["poor","former","similar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayrat, ajablantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "surprise",
                    "options": ["attack","bank","arm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xususiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "feature",
                    "options": ["surprise","attack","bank"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "omil",
                    "RightAnswer": "factor",
                    "options": ["article","cell","employee"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiroyli",
                    "RightAnswer": "pretty",
                    "options": ["likely","short","hard"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaqinda",
                    "RightAnswer": "recently",
                    "options": ["simply","particularly","usually"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'sir qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "affect",
                    "options": ["manage","compare","apply"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushmoq, tomchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "drop",
                    "options": ["finish","pick","lie"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaqinda sodir bo‘lgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "recent",
                    "options": ["foreign","poor","former"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog‘lanmoq, aloqador",
                    "RightAnswer": "relate",
                    "options": ["affect","manage","compare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rasmiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "official",
                    "options": ["current","due","total"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moliyaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "financial",
                    "options": ["recent","foreign","poor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'tkazib yubormoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "miss",
                    "options": ["drop","finish","pick"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "san’at",
                    "RightAnswer": "art",
                    "options": ["factor","article","cell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashkiliy harakat",
                    "RightAnswer": "campaign",
                    "options": ["feature","surprise","attack"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xususiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "private",
                    "options": ["official","current","due"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to‘xtatish, pauza",
                    "RightAnswer": "pause",
                    "options": ["campaign","feature","surprise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamma",
                    "RightAnswer": "everyone",
                    "options": ["itself","themselves","himself"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "unutmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "forget",
                    "options": ["relate","affect","manage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sahifa",
                    "RightAnswer": "page",
                    "options": ["pause","campaign","feature"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavotirlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "worry",
                    "options": ["page","pause","campaign"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoz",
                    "RightAnswer": "summer",
                    "options": ["art","factor","article"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ichimlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "drink",
                    "options": ["worry","page","pause"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fikr",
                    "RightAnswer": "opinion",
                    "options": ["summer","art","factor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hiyobon, mashinani joylashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "park",
                    "options": ["drink","worry","page"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vakil bo‘lmoq, ifodalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "represent",
                    "options": ["forget","relate","affect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kalit, muhim",
                    "RightAnswer": "key",
                    "options": ["firm","patient","material"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ichida",
                    "RightAnswer": "inside",
                    "options": ["alongside","regardless","beneath"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "menejer",
                    "RightAnswer": "manager",
                    "options": ["opinion","summer","art"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xalqaro",
                    "RightAnswer": "international",
                    "options": ["financial","recent","foreign"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘z ichiga olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "contain",
                    "options": ["represent","forget","relate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e’tibor, bildirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "notice",
                    "options": ["park","drink","worry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayron bo‘lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wonder",
                    "options": ["notice","park","drink"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tabiat",
                    "RightAnswer": "nature",
                    "options": ["manager","opinion","summer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuzilma",
                    "RightAnswer": "structure",
                    "options": ["wonder","notice","park"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo‘lim",
                    "RightAnswer": "section",
                    "options": ["nature","manager","opinion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘zim",
                    "RightAnswer": "myself",
                    "options": ["everyone","itself","themselves"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exactly",
                    "options": ["recently","simply","particularly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘simlik, zavod",
                    "RightAnswer": "plant",
                    "options": ["structure","wonder","notice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo‘yoq, bo‘yamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "paint",
                    "options": ["plant","structure","wonder"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "worker",
                    "options": ["section","nature","manager"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosma, press",
                    "RightAnswer": "press",
                    "options": ["paint","plant","structure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nima bo'lsa ham",
                    "RightAnswer": "whatever",
                    "options": ["self","ourselves","anybody"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zarur",
                    "RightAnswer": "necessary",
                    "options": ["international","financial","recent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mintaqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "region",
                    "options": ["worker","section","nature"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘sish",
                    "RightAnswer": "growth",
                    "options": ["region","worker","section"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kechki vaqt",
                    "RightAnswer": "evening",
                    "options": ["key","firm","patient"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'sir",
                    "RightAnswer": "influence",
                    "options": ["press","paint","plant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hurmat",
                    "RightAnswer": "respect",
                    "options": ["influence","press","paint"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "turli",
                    "RightAnswer": "various",
                    "options": ["necessary","international","financial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ushlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "catch",
                    "options": ["miss","drop","finish"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shuning uchun",
                    "RightAnswer": "thus",
                    "options": ["exactly","recently","simply"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko‘nikma",
                    "RightAnswer": "skill",
                    "options": ["growth","region","worker"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "urinish",
                    "RightAnswer": "attempt",
                    "options": ["respect","influence","press"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘g‘il",
                    "RightAnswer": "son",
                    "options": ["skill","growth","region"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oddiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "simple",
                    "options": ["various","necessary","international"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘rta",
                    "RightAnswer": "medium",
                    "options": ["evening","key","firm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘rtacha",
                    "RightAnswer": "average",
                    "options": ["private","official","current"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ombor, aksiyalar",
                    "RightAnswer": "stock",
                    "options": ["light","past","east"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshqaruv",
                    "RightAnswer": "management",
                    "options": ["son","skill","growth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xarakter, belgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "character",
                    "options": ["management","son","skill"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yotoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bed",
                    "options": ["character","management","son"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "urmoq, zarba",
                    "RightAnswer": "hit",
                    "options": ["catch","miss","drop"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashkil qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "establish",
                    "options": ["contain","represent","forget"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqatan",
                    "RightAnswer": "indeed",
                    "options": ["thus","exactly","recently"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yakuniy",
                    "RightAnswer": "final",
                    "options": ["average","private","official"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iqtisodiyot",
                    "RightAnswer": "economy",
                    "options": ["bed","character","management"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mos kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fit",
                    "options": ["moderate","mature","alter"]
                }
            ],
            "level 8": [
                {
                    "Question": "yigit",
                    "RightAnswer": "guy",
                    "options": ["economy","bed","character"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "funksiya, vazifa",
                    "RightAnswer": "function",
                    "options": ["attempt","respect","influence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kecha",
                    "RightAnswer": "yesterday",
                    "options": ["today","home","bottom"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rasm, tasvir",
                    "RightAnswer": "image",
                    "options": ["function","attempt","respect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘lcham",
                    "RightAnswer": "size",
                    "options": ["image","function","attempt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xulq-atvor",
                    "RightAnswer": "behavior",
                    "options": ["guy","economy","bed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo‘shimcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "addition",
                    "options": ["behavior","guy","economy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "belgilamoq, aniqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "determine",
                    "options": ["establish","contain","represent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "stansiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "station",
                    "options": ["addition","behavior","guy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aholi",
                    "RightAnswer": "population",
                    "options": ["station","addition","behavior"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uddasidan chiqmaslik",
                    "RightAnswer": "fail",
                    "options": ["hit","catch","miss"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhit",
                    "RightAnswer": "environment",
                    "options": ["population","station","addition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishlab chiqarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "production",
                    "options": ["environment","population","station"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shartnoma, qisqartmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "contract",
                    "options": ["size","image","function"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘yinchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "player",
                    "options": ["production","environment","population"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "izoh, fikr bildirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "comment",
                    "options": ["contract","size","image"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "enter",
                    "options": ["determine","establish","contain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uchrab turmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "occur",
                    "options": ["enter","determine","establish"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yolg‘iz",
                    "RightAnswer": "alone",
                    "options": ["pretty","likely","short"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhim, ahamiyatli",
                    "RightAnswer": "significant",
                    "options": ["simple","various","necessary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dori",
                    "RightAnswer": "drug",
                    "options": ["player","production","environment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "devor",
                    "RightAnswer": "wall",
                    "options": ["drug","player","production"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "seriya",
                    "RightAnswer": "series",
                    "options": ["wall","drug","player"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to‘g‘ridan-to‘g‘ri, boshqarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "direct",
                    "options": ["complete","clear","open"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muvaffaqiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "success",
                    "options": ["series","wall","drug"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ertaga",
                    "RightAnswer": "tomorrow",
                    "options": ["yesterday","today","home"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "director",
                    "options": ["success","series","wall"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq, ravshan",
                    "RightAnswer": "clearly",
                    "options": ["indeed","thus","exactly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetishmaslik",
                    "RightAnswer": "lack",
                    "options": ["comment","contract","size"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko‘rib chiqmoq, sharh",
                    "RightAnswer": "review",
                    "options": ["lack","comment","contract"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog‘liq bo‘lish",
                    "RightAnswer": "depend",
                    "options": ["occur","enter","determine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "irq, poyga",
                    "RightAnswer": "race",
                    "options": ["review","lack","comment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanimoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "recognize",
                    "options": ["depend","occur","enter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "deraza",
                    "RightAnswer": "window",
                    "options": ["director","success","series"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqsad",
                    "RightAnswer": "purpose",
                    "options": ["window","director","success"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo‘lim",
                    "RightAnswer": "department",
                    "options": ["purpose","window","director"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "erishmoq, foyda olish",
                    "RightAnswer": "gain",
                    "options": ["race","review","lack"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daraxt",
                    "RightAnswer": "tree",
                    "options": ["department","purpose","window"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kollej",
                    "RightAnswer": "college",
                    "options": ["tree","department","purpose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bahslashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "argue",
                    "options": ["recognize","depend","occur"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxta",
                    "RightAnswer": "board",
                    "options": ["gain","race","review"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'til",
                    "RightAnswer": "holiday",
                    "options": ["college","tree","department"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "belgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "mark",
                    "options": ["board","gain","race"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cherkov",
                    "RightAnswer": "church",
                    "options": ["holiday","college","tree"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurilma",
                    "RightAnswer": "machine",
                    "options": ["church","holiday","college"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "erishmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "achieve",
                    "options": ["argue","recognize","depend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "buyum, narsalar",
                    "RightAnswer": "item",
                    "options": ["machine","church","holiday"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "isbotlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "prove",
                    "options": ["achieve","argue","recognize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sent",
                    "RightAnswer": "cent",
                    "options": ["item","machine","church"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fasl",
                    "RightAnswer": "season",
                    "options": ["cent","item","machine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pol, qavat",
                    "RightAnswer": "floor",
                    "options": ["mark","board","gain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "narsalar",
                    "RightAnswer": "stuff",
                    "options": ["floor","mark","board"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keng",
                    "RightAnswer": "wide",
                    "options": ["alone","pretty","likely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "har kim",
                    "RightAnswer": "anyone",
                    "options": ["myself","everyone","itself"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "usul",
                    "RightAnswer": "method",
                    "options": ["season","cent","item"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tahlil",
                    "RightAnswer": "analysis",
                    "options": ["method","season","cent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saylov",
                    "RightAnswer": "election",
                    "options": ["analysis","method","season"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harbiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "military",
                    "options": ["final","average","private"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mehmonxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "hotel",
                    "options": ["election","analysis","method"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "klub",
                    "RightAnswer": "club",
                    "options": ["stuff","floor","mark"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pastda",
                    "RightAnswer": "below",
                    "options": ["behind","above","along"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "film",
                    "RightAnswer": "movie",
                    "options": ["hotel","election","analysis"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shifokor",
                    "RightAnswer": "doctor",
                    "options": ["club","stuff","floor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhokama",
                    "RightAnswer": "discussion",
                    "options": ["movie","hotel","election"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzr",
                    "RightAnswer": "sorry",
                    "options": ["significant","simple","various"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chaqiriq, qiyinchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "challenge",
                    "options": ["doctor","club","stuff"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "millat",
                    "RightAnswer": "nation",
                    "options": ["discussion","movie","hotel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "deyarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "nearly",
                    "options": ["clearly","indeed","thus"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bayonot",
                    "RightAnswer": "statement",
                    "options": ["nation","discussion","movie"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog‘lanish, havola",
                    "RightAnswer": "link",
                    "options": ["challenge","doctor","club"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qaramasdan",
                    "RightAnswer": "despite",
                    "options": ["upon","toward","among"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanishtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "introduce",
                    "options": ["prove","achieve","argue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "afzallik",
                    "RightAnswer": "advantage",
                    "options": ["statement","nation","discussion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayyor",
                    "RightAnswer": "ready",
                    "options": ["wide","alone","pretty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "turmush qurmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "marry",
                    "options": ["introduce","prove","achieve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zarba",
                    "RightAnswer": "strike",
                    "options": ["fail","hit","catch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mil",
                    "RightAnswer": "mile",
                    "options": ["advantage","statement","nation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "izlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "seek",
                    "options": ["marry","introduce","prove"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qobiliyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "ability",
                    "options": ["mile","advantage","statement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "unit",
                    "options": ["ability","mile","advantage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "karta",
                    "RightAnswer": "card",
                    "options": ["unit","ability","mile"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shifoxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "hospital",
                    "options": ["card","unit","ability"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tezda",
                    "RightAnswer": "quickly",
                    "options": ["nearly","clearly","indeed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suhbat",
                    "RightAnswer": "interview",
                    "options": ["link","challenge","doctor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kelishuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "agreement",
                    "options": ["hospital","card","unit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ozod qilmoq, chiqarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "release",
                    "options": ["interview","link","challenge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "tax",
                    "options": ["release","interview","link"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yechim",
                    "RightAnswer": "solution",
                    "options": ["agreement","hospital","card"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "poytaxt",
                    "RightAnswer": "capital",
                    "options": ["medium","evening","key"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mashhur",
                    "RightAnswer": "popular",
                    "options": ["sorry","significant","simple"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq, maxsus",
                    "RightAnswer": "specific",
                    "options": ["popular","sorry","significant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiroyli",
                    "RightAnswer": "beautiful",
                    "options": ["specific","popular","sorry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo‘rquv",
                    "RightAnswer": "fear",
                    "options": ["tax","release","interview"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqsad",
                    "RightAnswer": "aim",
                    "options": ["fear","tax","release"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "televizor",
                    "RightAnswer": "television",
                    "options": ["solution","agreement","hospital"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jiddiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "serious",
                    "options": ["beautiful","specific","popular"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqsad",
                    "RightAnswer": "target",
                    "options": ["aim","fear","tax"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daraja",
                    "RightAnswer": "degree",
                    "options": ["television","solution","agreement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tortmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pull",
                    "options": ["strike","fail","hit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qizil",
                    "RightAnswer": "red",
                    "options": ["military","final","average"]
                }
            ],
            "level 9": [
                {
                    "Question": "er",
                    "RightAnswer": "husband",
                    "options": ["degree","television","solution"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kirish imkoniyati",
                    "RightAnswer": "access",
                    "options": ["target","aim","fear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harakat",
                    "RightAnswer": "movement",
                    "options": ["husband","degree","television"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davolamoq, munosabatda bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "treat",
                    "options": ["pull","strike","fail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "identify",
                    "options": ["seek","marry","introduce"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo‘qotish",
                    "RightAnswer": "loss",
                    "options": ["movement","husband","degree"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zamonaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "modern",
                    "options": ["serious","beautiful","specific"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosim",
                    "RightAnswer": "pressure",
                    "options": ["access","target","aim"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "avtobus",
                    "RightAnswer": "bus",
                    "options": ["loss","movement","husband"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davolash",
                    "RightAnswer": "treatment",
                    "options": ["bus","loss","movement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "konferensiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "conference",
                    "options": ["treatment","bus","loss"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘zingiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "yourself",
                    "options": ["anyone","myself","everyone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'minlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "supply",
                    "options": ["pressure","access","target"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qishloq",
                    "RightAnswer": "village",
                    "options": ["conference","treatment","bus"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiymatli",
                    "RightAnswer": "worth",
                    "options": ["red","military","final"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tabiiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "natural",
                    "options": ["modern","serious","beautiful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ifodalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "express",
                    "options": ["close","mean","insure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko‘rsatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "indicate",
                    "options": ["identify","seek","marry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qatnashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "attend",
                    "options": ["indicate","identify","seek"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aka, uka",
                    "RightAnswer": "brother",
                    "options": ["village","conference","treatment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "investitsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "investment",
                    "options": ["brother","village","conference"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ball, natija",
                    "RightAnswer": "score",
                    "options": ["supply","pressure","access"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashkil qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "organize",
                    "options": ["attend","indicate","identify"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "safar, sayohat",
                    "RightAnswer": "trip",
                    "options": ["score","supply","pressure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ortda, tashqarida",
                    "RightAnswer": "beyond",
                    "options": ["below","behind","above"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uxlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sleep",
                    "options": ["trip","score","supply"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fish",
                    "options": ["sleep","trip","score"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "va'da",
                    "RightAnswer": "promise",
                    "options": ["fish","sleep","trip"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "potentsial",
                    "RightAnswer": "potential",
                    "options": ["worth","red","military"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "energiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "energy",
                    "options": ["investment","brother","village"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muammo",
                    "RightAnswer": "trouble",
                    "options": ["promise","fish","sleep"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "munosabat",
                    "RightAnswer": "relation",
                    "options": ["energy","investment","brother"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teginmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "touch",
                    "options": ["trouble","promise","fish"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fayl",
                    "RightAnswer": "file",
                    "options": ["touch","trouble","promise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘rtasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "middle",
                    "options": ["royal","voluntary","experimental"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ustun",
                    "RightAnswer": "bar",
                    "options": ["file","touch","trouble"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "azob chekmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "suffer",
                    "options": ["organize","attend","indicate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "strategiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "strategy",
                    "options": ["relation","energy","investment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chuqur",
                    "RightAnswer": "deep",
                    "options": ["ready","wide","alone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "… dan tashqari",
                    "RightAnswer": "except",
                    "options": ["until","since","before"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tozalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "clean",
                    "options": ["direct","complete","clear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moyillik ko‘rsatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "tend",
                    "options": ["suffer","organize","attend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldinga yurmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "advance",
                    "options": ["space","subject","blog"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to‘ldirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fill",
                    "options": ["treat","pull","strike"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yulduz",
                    "RightAnswer": "star",
                    "options": ["bar","file","touch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "network",
                    "options": ["star","bar","file"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "generally",
                    "options": ["quickly","nearly","clearly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "operatsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "operation",
                    "options": ["strategy","relation","energy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mos kelmoq, o‘yin",
                    "RightAnswer": "match",
                    "options": ["network","star","bar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chetlab o‘tmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "avoid",
                    "options": ["tend","suffer","organize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o‘rindiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "seat",
                    "options": ["match","network","star"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "otmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "throw",
                    "options": ["fill","treat","pull"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vazifa",
                    "RightAnswer": "task",
                    "options": ["operation","strategy","relation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odatiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "normal",
                    "options": ["potential","worth","red"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqsad",
                    "RightAnswer": "goal",
                    "options": ["task","operation","strategy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog‘lanmoq, sherik",
                    "RightAnswer": "associate",
                    "options": ["throw","fill","treat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko‘k",
                    "RightAnswer": "blue",
                    "options": ["normal","potential","worth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ijobiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "positive",
                    "options": ["blue","normal","potential"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "variant, tanlov",
                    "RightAnswer": "option",
                    "options": ["goal","task","operation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "quti",
                    "RightAnswer": "box",
                    "options": ["seat","match","network"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ulkan",
                    "RightAnswer": "huge",
                    "options": ["natural","modern","serious"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xabar",
                    "RightAnswer": "message",
                    "options": ["option","goal","task"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "misol",
                    "RightAnswer": "instance",
                    "options": ["message","option","goal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uslub",
                    "RightAnswer": "style",
                    "options": ["box","seat","match"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "murojaat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "refer",
                    "options": ["avoid","tend","suffer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sovuq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cold",
                    "options": ["middle","royal","voluntary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "itarmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "push",
                    "options": ["associate","throw","fill"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chorak",
                    "RightAnswer": "quarter",
                    "options": ["stock","light","past"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faraz qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "assume",
                    "options": ["refer","avoid","tend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chaqaloq",
                    "RightAnswer": "baby",
                    "options": ["capital","medium","evening"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muvaffaqiyatli",
                    "RightAnswer": "successful",
                    "options": ["huge","natural","modern"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuylamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sing",
                    "options": ["assume","refer","avoid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shubha",
                    "RightAnswer": "doubt",
                    "options": ["style","box","seat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqobat",
                    "RightAnswer": "competition",
                    "options": ["instance","message","option"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nazariya",
                    "RightAnswer": "theory",
                    "options": ["competition","instance","message"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "propose",
                    "options": ["sing","assume","refer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma’lumotnoma, havola",
                    "RightAnswer": "reference",
                    "options": ["doubt","style","box"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bahs, dalil",
                    "RightAnswer": "argument",
                    "options": ["theory","competition","instance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kattalar",
                    "RightAnswer": "adult",
                    "options": ["baby","capital","medium"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uchmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fly",
                    "options": ["push","associate","throw"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hujjat",
                    "RightAnswer": "document",
                    "options": ["reference","doubt","style"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "naqsh",
                    "RightAnswer": "pattern",
                    "options": ["document","reference","doubt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ariza, dastur",
                    "RightAnswer": "application",
                    "options": ["argument","theory","competition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "issiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hot",
                    "options": ["deep","ready","wide"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "albatta",
                    "RightAnswer": "obviously",
                    "options": ["generally","quickly","nearly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noaniq",
                    "RightAnswer": "unclear",
                    "options": ["successful","huge","natural"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uy to'lovi",
                    "RightAnswer": "bill",
                    "options": ["pattern","document","reference"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qidirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "search",
                    "options": ["bill","pattern","document"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajratmoq, alohida",
                    "RightAnswer": "separate",
                    "options": ["clean","direct","complete"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "markaziy",
                    "RightAnswer": "central",
                    "options": ["unclear","successful","huge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kasbiy faoliyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "career",
                    "options": ["application","argument","theory"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nima bolsa ham",
                    "RightAnswer": "anyway",
                    "options": ["obviously","generally","quickly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nutq",
                    "RightAnswer": "speech",
                    "options": ["career","application","argument"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "it",
                    "RightAnswer": "dog",
                    "options": ["speech","career","application"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ofitser",
                    "RightAnswer": "officer",
                    "options": ["dog","speech","career"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo‘ylab, davomida",
                    "RightAnswer": "throughout",
                    "options": ["beyond","below","behind"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "neft, yog‘",
                    "RightAnswer": "oil",
                    "options": ["officer","dog","speech"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "libos, kiymoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "dress",
                    "options": ["fly","push","associate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foyda",
                    "RightAnswer": "profit",
                    "options": ["search","bill","pattern"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxmin qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "guess",
                    "options": ["dress","fly","push"]
                }
            ],
            "level 10": [
                {
                    "Question": "ko'ngilochar, qiziqarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "fun",
                    "options": ["oil","officer","dog"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "himoya qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "protect",
                    "options": ["propose","sing","assume"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "manba",
                    "RightAnswer": "resource",
                    "options": ["profit","search","bill"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ilm-fan",
                    "RightAnswer": "science",
                    "options": ["fun","oil","officer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kasallik",
                    "RightAnswer": "disease",
                    "options": ["science","fun","oil"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muvozanat",
                    "RightAnswer": "balance",
                    "options": ["resource","profit","search"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zarar yetkazmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "damage",
                    "options": ["balance","resource","profit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asos",
                    "RightAnswer": "basis",
                    "options": ["disease","science","fun"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muallif",
                    "RightAnswer": "author",
                    "options": ["basis","disease","science"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "basic",
                    "options": ["central","unclear","successful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rag'batlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "encourage",
                    "options": ["protect","propose","sing"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soch",
                    "RightAnswer": "hair",
                    "options": ["author","basis","disease"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "erkak",
                    "RightAnswer": "male",
                    "options": ["positive","blue","normal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faoliyat yuritmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "operate",
                    "options": ["encourage","protect","propose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aks ettirmoq, fikr yuritmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reflect",
                    "options": ["guess","dress","fly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mashq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exercise",
                    "options": ["damage","balance","resource"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foydali",
                    "RightAnswer": "useful",
                    "options": ["basic","central","unclear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "restoran",
                    "RightAnswer": "restaurant",
                    "options": ["hair","author","basis"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daromad",
                    "RightAnswer": "income",
                    "options": ["restaurant","hair","author"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mulk",
                    "RightAnswer": "property",
                    "options": ["income","restaurant","hair"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldingi",
                    "RightAnswer": "previous",
                    "options": ["hot","deep","ready"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qorong'u",
                    "RightAnswer": "dark",
                    "options": ["cold","middle","royal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasavvur qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "imagine",
                    "options": ["operate","encourage","protect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaxshi",
                    "RightAnswer": "okay",
                    "options": ["monthly","weekly","mad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daromad topmoq, ishlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "earn",
                    "options": ["imagine","operate","encourage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiz farzand",
                    "RightAnswer": "daughter",
                    "options": ["property","income","restaurant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pochta, lavozim",
                    "RightAnswer": "post",
                    "options": ["exercise","damage","balance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gazeta",
                    "RightAnswer": "newspaper",
                    "options": ["daughter","property","income"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'riflamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "define",
                    "options": ["earn","imagine","operate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xulosa",
                    "RightAnswer": "conclusion",
                    "options": ["newspaper","daughter","property"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soat",
                    "RightAnswer": "clock",
                    "options": ["post","exercise","damage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamma",
                    "RightAnswer": "everybody",
                    "options": ["yourself","anyone","myself"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dam olish kuni",
                    "RightAnswer": "weekend",
                    "options": ["conclusion","newspaper","daughter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bajarmoq, ijro etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "perform",
                    "options": ["define","earn","imagine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "professional, kasbiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "professional",
                    "options": ["male","positive","blue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kon, meniki",
                    "RightAnswer": "mine",
                    "options": ["neither","none","whatever"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bahs",
                    "RightAnswer": "debate",
                    "options": ["clock","post","exercise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xotira",
                    "RightAnswer": "memory",
                    "options": ["weekend","conclusion","newspaper"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yashil",
                    "RightAnswer": "green",
                    "options": ["fine","present","tall"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "song",
                    "options": ["memory","weekend","conclusion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "obyekt, narsa",
                    "RightAnswer": "object",
                    "options": ["debate","clock","post"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "maintain",
                    "options": ["perform","define","earn"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishonch",
                    "RightAnswer": "credit",
                    "options": ["object","debate","clock"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzuk, halqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "ring",
                    "options": ["credit","object","debate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kashf qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "discover",
                    "options": ["maintain","perform","define"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'lik",
                    "RightAnswer": "dead",
                    "options": ["professional","male","positive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushdan keyin",
                    "RightAnswer": "afternoon",
                    "options": ["song","memory","weekend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "afzal ko'rmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "prefer",
                    "options": ["discover","maintain","perform"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kengaytirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "extend",
                    "options": ["prefer","discover","maintain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imkoniyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "possibility",
                    "options": ["afternoon","song","memory"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'nalish",
                    "RightAnswer": "direction",
                    "options": ["possibility","afternoon","song"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imkoniyat, qulaylik",
                    "RightAnswer": "facility",
                    "options": ["direction","possibility","afternoon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "turli-tumanlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "variety",
                    "options": ["facility","direction","possibility"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "har kuni, kundalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "daily",
                    "options": ["fast","wrong","right"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kiyimlar",
                    "RightAnswer": "clothes",
                    "options": ["variety","facility","direction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ekran, to'siq",
                    "RightAnswer": "screen",
                    "options": ["ring","credit","object"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'l, trek",
                    "RightAnswer": "track",
                    "options": ["screen","ring","credit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqs",
                    "RightAnswer": "dance",
                    "options": ["track","screen","ring"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'liq, butunlay",
                    "RightAnswer": "completely",
                    "options": ["anyway","obviously","generally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ayol",
                    "RightAnswer": "female",
                    "options": ["dead","professional","male"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mas'uliyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "responsibility",
                    "options": ["clothes","variety","facility"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asl",
                    "RightAnswer": "original",
                    "options": ["female","dead","professional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "opa-singil",
                    "RightAnswer": "sister",
                    "options": ["responsibility","clothes","variety"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "rock",
                    "options": ["dance","track","screen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tush, orzu",
                    "RightAnswer": "dream",
                    "options": ["rock","dance","track"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "... ham emas",
                    "RightAnswer": "nor",
                    "options": ["although","whether","because"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "universitet",
                    "RightAnswer": "university",
                    "options": ["sister","responsibility","clothes"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "osonlikcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "easily",
                    "options": ["completely","anyway","obviously"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "agentlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "agency",
                    "options": ["university","sister","responsibility"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog'",
                    "RightAnswer": "garden",
                    "options": ["agency","university","sister"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuzatmoq, o'rnatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fix",
                    "options": ["reflect","guess","dress"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldinga",
                    "RightAnswer": "ahead",
                    "options": ["forward","far","still"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kesishmoq, xoch",
                    "RightAnswer": "cross",
                    "options": ["fit","moderate","mature"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nomzod",
                    "RightAnswer": "candidate",
                    "options": ["garden","agency","university"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vazn",
                    "RightAnswer": "weight",
                    "options": ["dream","rock","dance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuridik, qonuniy",
                    "RightAnswer": "legal",
                    "options": ["useful","basic","central"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif",
                    "RightAnswer": "proposal",
                    "options": ["candidate","garden","agency"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "versiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "version",
                    "options": ["proposal","candidate","garden"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suhbat",
                    "RightAnswer": "conversation",
                    "options": ["version","proposal","candidate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kimdir",
                    "RightAnswer": "somebody",
                    "options": ["everybody","yourself","anyone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "funt, qoqmoq ",
                    "RightAnswer": "pound",
                    "options": ["weight","dream","rock"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jurnal",
                    "RightAnswer": "magazine",
                    "options": ["conversation","version","proposal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shakl, forma",
                    "RightAnswer": "shape",
                    "options": ["pound","weight","dream"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dengiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "sea",
                    "options": ["magazine","conversation","version"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "darhol",
                    "RightAnswer": "immediately",
                    "options": ["easily","completely","anyway"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaxshi kutib olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "welcome",
                    "options": ["advance","space","subject"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tabassum",
                    "RightAnswer": "smile",
                    "options": ["shape","pound","weight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muloqot",
                    "RightAnswer": "communication",
                    "options": ["sea","magazine","conversation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "an'anaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "traditional",
                    "options": ["legal","useful","basic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "almashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "replace",
                    "options": ["extend","prefer","discover"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sudya, baholamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "judge",
                    "options": ["smile","shape","pound"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zi",
                    "RightAnswer": "herself",
                    "options": ["somebody","everybody","yourself"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birdaniga",
                    "RightAnswer": "suddenly",
                    "options": ["immediately","easily","completely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "avlod",
                    "RightAnswer": "generation",
                    "options": ["communication","sea","magazine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxmin qilmoq, baholamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "estimate",
                    "options": ["judge","smile","shape"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sevimli",
                    "RightAnswer": "favorite",
                    "options": ["original","female","dead"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiyinchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "difficulty",
                    "options": ["generation","communication","sea"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sotib olish",
                    "RightAnswer": "purchase",
                    "options": ["estimate","judge","smile"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "otmoq, suratga olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "shoot",
                    "options": ["fix","reflect","guess"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'lon qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "announce",
                    "options": ["replace","extend","prefer"]
                }
            ],
            "level 11": [
                {
                    "Question": "agar ... bo'lmasa",
                    "RightAnswer": "unless",
                    "options": ["nor","although","whether"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mustaqil",
                    "RightAnswer": "independent",
                    "options": ["traditional","legal","useful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tavsiya qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "recommend",
                    "options": ["announce","replace","extend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'rov, tekshiruv",
                    "RightAnswer": "survey",
                    "options": ["purchase","estimate","judge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'pchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "majority",
                    "options": ["difficulty","generation","communication"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayoq, ushlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stick",
                    "options": ["shoot","fix","reflect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'rov, talab",
                    "RightAnswer": "request",
                    "options": ["survey","purchase","estimate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boy",
                    "RightAnswer": "rich",
                    "options": ["independent","traditional","legal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shamol",
                    "RightAnswer": "wind",
                    "options": ["request","survey","purchase"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hech biri",
                    "RightAnswer": "none",
                    "options": ["whatever","self","ourselves"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "almashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exchange",
                    "options": ["wind","request","survey"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "byudjet",
                    "RightAnswer": "budget",
                    "options": ["exchange","wind","request"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mashhur",
                    "RightAnswer": "famous",
                    "options": ["rich","independent","traditional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qon",
                    "RightAnswer": "blood",
                    "options": ["majority","difficulty","generation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mos, tegishli",
                    "RightAnswer": "appropriate",
                    "options": ["separate","clean","direct"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "blok, to'siq",
                    "RightAnswer": "block",
                    "options": ["budget","exchange","wind"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "issiq, iliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "warm",
                    "options": ["thin","narrow","frequent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisoblamoq, sanamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "count",
                    "options": ["stick","shoot","fix"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sahna, manzara",
                    "RightAnswer": "scene",
                    "options": ["blood","majority","difficulty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yozuvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "writer",
                    "options": ["scene","blood","majority"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mazmun, tarkib",
                    "RightAnswer": "content",
                    "options": ["adult","baby","capital"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldini olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "prevent",
                    "options": ["recommend","announce","replace"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavfsiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "safe",
                    "options": ["favorite","original","female"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "invite",
                    "options": ["prevent","recommend","announce"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aralashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "mix",
                    "options": ["count","stick","shoot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "unsur",
                    "RightAnswer": "element",
                    "options": ["writer","scene","blood"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "samarali",
                    "RightAnswer": "effective",
                    "options": ["famous","rich","independent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'g'ri",
                    "RightAnswer": "correct",
                    "options": ["appropriate","separate","clean"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tibbiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "medical",
                    "options": ["effective","famous","rich"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qabul qilmoq, tan olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "admit",
                    "options": ["invite","prevent","recommend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "urmoq, g'alaba qozonmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "beat",
                    "options": ["mix","count","stick"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "telefon",
                    "RightAnswer": "telephone",
                    "options": ["block","budget","exchange"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nusxa, ko'chirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "copy",
                    "options": ["telephone","block","budget"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'mita",
                    "RightAnswer": "committee",
                    "options": ["element","writer","scene"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xabardor",
                    "RightAnswer": "aware",
                    "options": ["medical","effective","famous"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maslahat",
                    "RightAnswer": "advice",
                    "options": ["committee","element","writer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tutqich, boshqarmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "handle",
                    "options": ["beat","mix","count"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "stakan, shisha",
                    "RightAnswer": "glass",
                    "options": ["copy","telephone","block"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sud jarayoni, sinov",
                    "RightAnswer": "trial",
                    "options": ["content","adult","baby"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosim",
                    "RightAnswer": "stress",
                    "options": ["glass","copy","telephone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma'muriyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "administration",
                    "options": ["advice","committee","element"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "murakkab, kompleks",
                    "RightAnswer": "complex",
                    "options": ["safe","favorite","original"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "matn",
                    "RightAnswer": "text",
                    "options": ["stress","glass","copy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mazmun, ma'no",
                    "RightAnswer": "context",
                    "options": ["administration","advice","committee"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "minmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "ride",
                    "options": ["handle","beat","mix"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'g'ridan-to'g'ri",
                    "RightAnswer": "directly",
                    "options": ["suddenly","immediately","easily"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "og'ir",
                    "RightAnswer": "heavy",
                    "options": ["previous","hot","deep"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olib tashlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "remove",
                    "options": ["admit","invite","prevent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olib borish, xulq-atvor",
                    "RightAnswer": "conduct",
                    "options": ["ride","handle","beat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uskuna",
                    "RightAnswer": "equipment",
                    "options": ["context","administration","advice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aks holda",
                    "RightAnswer": "otherwise",
                    "options": ["yet","once","however"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sarlavha, lavozim",
                    "RightAnswer": "title",
                    "options": ["text","stress","glass"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shimcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "extra",
                    "options": ["complex","safe","favorite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ijrochi",
                    "RightAnswer": "executive",
                    "options": ["extra","complex","safe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "stul, rais",
                    "RightAnswer": "chair",
                    "options": ["title","text","stress"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qimmat",
                    "RightAnswer": "expensive",
                    "options": ["aware","medical","effective"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "namuna",
                    "RightAnswer": "sample",
                    "options": ["chair","title","text"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetkazib bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "deliver",
                    "options": ["remove","admit","invite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ulanish",
                    "RightAnswer": "connection",
                    "options": ["equipment","context","administration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birinchi, asosiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "primary",
                    "options": ["executive","extra","complex"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ob-havo",
                    "RightAnswer": "weather",
                    "options": ["sample","chair","title"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yig'moq",
                    "RightAnswer": "collect",
                    "options": ["deliver","remove","admit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xabardor qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "inform",
                    "options": ["collect","deliver","remove"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tamoyil",
                    "RightAnswer": "principle",
                    "options": ["connection","equipment","context"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'g'ri",
                    "RightAnswer": "straight",
                    "options": ["daily","fast","wrong"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "murojaat qilmoq, jozibadorlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "appeal",
                    "options": ["weather","sample","chair"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuqori darajada",
                    "RightAnswer": "highly",
                    "options": ["directly","suddenly","immediately"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishonch, ishonmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "trust",
                    "options": ["appeal","weather","sample"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajoyib",
                    "RightAnswer": "wonderful",
                    "options": ["expensive","aware","medical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tekis, kvartira",
                    "RightAnswer": "flat",
                    "options": ["distant","wise","eastern"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mutlaqo",
                    "RightAnswer": "absolutely",
                    "options": ["highly","directly","suddenly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oqim, oqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "flow",
                    "options": ["conduct","ride","handle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "adolatli, chiroyli",
                    "RightAnswer": "fair",
                    "options": ["rare","straight","daily"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shimcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "additional",
                    "options": ["wonderful","expensive","aware"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mas'ul",
                    "RightAnswer": "responsible",
                    "options": ["additional","wonderful","expensive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ferma",
                    "RightAnswer": "farm",
                    "options": ["trust","appeal","weather"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'plam",
                    "RightAnswer": "collection",
                    "options": ["principle","connection","equipment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "osmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hang",
                    "options": ["flow","conduct","ride"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "salbiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "negative",
                    "options": ["primary","executive","extra"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "guruh",
                    "RightAnswer": "band",
                    "options": ["farm","trust","appeal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarindosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "relative",
                    "options": ["negative","primary","executive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sayohat, ekskursiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "tour",
                    "options": ["band","farm","trust"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muqobil",
                    "RightAnswer": "alternative",
                    "options": ["relative","negative","primary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dasturiy ta'minot",
                    "RightAnswer": "software",
                    "options": ["collection","principle","connection"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "juft",
                    "RightAnswer": "pair",
                    "options": ["tour","band","farm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kema",
                    "RightAnswer": "ship",
                    "options": ["pair","tour","band"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "munosabat",
                    "RightAnswer": "attitude",
                    "options": ["software","collection","principle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "arzon",
                    "RightAnswer": "cheap",
                    "options": ["heavy","previous","hot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ikki barobar",
                    "RightAnswer": "double",
                    "options": ["warm","thin","narrow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oyoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "leg",
                    "options": ["attitude","software","collection"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuzatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "observe",
                    "options": ["inform","collect","deliver"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gap, jumla",
                    "RightAnswer": "sentence",
                    "options": ["ship","pair","tour"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chop etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "print",
                    "options": ["hang","flow","conduct"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taraqqiyot",
                    "RightAnswer": "progress",
                    "options": ["sentence","ship","pair"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqat",
                    "RightAnswer": "truth",
                    "options": ["leg","attitude","software"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hech kim",
                    "RightAnswer": "nobody",
                    "options": ["herself","somebody","everybody"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tekshirmoq, o'rganmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "examine",
                    "options": ["observe","inform","collect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yotmoq, qo'ymoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "lay",
                    "options": ["print","hang","flow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tezlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "speed",
                    "options": ["progress","sentence","ship"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "siyosat",
                    "RightAnswer": "politics",
                    "options": ["truth","leg","attitude"]
                }
            ],
            "level 12": [
                {
                    "Question": "javob bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reply",
                    "options": ["speed","progress","sentence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rsatmoq, ekran",
                    "RightAnswer": "display",
                    "options": ["reply","speed","progress"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'chirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "transfer",
                    "options": ["display","reply","speed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mukammal",
                    "RightAnswer": "perfect",
                    "options": ["correct","appropriate","separate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "biroz, ozgina",
                    "RightAnswer": "slightly",
                    "options": ["absolutely","highly","directly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "umumiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "overall",
                    "options": ["cheap","heavy","previous"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "niyat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "intend",
                    "options": ["examine","observe","inform"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foydalanuvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "user",
                    "options": ["politics","truth","leg"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "javob qaytarmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "respond",
                    "options": ["intend","examine","observe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kechki ovqat",
                    "RightAnswer": "dinner",
                    "options": ["user","politics","truth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sekin",
                    "RightAnswer": "slow",
                    "options": ["fresh","further","free"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muntazam, odatdagi",
                    "RightAnswer": "regular",
                    "options": ["alternative","relative","negative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jismoniy",
                    "RightAnswer": "physical",
                    "options": ["regular","alternative","relative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "alohida, ajratilgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "apart",
                    "options": ["ahead","forward","far"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kostyum, mos kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "suit",
                    "options": ["lay","print","hang"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "federativ",
                    "RightAnswer": "federal",
                    "options": ["responsible","additional","wonderful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oshkor qilmoq, ko'rsatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reveal",
                    "options": ["respond","intend","examine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "percentage",
                    "options": ["dinner","user","politics"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tinchlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "peace",
                    "options": ["percentage","dinner","user"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqom, holat",
                    "RightAnswer": "status",
                    "options": ["peace","percentage","dinner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jinoyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "crime",
                    "options": ["status","peace","percentage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamayish, inkor etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "decline",
                    "options": ["suit","lay","print"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'n yil",
                    "RightAnswer": "decade",
                    "options": ["crime","status","peace"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishga tushurmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "launch",
                    "options": ["decline","suit","lay"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ogohlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "warn",
                    "options": ["reveal","respond","intend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iste'molchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "consumer",
                    "options": ["trial","content","adult"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yordam, maqullamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "favor",
                    "options": ["transfer","display","reply"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "quruq",
                    "RightAnswer": "dry",
                    "options": ["double","warm","thin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sherik",
                    "RightAnswer": "partner",
                    "options": ["favor","transfer","display"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashkilot",
                    "RightAnswer": "institution",
                    "options": ["decade","crime","status"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joy, payqamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "spot",
                    "options": ["welcome","advance","space"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ot",
                    "RightAnswer": "horse",
                    "options": ["institution","decade","crime"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oxir-oqibat",
                    "RightAnswer": "eventually",
                    "options": ["slightly","absolutely","highly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "issiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "heat",
                    "options": ["partner","favor","transfer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayratlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "excite",
                    "options": ["warn","reveal","respond"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'quvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "reader",
                    "options": ["horse","institution","decade"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ahamiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "importance",
                    "options": ["reader","horse","institution"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "masofa",
                    "RightAnswer": "distance",
                    "options": ["heat","partner","favor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'llanma, yo'l-yo'riq",
                    "RightAnswer": "guide",
                    "options": ["launch","decline","suit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "grant",
                    "options": ["guide","launch","decline"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taksi",
                    "RightAnswer": "taxi",
                    "options": ["distance","heat","partner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boqmoq, ovqatlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "feed",
                    "options": ["grant","guide","launch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "og'riq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pain",
                    "options": ["importance","reader","horse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soha, bo'lim",
                    "RightAnswer": "sector",
                    "options": ["pain","importance","reader"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xato",
                    "RightAnswer": "mistake",
                    "options": ["taxi","distance","heat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'minlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "ensure",
                    "options": ["excite","warn","reveal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qoniqtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "satisfy",
                    "options": ["ensure","excite","warn"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosh, asosiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "chief",
                    "options": ["physical","regular","alternative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sovuq, salqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "cool",
                    "options": ["tender","pale","blind"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mutaxassis",
                    "RightAnswer": "expert",
                    "options": ["consumer","trial","content"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'lqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "wave",
                    "options": ["mistake","taxi","distance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "janub",
                    "RightAnswer": "south",
                    "options": ["dark","cold","middle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mehnat",
                    "RightAnswer": "labor",
                    "options": ["wave","mistake","taxi"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sirt, yuz",
                    "RightAnswer": "surface",
                    "options": ["labor","wave","mistake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kutubxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "library",
                    "options": ["sector","pain","importance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "a'lo, zo'r",
                    "RightAnswer": "excellent",
                    "options": ["federal","responsible","additional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qirra, chekka",
                    "RightAnswer": "edge",
                    "options": ["surface","labor","wave"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "lager",
                    "RightAnswer": "camp",
                    "options": ["edge","surface","labor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "auditoriya, tomoshabinlar",
                    "RightAnswer": "audience",
                    "options": ["library","sector","pain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "lift, ko'tarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "lift",
                    "options": ["feed","grant","guide"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tartib, jarayon",
                    "RightAnswer": "procedure",
                    "options": ["audience","library","sector"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "elektron pochta",
                    "RightAnswer": "email",
                    "options": ["camp","edge","surface"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "global, jahon",
                    "RightAnswer": "global",
                    "options": ["excellent","federal","responsible"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kurashmoq, qiyinchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "struggle",
                    "options": ["lift","feed","grant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "reklama qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "advertise",
                    "options": ["satisfy","ensure","excite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "select",
                    "options": ["cross","fit","moderate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rab olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "surround",
                    "options": ["struggle","lift","feed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "darajada, miqdor",
                    "RightAnswer": "extent",
                    "options": ["procedure","audience","library"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daryo",
                    "RightAnswer": "river",
                    "options": ["extent","procedure","audience"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yillik",
                    "RightAnswer": "annual",
                    "options": ["chief","physical","regular"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'liq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fully",
                    "options": ["eventually","slightly","absolutely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarama-qarshi, farq",
                    "RightAnswer": "contrast",
                    "options": ["email","camp","edge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aylanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "roll",
                    "options": ["surround","struggle","lift"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqat",
                    "RightAnswer": "reality",
                    "options": ["river","extent","procedure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rasm",
                    "RightAnswer": "photograph",
                    "options": ["contrast","email","camp"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rassom, san'atkor",
                    "RightAnswer": "artist",
                    "options": ["reality","river","extent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nizo, mojaro",
                    "RightAnswer": "conflict",
                    "options": ["photograph","contrast","email"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "butun, to'liq",
                    "RightAnswer": "entire",
                    "options": ["global","excellent","federal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavjudlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "presence",
                    "options": ["artist","reality","river"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olamon",
                    "RightAnswer": "crowd",
                    "options": ["conflict","photograph","contrast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "burchak",
                    "RightAnswer": "corner",
                    "options": ["crowd","conflict","photograph"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gaz",
                    "RightAnswer": "gas",
                    "options": ["presence","artist","reality"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'chmoq, smena",
                    "RightAnswer": "shift",
                    "options": ["roll","surround","struggle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'r, tarmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "net",
                    "options": ["quarter","stock","light"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "toifalar",
                    "RightAnswer": "category",
                    "options": ["gas","presence","artist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kotib",
                    "RightAnswer": "secretary",
                    "options": ["category","gas","presence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mudofaa",
                    "RightAnswer": "defense",
                    "options": ["secretary","category","gas"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tez",
                    "RightAnswer": "quick",
                    "options": ["overall","cheap","heavy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pishirmoq, oshpaz",
                    "RightAnswer": "cook",
                    "options": ["shift","roll","surround"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoymoq, tarqatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "spread",
                    "options": ["cook","shift","roll"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yadroviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "nuclear",
                    "options": ["entire","global","excellent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "masshtab, shkala",
                    "RightAnswer": "scale",
                    "options": ["corner","crowd","conflict"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haydovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "driver",
                    "options": ["defense","secretary","category"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'p",
                    "RightAnswer": "ball",
                    "options": ["scale","corner","crowd"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yig'lamoq, baqirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cry",
                    "options": ["spread","cook","shift"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kirish, tanishtirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "introduction",
                    "options": ["driver","defense","secretary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "talab",
                    "RightAnswer": "requirement",
                    "options": ["introduction","driver","defense"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shimol",
                    "RightAnswer": "north",
                    "options": ["south","dark","cold"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasdiqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "confirm",
                    "options": ["advertise","satisfy","ensure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "katta, oliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "senior",
                    "options": ["annual","chief","physical"]
                }
            ],
            "level 13": [
                {
                    "Question": "fotosurat",
                    "RightAnswer": "photo",
                    "options": ["requirement","introduction","driver"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rad etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "refuse",
                    "options": ["cry","spread","cook"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "transport, yetkazib berish",
                    "RightAnswer": "transport",
                    "options": ["refuse","cry","spread"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "paydo bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "emerge",
                    "options": ["confirm","advertise","satisfy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xarita",
                    "RightAnswer": "map",
                    "options": ["ball","scale","corner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushuncha",
                    "RightAnswer": "concept",
                    "options": ["photo","requirement","introduction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "orol",
                    "RightAnswer": "island",
                    "options": ["concept","photo","requirement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "islohot qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reform",
                    "options": ["map","ball","scale"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "na ... na ...",
                    "RightAnswer": "neither",
                    "options": ["none","whatever","self"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "futbol",
                    "RightAnswer": "football",
                    "options": ["island","concept","photo"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "omon qolmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "survive",
                    "options": ["emerge","confirm","advertise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "parvoz",
                    "RightAnswer": "flight",
                    "options": ["reform","map","ball"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chap",
                    "RightAnswer": "left",
                    "options": ["flat","distant","wise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yechim topmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "solve",
                    "options": ["survive","emerge","confirm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shni",
                    "RightAnswer": "neighbor",
                    "options": ["football","island","concept"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fon, orqa fon",
                    "RightAnswer": "background",
                    "options": ["neighbor","football","island"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "texnika, usul",
                    "RightAnswer": "technique",
                    "options": ["background","neighbor","football"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qatnov",
                    "RightAnswer": "traffic",
                    "options": ["flight","reform","map"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaxshilanish",
                    "RightAnswer": "improvement",
                    "options": ["technique","background","neighbor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asbob",
                    "RightAnswer": "tool",
                    "options": ["improvement","technique","background"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oqibat",
                    "RightAnswer": "consequence",
                    "options": ["tool","improvement","technique"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vaziyat, holat",
                    "RightAnswer": "circumstance",
                    "options": ["consequence","tool","improvement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tutun",
                    "RightAnswer": "smoke",
                    "options": ["traffic","flight","reform"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "reaksiya, javob",
                    "RightAnswer": "reaction",
                    "options": ["circumstance","consequence","tool"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yomg'ir",
                    "RightAnswer": "rain",
                    "options": ["smoke","traffic","flight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "band, mashg'ul",
                    "RightAnswer": "busy",
                    "options": ["quick","overall","cheap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dars",
                    "RightAnswer": "lesson",
                    "options": ["reaction","circumstance","consequence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "miya",
                    "RightAnswer": "brain",
                    "options": ["lesson","reaction","circumstance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "massa, katta miqdor",
                    "RightAnswer": "mass",
                    "options": ["net","quarter","stock"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kulgili, qiziqarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "funny",
                    "options": ["nuclear","entire","global"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hissa qo'shmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "contribute",
                    "options": ["solve","survive","emerge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muvaffaqiyatsizlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "failure",
                    "options": ["brain","lesson","reaction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jadval",
                    "RightAnswer": "schedule",
                    "options": ["rain","smoke","traffic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nutq so'zlovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "speaker",
                    "options": ["failure","brain","lesson"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pastki qism",
                    "RightAnswer": "bottom",
                    "options": ["compound","fat","stone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qabul qilmoq, o'zlashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "adopt",
                    "options": ["contribute","solve","survive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birlashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "combine",
                    "options": ["transport","refuse","cry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tog'",
                    "RightAnswer": "mountain",
                    "options": ["speaker","failure","brain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "isrof, qoldiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "waste",
                    "options": ["schedule","rain","smoke"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yashirmoq, yashirin joy",
                    "RightAnswer": "hide",
                    "options": ["combine","transport","refuse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nikoh, turmush",
                    "RightAnswer": "marriage",
                    "options": ["mountain","speaker","failure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chipta, viza",
                    "RightAnswer": "ticket",
                    "options": ["waste","schedule","rain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ovqat, taom",
                    "RightAnswer": "meal",
                    "options": ["marriage","mountain","speaker"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamkasb",
                    "RightAnswer": "colleague",
                    "options": ["meal","marriage","mountain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sumka, sumka",
                    "RightAnswer": "bag",
                    "options": ["ticket","waste","schedule"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "takrorlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "repeat",
                    "options": ["hide","combine","transport"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teng",
                    "RightAnswer": "equal",
                    "options": ["green","fine","present"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ifoda, bayonot",
                    "RightAnswer": "expression",
                    "options": ["colleague","meal","marriage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shimcha, plus",
                    "RightAnswer": "plus",
                    "options": ["versus","to","till"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nihoyatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "extremely",
                    "options": ["fully","eventually","slightly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "owner",
                    "options": ["expression","colleague","meal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "samolyot, tekislik",
                    "RightAnswer": "plane",
                    "options": ["bag","ticket","waste"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tijorat, reklama",
                    "RightAnswer": "commercial",
                    "options": ["senior","annual","chief"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ayol, xonim",
                    "RightAnswer": "lady",
                    "options": ["owner","expression","colleague"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vazifa, majburiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "duty",
                    "options": ["lady","owner","expression"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuch, mustahkamlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "strength",
                    "options": ["duty","lady","owner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog'lamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "connect",
                    "options": ["adopt","contribute","solve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "madaniy",
                    "RightAnswer": "cultural",
                    "options": ["funny","nuclear","entire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tartibga solmoq, tashkil qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "arrange",
                    "options": ["connect","adopt","contribute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sxema, reja",
                    "RightAnswer": "scheme",
                    "options": ["plane","bag","ticket"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'lov",
                    "RightAnswer": "payment",
                    "options": ["strength","duty","lady"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "afsuski",
                    "RightAnswer": "unfortunately",
                    "options": ["extremely","fully","eventually"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qisqa, qisqacha",
                    "RightAnswer": "brief",
                    "options": ["equal","green","fine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qush",
                    "RightAnswer": "bird",
                    "options": ["payment","strength","duty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "namoyish qilmoq, ko'rsatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "demonstrate",
                    "options": ["arrange","connect","adopt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hissa",
                    "RightAnswer": "contribution",
                    "options": ["bird","payment","strength"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qadrlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "appreciate",
                    "options": ["demonstrate","arrange","connect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bob",
                    "RightAnswer": "chapter",
                    "options": ["contribution","bird","payment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sir, maxfiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "secret",
                    "options": ["commercial","senior","annual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rinib turibdi",
                    "RightAnswer": "apparently",
                    "options": ["unfortunately","extremely","fully"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "roman, yangicha",
                    "RightAnswer": "novel",
                    "options": ["secret","commercial","senior"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ittifoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "union",
                    "options": ["scheme","plane","bag"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yonmoq, kuymoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "burn",
                    "options": ["repeat","hide","combine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tendensiya, yo'nalish",
                    "RightAnswer": "trend",
                    "options": ["chapter","contribution","bird"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dastlabki, boshlang'ich",
                    "RightAnswer": "initial",
                    "options": ["novel","secret","commercial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zavq, mamnuniyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "pleasure",
                    "options": ["trend","chapter","contribution"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif",
                    "RightAnswer": "suggestion",
                    "options": ["pleasure","trend","chapter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanqidiy, muhim",
                    "RightAnswer": "critical",
                    "options": ["initial","novel","secret"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yig'ilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "gather",
                    "options": ["burn","repeat","hide"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosan",
                    "RightAnswer": "mostly",
                    "options": ["apparently","unfortunately","extremely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "Yer, yer yuzasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "earth",
                    "options": ["suggestion","pleasure","trend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yorilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pop",
                    "options": ["gather","burn","repeat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhim, zarur",
                    "RightAnswer": "essential",
                    "options": ["cultural","funny","nuclear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "istak, xohish",
                    "RightAnswer": "desire",
                    "options": ["union","scheme","plane"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "targ'ib qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "promote",
                    "options": ["appreciate","demonstrate","arrange"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hozirgi vaqtda",
                    "RightAnswer": "currently",
                    "options": ["mostly","apparently","unfortunately"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishga olmoq,",
                    "RightAnswer": "employ",
                    "options": ["promote","appreciate","demonstrate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "path",
                    "options": ["earth","suggestion","pleasure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavzu",
                    "RightAnswer": "topic",
                    "options": ["path","earth","suggestion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "plyaj, sohil",
                    "RightAnswer": "beach",
                    "options": ["desire","union","scheme"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jalb qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "attract",
                    "options": ["employ","promote","appreciate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jalb qilmoq, band qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "engage",
                    "options": ["attract","employ","promote"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuchli, qudratli",
                    "RightAnswer": "powerful",
                    "options": ["essential","cultural","funny"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gul",
                    "RightAnswer": "flower",
                    "options": ["beach","desire","union"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "inqiroz",
                    "RightAnswer": "crisis",
                    "options": ["topic","path","earth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rnashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "settle",
                    "options": ["engage","attract","employ"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qayiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "boat",
                    "options": ["flower","beach","desire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yordam",
                    "RightAnswer": "aid",
                    "options": ["boat","flower","beach"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muxlis, ventilyator",
                    "RightAnswer": "fan",
                    "options": ["aid","boat","flower"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oshxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "kitchen",
                    "options": ["crisis","topic","path"]
                }
            ],
            "level 14": [
                {
                    "Question": "ikki marta",
                    "RightAnswer": "twice",
                    "options": ["currently","mostly","apparently"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yangi, toza",
                    "RightAnswer": "fresh",
                    "options": ["further","free","rough"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kechiktirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "delay",
                    "options": ["pop","gather","burn"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavfsizlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "safety",
                    "options": ["kitchen","crisis","topic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhandis",
                    "RightAnswer": "engineer",
                    "options": ["fan","aid","boat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jimjit, sokin",
                    "RightAnswer": "quiet",
                    "options": ["slow","fresh","further"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sug'urta",
                    "RightAnswer": "insurance",
                    "options": ["safety","kitchen","crisis"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamshira",
                    "RightAnswer": "nurse",
                    "options": ["engineer","fan","aid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'lib tashlamoq, ajratmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "divide",
                    "options": ["delay","pop","gather"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzunlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "length",
                    "options": ["insurance","safety","kitchen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tergov, tadqiqot",
                    "RightAnswer": "investigation",
                    "options": ["length","insurance","safety"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "paket, jo'natma",
                    "RightAnswer": "package",
                    "options": ["nurse","engineer","fan"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "biror joyda",
                    "RightAnswer": "somewhere",
                    "options": ["twice","currently","mostly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kengaytirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "expand",
                    "options": ["settle","engage","attract"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sodir qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "commit",
                    "options": ["expand","settle","engage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq, ravshan",
                    "RightAnswer": "obvious",
                    "options": ["powerful","essential","cultural"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sakramoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "jump",
                    "options": ["divide","delay","pop"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurol",
                    "RightAnswer": "weapon",
                    "options": ["investigation","length","insurance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nisbatan",
                    "RightAnswer": "relatively",
                    "options": ["somewhere","twice","currently"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mezbon",
                    "RightAnswer": "host",
                    "options": ["jump","divide","delay"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qish",
                    "RightAnswer": "winter",
                    "options": ["weapon","investigation","length"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuman, mahalla",
                    "RightAnswer": "district",
                    "options": ["winter","weapon","investigation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keng",
                    "RightAnswer": "broad",
                    "options": ["busy","quick","overall"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shina",
                    "RightAnswer": "tire",
                    "options": ["host","jump","divide"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bahor",
                    "RightAnswer": "spring",
                    "options": ["spot","welcome","advance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ruh, kayfiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "spirit",
                    "options": ["district","winter","weapon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "lunch",
                    "options": ["package","nurse","engineer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqiy, asl",
                    "RightAnswer": "actual",
                    "options": ["obvious","powerful","essential"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hovuz",
                    "RightAnswer": "pool",
                    "options": ["lunch","package","nurse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jang",
                    "RightAnswer": "battle",
                    "options": ["pool","lunch","package"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "an'ana",
                    "RightAnswer": "tradition",
                    "options": ["spirit","district","winter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "naqd pul",
                    "RightAnswer": "cash",
                    "options": ["battle","pool","lunch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "deyarli emas, qiyin",
                    "RightAnswer": "hardly",
                    "options": ["relatively","somewhere","twice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mukofot",
                    "RightAnswer": "award",
                    "options": ["cash","battle","pool"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "murabbiy, avtobus",
                    "RightAnswer": "coach",
                    "options": ["award","cash","battle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sinov, tajriba",
                    "RightAnswer": "experiment",
                    "options": ["coach","award","cash"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisobga olish, e'tibor",
                    "RightAnswer": "consideration",
                    "options": ["tradition","spirit","district"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'alati, noodatiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "strange",
                    "options": ["actual","obvious","powerful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kod, kodlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "code",
                    "options": ["experiment","coach","award"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mumkin, ehtimol",
                    "RightAnswer": "possibly",
                    "options": ["hardly","relatively","somewhere"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tahdid",
                    "RightAnswer": "threat",
                    "options": ["consideration","tradition","spirit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "avariya, hodisa",
                    "RightAnswer": "accident",
                    "options": ["threat","consideration","tradition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imkonsiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "impossible",
                    "options": ["strange","actual","obvious"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daromad",
                    "RightAnswer": "revenue",
                    "options": ["accident","threat","consideration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imkon yaratmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "enable",
                    "options": ["commit","expand","settle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'rqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "afraid",
                    "options": ["impossible","strange","actual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faol",
                    "RightAnswer": "active",
                    "options": ["afraid","impossible","strange"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xulosa qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "conclude",
                    "options": ["enable","commit","expand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "diniy",
                    "RightAnswer": "religious",
                    "options": ["active","afraid","impossible"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saraton",
                    "RightAnswer": "cancer",
                    "options": ["revenue","accident","threat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishontirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "convince",
                    "options": ["conclude","enable","commit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "farqlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "vary",
                    "options": ["convince","conclude","enable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "atrof-muhitga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "environmental",
                    "options": ["religious","active","afraid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "quyosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "sun",
                    "options": ["code","experiment","coach"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sog'lom",
                    "RightAnswer": "healthy",
                    "options": ["environmental","religious","active"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "esmoq, puflamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "blow",
                    "options": ["tire","host","jump"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hajm, ovoz",
                    "RightAnswer": "volume",
                    "options": ["sun","code","experiment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joylashuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "location",
                    "options": ["cancer","revenue","accident"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sarmoya kiritmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "invest",
                    "options": ["vary","convince","conclude"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davom etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "proceed",
                    "options": ["invest","vary","convince"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuvmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wash",
                    "options": ["blow","tire","host"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aktyor",
                    "RightAnswer": "actor",
                    "options": ["location","cancer","revenue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xursand",
                    "RightAnswer": "glad",
                    "options": ["healthy","environmental","religious"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "lenta, magnit lenta",
                    "RightAnswer": "tape",
                    "options": ["volume","sun","code"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'lsa-da",
                    "RightAnswer": "whereas",
                    "options": ["unless","nor","although"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarama-qarshi",
                    "RightAnswer": "opposite",
                    "options": ["left","flat","distant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "stone",
                    "options": ["mass","net","quarter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yig'indisi, summa",
                    "RightAnswer": "sum",
                    "options": ["tape","volume","sun"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qotillik",
                    "RightAnswer": "murder",
                    "options": ["sum","tape","volume"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nazorat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "monitor",
                    "options": ["wash","blow","tire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "askar",
                    "RightAnswer": "soldier",
                    "options": ["actor","location","cancer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moliya",
                    "RightAnswer": "finance",
                    "options": ["murder","sum","tape"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nafrat",
                    "RightAnswer": "hate",
                    "options": ["monitor","wash","blow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuxum",
                    "RightAnswer": "egg",
                    "options": ["soldier","actor","location"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "konsert",
                    "RightAnswer": "concert",
                    "options": ["finance","murder","sum"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tebranish, hayrat",
                    "RightAnswer": "shock",
                    "options": ["concert","finance","murder"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qulay",
                    "RightAnswer": "comfortable",
                    "options": ["glad","healthy","environmental"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odatiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "usual",
                    "options": ["critical","initial","novel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtiyotkorlik bilan",
                    "RightAnswer": "carefully",
                    "options": ["possibly","hardly","relatively"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sumka, paketlash",
                    "RightAnswer": "pack",
                    "options": ["hate","monitor","wash"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eslamoq, chaqirib olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "recall",
                    "options": ["pack","hate","monitor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sharob",
                    "RightAnswer": "wine",
                    "options": ["shock","concert","finance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamera",
                    "RightAnswer": "camera",
                    "options": ["egg","soldier","actor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suzmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "swim",
                    "options": ["recall","pack","hate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishlab chiqarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "manufacture",
                    "options": ["swim","recall","pack"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teatr",
                    "RightAnswer": "theater",
                    "options": ["camera","egg","soldier"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aylana, velosiped",
                    "RightAnswer": "cycle",
                    "options": ["wine","shock","concert"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kofe",
                    "RightAnswer": "coffee",
                    "options": ["theater","camera","egg"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "butunlay",
                    "RightAnswer": "totally",
                    "options": ["carefully","possibly","hardly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muzey",
                    "RightAnswer": "museum",
                    "options": ["coffee","theater","camera"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mehmon",
                    "RightAnswer": "visitor",
                    "options": ["museum","coffee","theater"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "erkinlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "freedom",
                    "options": ["visitor","museum","coffee"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurilish",
                    "RightAnswer": "construction",
                    "options": ["freedom","visitor","museum"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aziz",
                    "RightAnswer": "dear",
                    "options": ["usual","critical","initial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqsad, obyektiv",
                    "RightAnswer": "objective",
                    "options": ["brief","equal","green"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bundan tashqari",
                    "RightAnswer": "moreover",
                    "options": ["totally","carefully","possibly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ustiga",
                    "RightAnswer": "onto",
                    "options": ["despite","upon","toward"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarixiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "historical",
                    "options": ["comfortable","glad","healthy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarshi chiqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "oppose",
                    "options": ["proceed","invest","vary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarmoq, filial",
                    "RightAnswer": "branch",
                    "options": ["cycle","wine","shock"]
                }
            ],
            "level 15": [
                {
                    "Question": "transport vositasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "vehicle",
                    "options": ["construction","freedom","visitor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olim",
                    "RightAnswer": "scientist",
                    "options": ["vehicle","construction","freedom"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "marshrut, yo'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "route",
                    "options": ["branch","cycle","wine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog'lamoq, o'ramoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bind",
                    "options": ["manufacture","swim","recall"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tegishli bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "belong",
                    "options": ["oppose","proceed","invest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'm, tatib ko'rmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "taste",
                    "options": ["bind","manufacture","swim"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bugun kechasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "tonight",
                    "options": ["tomorrow","yesterday","today"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moda",
                    "RightAnswer": "fashion",
                    "options": ["spring","spot","welcome"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavf",
                    "RightAnswer": "danger",
                    "options": ["scientist","vehicle","construction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bomba",
                    "RightAnswer": "bomb",
                    "options": ["route","branch","cycle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harbiy kuchlar",
                    "RightAnswer": "army",
                    "options": ["danger","scientist","vehicle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavfli",
                    "RightAnswer": "dangerous",
                    "options": ["historical","comfortable","glad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamaymoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "decrease",
                    "options": ["taste","bind","manufacture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jarohat yetkazmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hurt",
                    "options": ["grin","cough","fade"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kengash",
                    "RightAnswer": "council",
                    "options": ["army","danger","scientist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tahrirchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "editor",
                    "options": ["council","army","danger"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "normally",
                    "options": ["moreover","totally","carefully"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rish, manzara",
                    "RightAnswer": "sight",
                    "options": ["bomb","route","branch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaratmoq, hosil qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "generate",
                    "options": ["belong","oppose","proceed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sovg'a",
                    "RightAnswer": "gift",
                    "options": ["sight","bomb","route"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetkazib berish",
                    "RightAnswer": "delivery",
                    "options": ["editor","council","army"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "inkor qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "deny",
                    "options": ["generate","belong","oppose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mehmon",
                    "RightAnswer": "guest",
                    "options": ["delivery","editor","council"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "biror kim",
                    "RightAnswer": "anybody",
                    "options": ["nobody","herself","somebody"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yotoqxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "bedroom",
                    "options": ["guest","delivery","editor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iqtibos",
                    "RightAnswer": "quote",
                    "options": ["decrease","taste","bind"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "climb",
                    "options": ["quote","decrease","taste"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosan",
                    "RightAnswer": "basically",
                    "options": ["normally","moreover","totally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zo'ravonlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "violence",
                    "options": ["bedroom","guest","delivery"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vazir",
                    "RightAnswer": "minister",
                    "options": ["violence","bedroom","guest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosan",
                    "RightAnswer": "mainly",
                    "options": ["basically","normally","moreover"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "og'iz",
                    "RightAnswer": "mouth",
                    "options": ["minister","violence","bedroom"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shovqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "noise",
                    "options": ["mouth","minister","violence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xulq-atvor",
                    "RightAnswer": "manner",
                    "options": ["noise","mouth","minister"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurol",
                    "RightAnswer": "gun",
                    "options": ["manner","noise","mouth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kvadrat, maydon",
                    "RightAnswer": "square",
                    "options": ["objective","brief","equal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hodisa, bayram",
                    "RightAnswer": "occasion",
                    "options": ["gun","manner","noise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanish, xushmuomala",
                    "RightAnswer": "familiar",
                    "options": ["dear","usual","critical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "ignore",
                    "options": ["deny","generate","belong"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vayron qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "destroy",
                    "options": ["ignore","deny","generate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ish, masala",
                    "RightAnswer": "affair",
                    "options": ["occasion","gun","manner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fuqarolik",
                    "RightAnswer": "civil",
                    "options": ["familiar","dear","usual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "topmoq, joylashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "locate",
                    "options": ["destroy","ignore","deny"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fuqaro",
                    "RightAnswer": "citizen",
                    "options": ["affair","occasion","gun"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harorat",
                    "RightAnswer": "temperature",
                    "options": ["citizen","affair","occasion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oltin",
                    "RightAnswer": "gold",
                    "options": ["expert","consumer","trial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ichki, uyga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "domestic",
                    "options": ["civil","familiar","dear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuk, yuklash",
                    "RightAnswer": "load",
                    "options": ["gift","sight","bomb"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'tiqod",
                    "RightAnswer": "belief",
                    "options": ["temperature","citizen","affair"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "askarlar",
                    "RightAnswer": "troops",
                    "options": ["belief","temperature","citizen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "texnik",
                    "RightAnswer": "technical",
                    "options": ["dangerous","historical","comfortable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "eslatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "remind",
                    "options": ["locate","destroy","ignore"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tartib, kelishuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "arrangement",
                    "options": ["troops","belief","temperature"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teri",
                    "RightAnswer": "skin",
                    "options": ["load","gift","sight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qamoqxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "prison",
                    "options": ["arrangement","troops","belief"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "almashtirmoq, o'zgartirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "switch",
                    "options": ["climb","quote","decrease"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egallamoq, olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "acquire",
                    "options": ["remind","locate","destroy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "korporativ",
                    "RightAnswer": "corporate",
                    "options": ["technical","dangerous","historical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "adolatli, munosib",
                    "RightAnswer": "fairly",
                    "options": ["mainly","basically","normally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yog'och",
                    "RightAnswer": "wood",
                    "options": ["prison","arrangement","troops"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qatnashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "participate",
                    "options": ["acquire","remind","locate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiyin, mustahkam",
                    "RightAnswer": "tough",
                    "options": ["broad","busy","quick"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yirtmoq, ko'z yoshi ",
                    "RightAnswer": "tear",
                    "options": ["switch","climb","quote"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vakil",
                    "RightAnswer": "representative",
                    "options": ["gold","expert","consumer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sig'im, qobiliyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "capacity",
                    "options": ["wood","prison","arrangement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chegara",
                    "RightAnswer": "border",
                    "options": ["skin","load","gift"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "silkitmoq, titratmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "shake",
                    "options": ["tear","switch","climb"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baholash, tahlil",
                    "RightAnswer": "assessment",
                    "options": ["capacity","wood","prison"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "poyabzal",
                    "RightAnswer": "shoe",
                    "options": ["assessment","capacity","wood"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kerak, lozim",
                    "RightAnswer": "ought",
                    "options": ["must","might","may"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "reklama a_) : ad,",
                    "RightAnswer": "ad",
                    "options": ["shoe","assessment","capacity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'lov, haq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fee",
                    "options": ["ad","shoe","assessment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zal",
                    "RightAnswer": "hall",
                    "options": ["fee","ad","shoe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tartib-qoidalar",
                    "RightAnswer": "regulation",
                    "options": ["hall","fee","ad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qochmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "escape",
                    "options": ["shake","tear","switch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "studiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "studio",
                    "options": ["regulation","hall","fee"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'g'ri, mos",
                    "RightAnswer": "proper",
                    "options": ["tough","broad","busy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dam olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "relax",
                    "options": ["participate","acquire","remind"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sayyoh",
                    "RightAnswer": "tourist",
                    "options": ["studio","regulation","hall"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "komponent, qism",
                    "RightAnswer": "component",
                    "options": ["tourist","studio","regulation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurbi yetmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "afford",
                    "options": ["relax","participate","acquire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "advokat",
                    "RightAnswer": "lawyer",
                    "options": ["component","tourist","studio"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shubha qilmoq, gumondor",
                    "RightAnswer": "suspect",
                    "options": ["select","cross","fit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "stakan, kubok",
                    "RightAnswer": "cup",
                    "options": ["border","skin","load"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'rif",
                    "RightAnswer": "description",
                    "options": ["lawyer","component","tourist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishonch",
                    "RightAnswer": "confidence",
                    "options": ["description","lawyer","component"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sanoatga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "industrial",
                    "options": ["corporate","technical","dangerous"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shikoyat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "complain",
                    "options": ["afford","relax","participate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nuqtai nazar",
                    "RightAnswer": "perspective",
                    "options": ["confidence","description","lawyer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xato",
                    "RightAnswer": "error",
                    "options": ["perspective","confidence","description"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xibsga olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "arrest",
                    "options": ["escape","shake","tear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baholamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "assess",
                    "options": ["complain","afford","relax"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ro'yxatdan o'tmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "register",
                    "options": ["arrest","escape","shake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foyda keltiruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "asset",
                    "options": ["error","perspective","confidence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "belgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "signal",
                    "options": ["cup","border","skin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "barmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "finger",
                    "options": ["signal","cup","border"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tegishli, aloqador",
                    "RightAnswer": "relevant",
                    "options": ["industrial","corporate","technical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rganmoq, tadqiq qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "explore",
                    "options": ["assess","complain","afford"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetakchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "leadership",
                    "options": ["asset","error","perspective"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sodiqlik, mas'uliyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "commitment",
                    "options": ["leadership","asset","error"]
                }
            ],
            "level 16": [
                {
                    "Question": "uyg'onmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wake",
                    "options": ["finger","signal","cup"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "talab etiladi, zarur",
                    "RightAnswer": "necessarily",
                    "options": ["fairly","mainly","basically"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yorqin, porloq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bright",
                    "options": ["proper","tough","broad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ramka",
                    "RightAnswer": "frame",
                    "options": ["wake","finger","signal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sekin-asta",
                    "RightAnswer": "slowly",
                    "options": ["necessarily","fairly","mainly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog'lanish, aloqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "bond",
                    "options": ["frame","wake","finger"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishga olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hire",
                    "options": ["register","arrest","escape"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teshik, bo'shliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hole",
                    "options": ["commitment","leadership","asset"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog'lamoq, galstuk",
                    "RightAnswer": "tie",
                    "options": ["bond","frame","wake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ichki",
                    "RightAnswer": "internal",
                    "options": ["relevant","industrial","corporate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zanjir",
                    "RightAnswer": "chain",
                    "options": ["tie","bond","frame"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "adabiyot",
                    "RightAnswer": "literature",
                    "options": ["hole","commitment","leadership"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurbon",
                    "RightAnswer": "victim",
                    "options": ["literature","hole","commitment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tahdid qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "threaten",
                    "options": ["explore","assess","complain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'linma, bo'lim",
                    "RightAnswer": "division",
                    "options": ["victim","literature","hole"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xavfsiz, mustahkam",
                    "RightAnswer": "secure",
                    "options": ["perfect","correct","appropriate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayratlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "amaze",
                    "options": ["threaten","explore","assess"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurilma, asbob",
                    "RightAnswer": "device",
                    "options": ["division","victim","literature"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tug'ilish",
                    "RightAnswer": "birth",
                    "options": ["device","division","victim"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rmon",
                    "RightAnswer": "forest",
                    "options": ["birth","device","division"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yorliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "label",
                    "options": ["chain","tie","bond"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ildiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "root",
                    "options": ["label","chain","tie"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zavod",
                    "RightAnswer": "factory",
                    "options": ["forest","birth","device"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xarajat",
                    "RightAnswer": "expense",
                    "options": ["root","label","chain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kanal",
                    "RightAnswer": "channel",
                    "options": ["expense","root","label"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tergov qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "investigate",
                    "options": ["amaze","threaten","explore"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tavsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "recommendation",
                    "options": ["factory","forest","birth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pog'ona, daraja",
                    "RightAnswer": "rank",
                    "options": ["channel","expense","root"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tipik, odatiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "typical",
                    "options": ["internal","relevant","industrial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'arb",
                    "RightAnswer": "west",
                    "options": ["leather","stranger","liquid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "do'stona",
                    "RightAnswer": "friendly",
                    "options": ["typical","internal","relevant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "turuvchi, aholi",
                    "RightAnswer": "resident",
                    "options": ["representative","gold","expert"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'minot",
                    "RightAnswer": "provision",
                    "options": ["recommendation","factory","forest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "diqqatni qaratmoq, yig'moq",
                    "RightAnswer": "concentrate",
                    "options": ["hire","register","arrest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'p",
                    "RightAnswer": "plenty",
                    "options": ["west","leather","stranger"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chetga sotmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "export",
                    "options": ["rank","channel","expense"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "butunlay",
                    "RightAnswer": "entirely",
                    "options": ["slowly","necessarily","fairly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuchli tarzda",
                    "RightAnswer": "strongly",
                    "options": ["entirely","slowly","necessarily"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'prik",
                    "RightAnswer": "bridge",
                    "options": ["export","rank","channel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iborat bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "consist",
                    "options": ["investigate","amaze","threaten"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bitiruvchi, bitirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "graduate",
                    "options": ["concentrate","hire","register"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "brend",
                    "RightAnswer": "brand",
                    "options": ["bridge","export","rank"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "axloqiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "moral",
                    "options": ["domestic","civil","familiar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qat'iyat bilan talab qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "insist",
                    "options": ["consist","investigate","amaze"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kombinatsiya, aralashma",
                    "RightAnswer": "combination",
                    "options": ["provision","recommendation","factory"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suiiste'mol, zo'ravonlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "abuse",
                    "options": ["brand","bridge","export"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muz",
                    "RightAnswer": "ice",
                    "options": ["abuse","brand","bridge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosiy, direktor",
                    "RightAnswer": "principal",
                    "options": ["moral","domestic","civil"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ustoz, boshliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "master",
                    "options": ["fashion","spring","spot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq, albatta",
                    "RightAnswer": "definitely",
                    "options": ["strongly","entirely","slowly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sessiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "session",
                    "options": ["combination","provision","recommendation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daraja, sinf",
                    "RightAnswer": "grade",
                    "options": ["ice","abuse","brand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shunga qaramay",
                    "RightAnswer": "nevertheless",
                    "options": ["therefore","though","whereas"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bashorat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "predict",
                    "options": ["insist","consist","investigate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldin, ilgari",
                    "RightAnswer": "previously",
                    "options": ["definitely","strongly","entirely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "himoya",
                    "RightAnswer": "protection",
                    "options": ["session","combination","provision"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosan",
                    "RightAnswer": "largely",
                    "options": ["previously","definitely","strongly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uylanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wed",
                    "options": ["predict","insist","consist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ijaraga olmoq, ijara",
                    "RightAnswer": "rent",
                    "options": ["grade","ice","abuse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zarba, otish",
                    "RightAnswer": "shot",
                    "options": ["rent","grade","ice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rinish",
                    "RightAnswer": "appearance",
                    "options": ["protection","session","combination"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mantiqan to'g'ri, oqilona",
                    "RightAnswer": "reasonable",
                    "options": ["friendly","typical","internal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kafolat",
                    "RightAnswer": "guarantee",
                    "options": ["shot","rent","grade"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gacha",
                    "RightAnswer": "till",
                    "options": ["except","until","since"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavzu, tema",
                    "RightAnswer": "theme",
                    "options": ["appearance","protection","session"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hukm, baholash",
                    "RightAnswer": "judgment",
                    "options": ["theme","appearance","protection"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'alati",
                    "RightAnswer": "odd",
                    "options": ["north","south","dark"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasdiqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "approve",
                    "options": ["wed","predict","insist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kredit, qarz",
                    "RightAnswer": "loan",
                    "options": ["guarantee","shot","rent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'rif",
                    "RightAnswer": "definition",
                    "options": ["judgment","theme","appearance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saylamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "elect",
                    "options": ["express","close","mean"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "atmosfera, havo",
                    "RightAnswer": "atmosphere",
                    "options": ["definition","judgment","theme"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dehqon",
                    "RightAnswer": "farmer",
                    "options": ["atmosphere","definition","judgment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqqoslash",
                    "RightAnswer": "comparison",
                    "options": ["farmer","atmosphere","definition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xususiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "characteristic",
                    "options": ["principal","moral","domestic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "litsenziya, ruxsatnoma",
                    "RightAnswer": "license",
                    "options": ["loan","guarantee","shot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayanmoq, ishonmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rely",
                    "options": ["approve","wed","predict"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tor",
                    "RightAnswer": "narrow",
                    "options": ["frequent","keen","exact"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muvaffaqiyat qozonmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "succeed",
                    "options": ["rely","approve","wed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shaxsi",
                    "RightAnswer": "identity",
                    "options": ["comparison","farmer","atmosphere"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ish stoli",
                    "RightAnswer": "desk",
                    "options": ["identity","comparison","farmer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ruxsat, lisenziya",
                    "RightAnswer": "permit",
                    "options": ["graduate","concentrate","hire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jiddiylik bilan",
                    "RightAnswer": "seriously",
                    "options": ["largely","previously","definitely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yovvoyi",
                    "RightAnswer": "wild",
                    "options": ["quiet","slow","fresh"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'sh",
                    "RightAnswer": "empty",
                    "options": ["dry","double","warm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'mita, komissiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "commission",
                    "options": ["license","loan","guarantee"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'ziga xos, yagona",
                    "RightAnswer": "unique",
                    "options": ["reasonable","friendly","typical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "assotsiatsiya, uyushma",
                    "RightAnswer": "association",
                    "options": ["desk","identity","comparison"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asbob, jihoz",
                    "RightAnswer": "instrument",
                    "options": ["association","desk","identity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sarmoyador",
                    "RightAnswer": "investor",
                    "options": ["instrument","association","desk"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "amaliy, foydali",
                    "RightAnswer": "practical",
                    "options": ["characteristic","principal","moral"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "choy",
                    "RightAnswer": "tea",
                    "options": ["investor","instrument","association"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiroyli, yoqimli",
                    "RightAnswer": "lovely",
                    "options": ["bright","proper","tough"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yumshoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "soft",
                    "options": ["fair","rare","straight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qator, chiziq",
                    "RightAnswer": "row",
                    "options": ["commission","license","loan"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoshlar, yoshlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "youth",
                    "options": ["tea","investor","instrument"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qulf",
                    "RightAnswer": "lock",
                    "options": ["row","commission","license"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoqilg'i",
                    "RightAnswer": "fuel",
                    "options": ["lock","row","commission"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kutish, umid",
                    "RightAnswer": "expectation",
                    "options": ["youth","tea","investor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ish bilan ta'minlash, bandlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "employment",
                    "options": ["expectation","youth","tea"]
                }
            ],
            "level 17": [
                {
                    "Question": "bayram qilmoq, nishonlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "celebrate",
                    "options": ["succeed","rely","approve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yelka",
                    "RightAnswer": "shoulder",
                    "options": ["fuel","lock","row"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nafas",
                    "RightAnswer": "breath",
                    "options": ["employment","expectation","youth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tobora ko'proq",
                    "RightAnswer": "increasingly",
                    "options": ["seriously","largely","previously"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chetdan sotib olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "import",
                    "options": ["shoulder","fuel","lock"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shisha idish",
                    "RightAnswer": "bottle",
                    "options": ["import","shoulder","fuel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zimiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "ourselves",
                    "options": ["anybody","nobody","herself"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "varoq, choyshab",
                    "RightAnswer": "sheet",
                    "options": ["bottle","import","shoulder"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dvigatel, motor",
                    "RightAnswer": "engine",
                    "options": ["breath","employment","expectation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uloqtirmoq, otmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cast",
                    "options": ["permit","graduate","concentrate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'oya, tushuncha",
                    "RightAnswer": "notion",
                    "options": ["engine","breath","employment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "konservativ, an'anaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "conservative",
                    "options": ["unique","reasonable","friendly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sayohat, safar",
                    "RightAnswer": "journey",
                    "options": ["sheet","bottle","import"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarshilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "opposition",
                    "options": ["notion","engine","breath"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yengillik",
                    "RightAnswer": "relief",
                    "options": ["opposition","notion","engine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarz",
                    "RightAnswer": "debt",
                    "options": ["relief","opposition","notion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sharaf, hurmat",
                    "RightAnswer": "honor",
                    "options": ["journey","sheet","bottle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "natija",
                    "RightAnswer": "outcome",
                    "options": ["debt","relief","opposition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ayblamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "blame",
                    "options": ["honor","journey","sheet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushuntirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "explanation",
                    "options": ["outcome","debt","relief"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuzaga kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "arise",
                    "options": ["celebrate","succeed","rely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "musiqiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "musical",
                    "options": ["practical","characteristic","principal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tiklanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "recover",
                    "options": ["arise","celebrate","succeed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ota",
                    "RightAnswer": "dad",
                    "options": ["explanation","outcome","debt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cho'zilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stretch",
                    "options": ["cast","permit","graduate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'lon qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "declare",
                    "options": ["recover","arise","celebrate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nafaqaga chiqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "retire",
                    "options": ["declare","recover","arise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "juda kichik",
                    "RightAnswer": "tiny",
                    "options": ["conservative","unique","reasonable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtiyotkor",
                    "RightAnswer": "careful",
                    "options": ["tiny","conservative","unique"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mos, qulay",
                    "RightAnswer": "suitable",
                    "options": ["careful","tiny","conservative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mahalliy, ona tiliga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "native",
                    "options": ["musical","practical","characteristic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "meva",
                    "RightAnswer": "fruit",
                    "options": ["blame","honor","journey"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tahlil qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "analyze",
                    "options": ["retire","declare","recover"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "guvoh bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "witness",
                    "options": ["fruit","blame","honor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pochta",
                    "RightAnswer": "mail",
                    "options": ["witness","fruit","blame"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dahshatli",
                    "RightAnswer": "terrible",
                    "options": ["suitable","careful","tiny"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tadqiqotchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "researcher",
                    "options": ["dad","explanation","outcome"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odatiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "ordinary",
                    "options": ["native","musical","practical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanlov",
                    "RightAnswer": "selection",
                    "options": ["researcher","dad","explanation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "har qanday joyda",
                    "RightAnswer": "anywhere",
                    "options": ["there","instead","down"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aqliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "mental",
                    "options": ["terrible","suitable","careful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishtirokchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "participant",
                    "options": ["selection","researcher","dad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rish, orzu",
                    "RightAnswer": "vision",
                    "options": ["participant","selection","researcher"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shaxsiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "personality",
                    "options": ["vision","participant","selection"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aynan, asosan",
                    "RightAnswer": "specifically",
                    "options": ["increasingly","seriously","largely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yog'",
                    "RightAnswer": "fat",
                    "options": ["stone","mass","net"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "entry",
                    "options": ["mail","witness","fruit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamkasb, sherik",
                    "RightAnswer": "fellow",
                    "options": ["resident","representative","gold"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kimyoviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "chemical",
                    "options": ["ordinary","native","musical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ushlamoq, qo'lga kiritmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "capture",
                    "options": ["stretch","cast","permit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uch, maslahat",
                    "RightAnswer": "tip",
                    "options": ["entry","mail","witness"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chegirma",
                    "RightAnswer": "discount",
                    "options": ["tip","entry","mail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cho'qqi",
                    "RightAnswer": "peak",
                    "options": ["discount","tip","entry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rais",
                    "RightAnswer": "chairman",
                    "options": ["personality","vision","participant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nisbat, ulush",
                    "RightAnswer": "proportion",
                    "options": ["chairman","personality","vision"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "quloq",
                    "RightAnswer": "ear",
                    "options": ["proportion","chairman","personality"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'qolmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "disappear",
                    "options": ["analyze","retire","declare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baqirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "shout",
                    "options": ["capture","stretch","cast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yarim metr, maydon",
                    "RightAnswer": "yard",
                    "options": ["ear","proportion","chairman"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "doimiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "constant",
                    "options": ["chemical","ordinary","native"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sezilarli darajada",
                    "RightAnswer": "significantly",
                    "options": ["specifically","increasingly","seriously"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tepalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "hill",
                    "options": ["yard","ear","proportion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sezilarli, katta",
                    "RightAnswer": "considerable",
                    "options": ["mental","terrible","suitable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rsatma, dars",
                    "RightAnswer": "instruction",
                    "options": ["hill","yard","ear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aql, ong",
                    "RightAnswer": "intelligence",
                    "options": ["instruction","hill","yard"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mukammal",
                    "RightAnswer": "ideal",
                    "options": ["constant","chemical","ordinary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xalq",
                    "RightAnswer": "folk",
                    "options": ["intelligence","instruction","hill"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "albatta, ishonch bilan",
                    "RightAnswer": "surely",
                    "options": ["significantly","specifically","increasingly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "himoya qilmoq, qo'riqchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "guard",
                    "options": ["shout","capture","stretch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mushuk",
                    "RightAnswer": "cat",
                    "options": ["folk","intelligence","instruction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "biroz",
                    "RightAnswer": "somewhat",
                    "options": ["surely","significantly","specifically"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'pmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "kiss",
                    "options": ["guard","shout","capture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqdimot, ko'rsatma",
                    "RightAnswer": "presentation",
                    "options": ["cat","folk","intelligence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shma, bog'lanish",
                    "RightAnswer": "joint",
                    "options": ["ideal","constant","chemical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqobat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "compete",
                    "options": ["disappear","analyze","retire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'rovnoma, saylov",
                    "RightAnswer": "poll",
                    "options": ["peak","discount","tip"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zaif",
                    "RightAnswer": "weak",
                    "options": ["lovely","bright","proper"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'tiqod, ishonch",
                    "RightAnswer": "faith",
                    "options": ["presentation","cat","folk"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamayish, qisqartirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "reduction",
                    "options": ["faith","presentation","cat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zaxira",
                    "RightAnswer": "reserve",
                    "options": ["kiss","guard","shout"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shikoyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "complaint",
                    "options": ["reduction","faith","presentation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zerikmoq, burg'ulamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bore",
                    "options": ["reserve","kiss","guard"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "missiya, vazifa",
                    "RightAnswer": "mission",
                    "options": ["complaint","reduction","faith"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qandaydir, biroz",
                    "RightAnswer": "somehow",
                    "options": ["somewhat","surely","significantly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ohang",
                    "RightAnswer": "tone",
                    "options": ["mission","complaint","reduction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mahalla",
                    "RightAnswer": "neighborhood",
                    "options": ["tone","mission","complaint"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'lovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "passenger",
                    "options": ["neighborhood","tone","mission"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "adolat",
                    "RightAnswer": "justice",
                    "options": ["passenger","neighborhood","tone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosqich, davr",
                    "RightAnswer": "phase",
                    "options": ["justice","passenger","neighborhood"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oriq, yupqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "thin",
                    "options": ["narrow","frequent","keen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shoshilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rush",
                    "options": ["bore","reserve","kiss"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rasmiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "formal",
                    "options": ["joint","ideal","constant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "din",
                    "RightAnswer": "religion",
                    "options": ["phase","justice","passenger"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ish beruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "employer",
                    "options": ["religion","phase","justice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rad etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reject",
                    "options": ["rush","bore","reserve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ikkinchi, so'nggi",
                    "RightAnswer": "latter",
                    "options": ["sharp","round","abstract"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarelka",
                    "RightAnswer": "plate",
                    "options": ["poll","peak","discount"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqiqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "ban",
                    "options": ["plate","poll","peak"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'g'irlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "steal",
                    "options": ["reject","rush","bore"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "norozilik, namoyish",
                    "RightAnswer": "protest",
                    "options": ["steal","reject","rush"]
                }
            ],
            "level 18": [
                {
                    "Question": "indeks, ko'rsatkich",
                    "RightAnswer": "index",
                    "options": ["ban","plate","poll"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qayg'uli, g'amgin",
                    "RightAnswer": "sad",
                    "options": ["considerable","mental","terrible"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tez-tez",
                    "RightAnswer": "frequently",
                    "options": ["somehow","somewhat","surely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "doira, aylana",
                    "RightAnswer": "circle",
                    "options": ["index","ban","plate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "foydali, yordam beruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "helpful",
                    "options": ["sad","considerable","mental"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "buyrug', boshqarish",
                    "RightAnswer": "command",
                    "options": ["protest","steal","reject"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jozibali, chiroyli",
                    "RightAnswer": "attractive",
                    "options": ["helpful","sad","considerable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kasal",
                    "RightAnswer": "sick",
                    "options": ["square","objective","brief"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taassurot",
                    "RightAnswer": "impression",
                    "options": ["employer","religion","phase"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qodir emas",
                    "RightAnswer": "unable",
                    "options": ["attractive","helpful","sad"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hazil, kulgili so'z",
                    "RightAnswer": "joke",
                    "options": ["circle","index","ban"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "osmon",
                    "RightAnswer": "sky",
                    "options": ["impression","employer","religion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ustun, kolonka",
                    "RightAnswer": "column",
                    "options": ["sky","impression","employer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "elektron",
                    "RightAnswer": "electronic",
                    "options": ["unable","attractive","helpful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "majbur qilmoq, qo'ymoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "impose",
                    "options": ["compete","disappear","analyze"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jinoyatchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "criminal",
                    "options": ["formal","joint","ideal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bundan tashqari, shuningdek",
                    "RightAnswer": "besides",
                    "options": ["throughout","beyond","below"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'g'ri, mos ravishda",
                    "RightAnswer": "properly",
                    "options": ["frequently","somehow","somewhat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qadimgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "ancient",
                    "options": ["criminal","formal","joint"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qirg'oq",
                    "RightAnswer": "coast",
                    "options": ["joke","circle","index"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jiddiy kasal",
                    "RightAnswer": "ill",
                    "options": ["ancient","criminal","formal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "otmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "kick",
                    "options": ["command","protest","steal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaqin, yaqindan",
                    "RightAnswer": "closely",
                    "options": ["properly","frequently","somehow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'p, bir nechta",
                    "RightAnswer": "multiple",
                    "options": ["ill","ancient","criminal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hosil, berish",
                    "RightAnswer": "yield",
                    "options": ["kick","command","protest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "orqali, yondashuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "via",
                    "options": ["onto","despite","upon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qonunchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "legislation",
                    "options": ["column","sky","impression"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuman, viloyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "county",
                    "options": ["legislation","column","sky"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'xshamagan, farqli",
                    "RightAnswer": "unlike",
                    "options": ["via","onto","despite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mobil, harakatlanuvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "mobile",
                    "options": ["multiple","ill","ancient"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yordamchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "assistant",
                    "options": ["county","legislation","column"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "amalga oshirmoq, asbob",
                    "RightAnswer": "implement",
                    "options": ["yield","kick","command"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "diagramma, jadval",
                    "RightAnswer": "chart",
                    "options": ["coast","joke","circle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shmoq, ilova qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "attach",
                    "options": ["impose","compete","disappear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "do'zax",
                    "RightAnswer": "hell",
                    "options": ["assistant","county","legislation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamma joyda",
                    "RightAnswer": "everywhere",
                    "options": ["closely","properly","frequently"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maslahat bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "advise",
                    "options": ["attach","impose","compete"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uy xo'jaligi",
                    "RightAnswer": "household",
                    "options": ["fellow","resident","representative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tan olmoq, e'tirof etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "acknowledge",
                    "options": ["advise","attach","impose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mukofot",
                    "RightAnswer": "reward",
                    "options": ["chart","coast","joke"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sharq",
                    "RightAnswer": "east",
                    "options": ["plenty","west","leather"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shlyapa",
                    "RightAnswer": "hat",
                    "options": ["hell","assistant","county"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "akademik, ilmiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "academic",
                    "options": ["mobile","multiple","ill"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saylovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "voter",
                    "options": ["hat","hell","assistant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shu vaqtda, o'shanda",
                    "RightAnswer": "meanwhile",
                    "options": ["less","most","more"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bundan tashqari, shuningdek",
                    "RightAnswer": "furthermore",
                    "options": ["everywhere","closely","properly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ayblamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "accuse",
                    "options": ["acknowledge","advise","attach"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ilmiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "scientific",
                    "options": ["electronic","unable","attractive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maosh, ish haqi",
                    "RightAnswer": "wage",
                    "options": ["reward","chart","coast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'qlik, qoldirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "absence",
                    "options": ["voter","hat","hell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qurmoq, tuzmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "construct",
                    "options": ["implement","yield","kick"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "izoh, mulohaza",
                    "RightAnswer": "remark",
                    "options": ["construct","implement","yield"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dori-darmon",
                    "RightAnswer": "medicine",
                    "options": ["absence","voter","hat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "professor",
                    "RightAnswer": "professor",
                    "options": ["medicine","absence","voter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamdan-kam, nodir",
                    "RightAnswer": "rare",
                    "options": ["straight","daily","fast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "niyat, maqsad",
                    "RightAnswer": "intention",
                    "options": ["professor","medicine","absence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'n ikkita",
                    "RightAnswer": "dozen",
                    "options": ["intention","professor","medicine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yerlashish, kelishuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "settlement",
                    "options": ["dozen","intention","professor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'shliq, teshik",
                    "RightAnswer": "gap",
                    "options": ["settlement","dozen","intention"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keng tarqalgan, keng doirada",
                    "RightAnswer": "widely",
                    "options": ["furthermore","everywhere","closely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "minimal, eng kam",
                    "RightAnswer": "minimum",
                    "options": ["household","fellow","resident"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shimoliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "northern",
                    "options": ["academic","mobile","multiple"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mulk, yer",
                    "RightAnswer": "estate",
                    "options": ["gap","settlement","dozen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teng ravishda",
                    "RightAnswer": "equally",
                    "options": ["widely","furthermore","everywhere"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ochib berish, ko'rsatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "expose",
                    "options": ["accuse","acknowledge","advise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jonli, tirik",
                    "RightAnswer": "alive",
                    "options": ["scientific","electronic","unable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yopmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "shut",
                    "options": ["suspect","select","cross"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'alaba",
                    "RightAnswer": "victory",
                    "options": ["estate","gap","settlement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hal qilmoq, yechim topmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "resolve",
                    "options": ["remark","construct","implement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanqidchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "critic",
                    "options": ["victory","estate","gap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zgaruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "variable",
                    "options": ["northern","academic","mobile"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ulkan, katta",
                    "RightAnswer": "enormous",
                    "options": ["alive","scientific","electronic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shirin",
                    "RightAnswer": "sweet",
                    "options": ["sick","square","objective"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "doimiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "permanent",
                    "options": ["variable","northern","academic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "his-tuyg'u",
                    "RightAnswer": "emotion",
                    "options": ["critic","victory","estate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "izlamoq, orzu qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pursue",
                    "options": ["expose","accuse","acknowledge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baland",
                    "RightAnswer": "tall",
                    "options": ["opposite","left","flat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shoshilmoq, rag'batlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "urge",
                    "options": ["resolve","remark","construct"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dushman",
                    "RightAnswer": "enemy",
                    "options": ["emotion","critic","victory"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayinlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "appoint",
                    "options": ["pursue","expose","accuse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sut",
                    "RightAnswer": "milk",
                    "options": ["wage","reward","chart"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iste'dod",
                    "RightAnswer": "talent",
                    "options": ["enemy","emotion","critic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hid, hidlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "smell",
                    "options": ["urge","resolve","remark"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "avvalgi, oldingi",
                    "RightAnswer": "prior",
                    "options": ["permanent","variable","northern"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ustuvorlik, birinchi navbatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "priority",
                    "options": ["talent","enemy","emotion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "onlayn, internet orqali",
                    "RightAnswer": "online",
                    "options": ["weak","lovely","bright"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ibora, jumla",
                    "RightAnswer": "phrase",
                    "options": ["milk","wage","reward"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uchuvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "pilot",
                    "options": ["phrase","milk","wage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "barqaror",
                    "RightAnswer": "stable",
                    "options": ["prior","permanent","variable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faqatgina, oddiygina",
                    "RightAnswer": "merely",
                    "options": ["equally","widely","furthermore"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yechim, qaror",
                    "RightAnswer": "resolution",
                    "options": ["priority","talent","enemy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muloqot qilmoq, yetkazmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "communicate",
                    "options": ["appoint","pursue","expose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jarohat",
                    "RightAnswer": "injury",
                    "options": ["resolution","priority","talent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "katta, keng",
                    "RightAnswer": "vast",
                    "options": ["enormous","alive","scientific"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rgazma",
                    "RightAnswer": "exhibition",
                    "options": ["injury","resolution","priority"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishlab chiqaruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "producer",
                    "options": ["exhibition","injury","resolution"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mintaqaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "regional",
                    "options": ["vast","enormous","alive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "darhol, zudlik bilan",
                    "RightAnswer": "immediate",
                    "options": ["stable","prior","permanent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hodisa, voqea",
                    "RightAnswer": "incident",
                    "options": ["producer","exhibition","injury"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bolalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "childhood",
                    "options": ["incident","producer","exhibition"]
                }
            ],
            "level 19": [
                {
                    "Question": "loyiha, chizma",
                    "RightAnswer": "draft",
                    "options": ["pilot","phrase","milk"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sirpanish, qochmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "slip",
                    "options": ["smell","urge","resolve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamroh bo'lmoq, olib kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "accompany",
                    "options": ["communicate","appoint","pursue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "siyosatchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "politician",
                    "options": ["childhood","incident","producer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'azablangan",
                    "RightAnswer": "angry",
                    "options": ["regional","vast","enormous"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqqilatmoq, urmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "knock",
                    "options": ["slip","smell","urge"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "urug'",
                    "RightAnswer": "seed",
                    "options": ["draft","pilot","phrase"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "salary",
                    "options": ["politician","childhood","incident"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasvirlamoq, misol keltirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "illustrate",
                    "options": ["accompany","communicate","appoint"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sha'ma qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "imply",
                    "options": ["illustrate","accompany","communicate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nonushta",
                    "RightAnswer": "breakfast",
                    "options": ["salary","politician","childhood"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vaqtincha",
                    "RightAnswer": "temporary",
                    "options": ["immediate","stable","prior"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "erkin fikrlovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "liberal",
                    "options": ["temporary","immediate","stable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "lake",
                    "options": ["breakfast","salary","politician"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "malakali bo'lmoq, mos kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "qualify",
                    "options": ["imply","illustrate","accompany"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqobatbardosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "competitive",
                    "options": ["angry","regional","vast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqatan, chin dildan",
                    "RightAnswer": "truly",
                    "options": ["merely","equally","widely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "salom h_) : hi,",
                    "RightAnswer": "hi",
                    "options": ["each","another","both"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sariq",
                    "RightAnswer": "yellow",
                    "options": ["liberal","temporary","immediate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odat, xulq",
                    "RightAnswer": "habit",
                    "options": ["lake","breakfast","salary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tekis, aylana narsa",
                    "RightAnswer": "disk",
                    "options": ["habit","lake","breakfast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yadro, asos",
                    "RightAnswer": "core",
                    "options": ["disk","habit","lake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hissiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "emotional",
                    "options": ["competitive","angry","regional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "samolyot",
                    "RightAnswer": "aircraft",
                    "options": ["core","disk","habit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zi",
                    "RightAnswer": "self",
                    "options": ["ourselves","anybody","nobody"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "metal",
                    "RightAnswer": "metal",
                    "options": ["aircraft","core","disk"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavjudlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "existence",
                    "options": ["metal","aircraft","core"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suyak",
                    "RightAnswer": "bone",
                    "options": ["existence","metal","aircraft"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "panel, panjara",
                    "RightAnswer": "panel",
                    "options": ["seed","draft","pilot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosiy, birinchi darajali",
                    "RightAnswer": "prime",
                    "options": ["sweet","sick","square"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayinlash, uchrashuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "appointment",
                    "options": ["bone","existence","metal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'kidlash, urg'u berish",
                    "RightAnswer": "emphasize",
                    "options": ["qualify","imply","illustrate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maksimal, eng katta",
                    "RightAnswer": "maximum",
                    "options": ["minimum","household","fellow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "samarali tarzda",
                    "RightAnswer": "effectively",
                    "options": ["truly","merely","equally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshqa joyda",
                    "RightAnswer": "elsewhere",
                    "options": ["effectively","truly","merely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashvishlanmoq, aralashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bother",
                    "options": ["knock","slip","smell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashabbus",
                    "RightAnswer": "initiative",
                    "options": ["appointment","bone","existence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'tkir, tez",
                    "RightAnswer": "sharp",
                    "options": ["round","abstract","concrete"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "parhez, dieta",
                    "RightAnswer": "diet",
                    "options": ["panel","seed","draft"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "harakat, tuzatish",
                    "RightAnswer": "motion",
                    "options": ["diet","panel","seed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kulrang",
                    "RightAnswer": "gray",
                    "options": ["yellow","liberal","temporary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "plastik",
                    "RightAnswer": "plastic",
                    "options": ["gray","yellow","liberal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "murakkablashtirmoq, qiyinlashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "complicate",
                    "options": ["emphasize","qualify","imply"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "intizom",
                    "RightAnswer": "discipline",
                    "options": ["motion","diet","panel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kutgandek chiqmaslik, ko'nglini qoldirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "disappoint",
                    "options": ["complicate","emphasize","qualify"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rahbar, ish beruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "boss",
                    "options": ["discipline","motion","diet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxmin, faraz",
                    "RightAnswer": "assumption",
                    "options": ["initiative","appointment","bone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muzlamoq, muzlatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "freeze",
                    "options": ["bother","knock","slip"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ekstremal, haddan tashqari",
                    "RightAnswer": "extreme",
                    "options": ["plastic","gray","yellow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'tish, matn",
                    "RightAnswer": "passage",
                    "options": ["assumption","initiative","appointment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "obro', sha'n",
                    "RightAnswer": "reputation",
                    "options": ["passage","assumption","initiative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oldinga",
                    "RightAnswer": "forth",
                    "options": ["meanwhile","less","most"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muzokara, kelishuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "negotiation",
                    "options": ["reputation","passage","assumption"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mexanizm, usul",
                    "RightAnswer": "mechanism",
                    "options": ["negotiation","reputation","passage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "paltolar, poyabzal",
                    "RightAnswer": "coat",
                    "options": ["boss","discipline","motion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "demokratiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "democracy",
                    "options": ["mechanism","negotiation","reputation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cho'ntak",
                    "RightAnswer": "pocket",
                    "options": ["coat","boss","discipline"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "omadli",
                    "RightAnswer": "lucky",
                    "options": ["online","weak","lovely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'qnashuv, avariya",
                    "RightAnswer": "crash",
                    "options": ["freeze","bother","knock"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuzatuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "observation",
                    "options": ["democracy","mechanism","negotiation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "go'sht",
                    "RightAnswer": "meat",
                    "options": ["observation","democracy","mechanism"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "diqqat, e'tibor",
                    "RightAnswer": "concentration",
                    "options": ["meat","observation","democracy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "natija, oqibat",
                    "RightAnswer": "implication",
                    "options": ["concentration","meat","observation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "munosib bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "deserve",
                    "options": ["disappoint","complicate","emphasize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noodatiy, g'alati",
                    "RightAnswer": "unusual",
                    "options": ["emotional","competitive","angry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "himoya qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "defend",
                    "options": ["deserve","disappoint","complicate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "klassik, an'anaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "classic",
                    "options": ["extreme","plastic","gray"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "podshoh",
                    "RightAnswer": "king",
                    "options": ["implication","concentration","meat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zaro aloqalar, muloqot",
                    "RightAnswer": "interaction",
                    "options": ["king","implication","concentration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'mirlash, tuzatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "repair",
                    "options": ["crash","freeze","bother"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qulab tushmoq, yiqilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "collapse",
                    "options": ["repair","crash","freeze"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarz olmoq, olib turmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "borrow",
                    "options": ["defend","deserve","disappoint"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosiy, fundamental",
                    "RightAnswer": "fundamental",
                    "options": ["classic","extreme","plastic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taom, idish",
                    "RightAnswer": "dish",
                    "options": ["pocket","coat","boss"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xorijda, chet elda",
                    "RightAnswer": "abroad",
                    "options": ["apart","ahead","forward"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jon, ruh",
                    "RightAnswer": "soul",
                    "options": ["interaction","king","implication"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qodir, imkoniyatga ega",
                    "RightAnswer": "capable",
                    "options": ["unusual","emotional","competitive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yutmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "defeat",
                    "options": ["collapse","repair","crash"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "prezidentga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "presidential",
                    "options": ["capable","unusual","emotional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mukammal tarzda",
                    "RightAnswer": "perfectly",
                    "options": ["elsewhere","effectively","truly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuchaytirmoq, yaxshilamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "enhance",
                    "options": ["borrow","defend","deserve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faxrlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "proud",
                    "options": ["presidential","capable","unusual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "favqulodda vaziyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "emergency",
                    "options": ["soul","interaction","king"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'limga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "educational",
                    "options": ["proud","presidential","capable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "farqlamoq, ajrata olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "distinguish",
                    "options": ["enhance","borrow","defend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sezilarli, muhim",
                    "RightAnswer": "substantial",
                    "options": ["fundamental","classic","extreme"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "nearby",
                    "options": ["lucky","online","weak"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishlab chiqaruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "manufacturer",
                    "options": ["emergency","soul","interaction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sirpanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "slide",
                    "options": ["defeat","collapse","repair"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qimmatli",
                    "RightAnswer": "valuable",
                    "options": ["substantial","fundamental","classic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shaxsan",
                    "RightAnswer": "personally",
                    "options": ["perfectly","elsewhere","effectively"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiyinchiliklarga bardosh bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cope",
                    "options": ["distinguish","enhance","borrow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxminan",
                    "RightAnswer": "approximately",
                    "options": ["personally","perfectly","elsewhere"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joylashuv, turar joy",
                    "RightAnswer": "accommodation",
                    "options": ["manufacturer","emergency","soul"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajratib ko'rsatmoq, urg'u bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "highlight",
                    "options": ["slide","defeat","collapse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sharxlovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "reporter",
                    "options": ["accommodation","manufacturer","emergency"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iqlim",
                    "RightAnswer": "climate",
                    "options": ["reporter","accommodation","manufacturer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'ylak",
                    "RightAnswer": "shirt",
                    "options": ["climate","reporter","accommodation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "istisno",
                    "RightAnswer": "exception",
                    "options": ["shirt","climate","reporter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "korporatsiya, kompaniya",
                    "RightAnswer": "corporation",
                    "options": ["exception","shirt","climate"]
                }
            ],
            "level 20": [
                {
                    "Question": "bo'lak",
                    "RightAnswer": "chip",
                    "options": ["dish","pocket","coat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'olib",
                    "RightAnswer": "winner",
                    "options": ["corporation","exception","shirt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "duch kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "encounter",
                    "options": ["highlight","slide","defeat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jigarrang",
                    "RightAnswer": "brown",
                    "options": ["valuable","substantial","fundamental"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nafas olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "breathe",
                    "options": ["cope","distinguish","enhance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzr, bahona",
                    "RightAnswer": "excuse",
                    "options": ["encounter","highlight","slide"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qisman",
                    "RightAnswer": "partly",
                    "options": ["approximately","personally","perfectly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tennis",
                    "RightAnswer": "tennis",
                    "options": ["winner","corporation","exception"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shahar bilan bog'liq",
                    "RightAnswer": "urban",
                    "options": ["brown","valuable","substantial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chalkashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "confuse",
                    "options": ["breathe","cope","distinguish"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "janubiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "southern",
                    "options": ["odd","north","south"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiqim, hosil",
                    "RightAnswer": "output",
                    "options": ["chip","dish","pocket"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "go'zallik",
                    "RightAnswer": "beauty",
                    "options": ["tennis","winner","corporation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ulkan, katta",
                    "RightAnswer": "massive",
                    "options": ["urban","brown","valuable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rnatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "install",
                    "options": ["confuse","breathe","cope"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisoblamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "calculate",
                    "options": ["install","confuse","breathe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sichqon, sichqoncha",
                    "RightAnswer": "mouse",
                    "options": ["beauty","tennis","winner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "matematika",
                    "RightAnswer": "mathematics",
                    "options": ["mouse","beauty","tennis"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuqori",
                    "RightAnswer": "upper",
                    "options": ["southern","odd","north"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaratish, yaratilish",
                    "RightAnswer": "creation",
                    "options": ["mathematics","mouse","beauty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egallamoq, band qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "occupy",
                    "options": ["calculate","install","confuse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuzaki tushuntirmoq, kontur",
                    "RightAnswer": "outline",
                    "options": ["excuse","encounter","highlight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "sufficient",
                    "options": ["educational","proud","presidential"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yangilamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "update",
                    "options": ["outline","excuse","encounter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "omad",
                    "RightAnswer": "luck",
                    "options": ["creation","mathematics","mouse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saqlamoq, himoya qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "preserve",
                    "options": ["update","outline","excuse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajratmoq, bo'lishmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "split",
                    "options": ["preserve","update","outline"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tebranmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "swing",
                    "options": ["split","preserve","update"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kasallik",
                    "RightAnswer": "illness",
                    "options": ["luck","creation","mathematics"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jurnalist",
                    "RightAnswer": "journalist",
                    "options": ["illness","luck","creation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birdaniga, kutilmaganda",
                    "RightAnswer": "sudden",
                    "options": ["upper","southern","odd"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "reklama",
                    "RightAnswer": "advertisement",
                    "options": ["journalist","illness","luck"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "izchil, muntazam",
                    "RightAnswer": "consistent",
                    "options": ["sufficient","educational","proud"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dastlab, aslida",
                    "RightAnswer": "originally",
                    "options": ["partly","approximately","personally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yon taraf, chetga",
                    "RightAnswer": "aside",
                    "options": ["forth","meanwhile","less"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qulaylik, tasalli",
                    "RightAnswer": "comfort",
                    "options": ["output","chip","dish"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ikkinchi navbatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "secondly",
                    "options": ["originally","partly","approximately"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jiddiy, og'ir",
                    "RightAnswer": "severe",
                    "options": ["consistent","sufficient","educational"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gen",
                    "RightAnswer": "gene",
                    "options": ["advertisement","journalist","illness"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "istiqbollar, kelajak",
                    "RightAnswer": "prospect",
                    "options": ["comfort","output","chip"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qor",
                    "RightAnswer": "snow",
                    "options": ["prospect","comfort","output"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "syujet, rejalashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "plot",
                    "options": ["snow","prospect","comfort"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'yin",
                    "RightAnswer": "neck",
                    "options": ["gene","advertisement","journalist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "me'zon, talablar",
                    "RightAnswer": "criteria",
                    "options": ["thirst","hunger","noun"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosan",
                    "RightAnswer": "primarily",
                    "options": ["secondly","originally","partly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "integratsiya qilmoq, birlashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "integrate",
                    "options": ["occupy","calculate","install"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanqid",
                    "RightAnswer": "criticism",
                    "options": ["neck","gene","advertisement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "anjuman, kelishuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "convention",
                    "options": ["criticism","neck","gene"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pul tikmoq, garov",
                    "RightAnswer": "bet",
                    "options": ["swing","split","preserve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saqlab qolmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "retain",
                    "options": ["integrate","occupy","calculate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ketma-ketlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "sequence",
                    "options": ["convention","criticism","neck"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oddiy, tekis",
                    "RightAnswer": "plain",
                    "options": ["massive","urban","brown"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'ngilli",
                    "RightAnswer": "volunteer",
                    "options": ["bet","swing","split"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qishloq bilan bog'liq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rural",
                    "options": ["severe","consistent","sufficient"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tinch",
                    "RightAnswer": "calm",
                    "options": ["empty","dry","double"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tark etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "abandon",
                    "options": ["retain","integrate","occupy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imtihon, tekshiruv",
                    "RightAnswer": "examination",
                    "options": ["sequence","convention","criticism"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jimlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "silence",
                    "options": ["plot","snow","prospect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tezda",
                    "RightAnswer": "rapidly",
                    "options": ["primarily","secondly","originally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "samarali",
                    "RightAnswer": "efficient",
                    "options": ["rural","severe","consistent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "inqilob",
                    "RightAnswer": "revolution",
                    "options": ["examination","sequence","convention"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zavq, mamnuniyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "delight",
                    "options": ["silence","plot","snow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sehr, imlo",
                    "RightAnswer": "spell",
                    "options": ["volunteer","bet","swing"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asosiy fikr, bosh g'oya",
                    "RightAnswer": "premise",
                    "options": ["revolution","examination","sequence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moyil bo'lmoq, cho'zilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "lean",
                    "options": ["shut","suspect","select"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dramatik, hayajonli",
                    "RightAnswer": "dramatic",
                    "options": ["efficient","rural","severe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "farqlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "differ",
                    "options": ["abandon","retain","integrate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "minnatdor",
                    "RightAnswer": "grateful",
                    "options": ["dramatic","efficient","rural"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oqsil",
                    "RightAnswer": "protein",
                    "options": ["premise","revolution","examination"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "velosiped",
                    "RightAnswer": "bike",
                    "options": ["delight","silence","plot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taqsimlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "distribute",
                    "options": ["differ","abandon","retain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aqliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "intellectual",
                    "options": ["plain","massive","urban"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kelib chiqmoq, olinmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "derive",
                    "options": ["distribute","differ","abandon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muhim, hal qiluvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "crucial",
                    "options": ["grateful","dramatic","efficient"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishsizlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "unemployment",
                    "options": ["protein","premise","revolution"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'ildirak",
                    "RightAnswer": "wheel",
                    "options": ["unemployment","protein","premise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hosil, ekin",
                    "RightAnswer": "crop",
                    "options": ["bike","delight","silence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ozchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "minority",
                    "options": ["wheel","unemployment","protein"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kelib chiqish, asl manba",
                    "RightAnswer": "origin",
                    "options": ["minority","wheel","unemployment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "talqin, izoh",
                    "RightAnswer": "interpretation",
                    "options": ["origin","minority","wheel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "janob, hurmatli erkak",
                    "RightAnswer": "gentleman",
                    "options": ["interpretation","origin","minority"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "drama, sahna san'ati",
                    "RightAnswer": "drama",
                    "options": ["gentleman","interpretation","origin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "landshaft, manzara",
                    "RightAnswer": "landscape",
                    "options": ["drama","gentleman","interpretation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'lim berish, o'rgatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "educate",
                    "options": ["derive","distribute","differ"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'yinchoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "toy",
                    "options": ["crop","bike","delight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xato, nuqson",
                    "RightAnswer": "fault",
                    "options": ["toy","crop","bike"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rsatmoq, namoyish qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exhibit",
                    "options": ["spell","volunteer","bet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kichik, muhim bo'lmagan",
                    "RightAnswer": "minor",
                    "options": ["intellectual","plain","massive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ovlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hunt",
                    "options": ["exhibit","spell","volunteer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'ron",
                    "RightAnswer": "storm",
                    "options": ["fault","toy","crop"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qalin",
                    "RightAnswer": "thick",
                    "options": ["nearby","lucky","online"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yutuq, erishuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "achievement",
                    "options": ["landscape","drama","gentleman"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muzokara qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "negotiate",
                    "options": ["educate","derive","distribute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hukmronlik qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "dominate",
                    "options": ["negotiate","educate","derive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'minotchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "supplier",
                    "options": ["achievement","landscape","drama"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mukofot",
                    "RightAnswer": "prize",
                    "options": ["storm","fault","toy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "typically",
                    "options": ["rapidly","primarily","secondly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tengdosh",
                    "RightAnswer": "peer",
                    "options": ["prize","storm","fault"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pensiya, nafaqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "pension",
                    "options": ["supplier","achievement","landscape"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qanot",
                    "RightAnswer": "wing",
                    "options": ["peer","prize","storm"]
                }
            ],
            "level 21": [
                {
                    "Question": "egallash, sotib olish",
                    "RightAnswer": "acquisition",
                    "options": ["pension","supplier","achievement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kulgu",
                    "RightAnswer": "laughter",
                    "options": ["acquisition","pension","supplier"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chuqur",
                    "RightAnswer": "deeply",
                    "options": ["typically","rapidly","primarily"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tan olmoq, e'tirof",
                    "RightAnswer": "recognition",
                    "options": ["laughter","acquisition","pension"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "elektr",
                    "RightAnswer": "electricity",
                    "options": ["recognition","laughter","acquisition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yordam",
                    "RightAnswer": "assistance",
                    "options": ["electricity","recognition","laughter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tom",
                    "RightAnswer": "roof",
                    "options": ["assistance","electricity","recognition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nafaqaga chiqish",
                    "RightAnswer": "retirement",
                    "options": ["roof","assistance","electricity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mos ravishda",
                    "RightAnswer": "respectively",
                    "options": ["deeply","typically","rapidly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zgarish, farq",
                    "RightAnswer": "variation",
                    "options": ["retirement","roof","assistance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nihoyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "ultimately",
                    "options": ["respectively","deeply","typically"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dalil, isbot",
                    "RightAnswer": "proof",
                    "options": ["maximum","minimum","household"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuproq",
                    "RightAnswer": "soil",
                    "options": ["wing","peer","prize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aqlli, aqlli ko'rinish",
                    "RightAnswer": "smart",
                    "options": ["secure","perfect","correct"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qatlam",
                    "RightAnswer": "layer",
                    "options": ["soil","wing","peer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'azablangan, qayg'u",
                    "RightAnswer": "upset",
                    "options": ["hurt","grin","cough"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tish",
                    "RightAnswer": "tooth",
                    "options": ["variation","retirement","roof"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vakillik, namoyon etish",
                    "RightAnswer": "representation",
                    "options": ["tooth","variation","retirement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayyorgarlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "preparation",
                    "options": ["representation","tooth","variation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bahs, nizolar",
                    "RightAnswer": "dispute",
                    "options": ["layer","soil","wing"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kun tartibi",
                    "RightAnswer": "agenda",
                    "options": ["preparation","representation","tooth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "urg'u, ta'kidlash",
                    "RightAnswer": "emphasis",
                    "options": ["agenda","preparation","representation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nashr, adad",
                    "RightAnswer": "edition",
                    "options": ["emphasis","agenda","preparation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kumush",
                    "RightAnswer": "silver",
                    "options": ["proof","maximum","minimum"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'ngilochar mashg'ulot",
                    "RightAnswer": "entertainment",
                    "options": ["edition","emphasis","agenda"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "halol, rostgo'y",
                    "RightAnswer": "honest",
                    "options": ["crucial","grateful","dramatic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshlamoq, qo'lga kiritmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "undertake",
                    "options": ["dominate","negotiate","educate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chakana savdo",
                    "RightAnswer": "retail",
                    "options": ["silver","proof","maximum"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sim",
                    "RightAnswer": "wire",
                    "options": ["dispute","layer","soil"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtimoldan yiroq",
                    "RightAnswer": "unlikely",
                    "options": ["honest","crucial","grateful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nashr, e'lon",
                    "RightAnswer": "publication",
                    "options": ["entertainment","edition","emphasis"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "biroz",
                    "RightAnswer": "slight",
                    "options": ["prime","sweet","sick"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noma'lum",
                    "RightAnswer": "unknown",
                    "options": ["minor","intellectual","plain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asos, tuzilma",
                    "RightAnswer": "framework",
                    "options": ["publication","entertainment","edition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zona, hudud",
                    "RightAnswer": "zone",
                    "options": ["framework","publication","entertainment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cheklamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "restrict",
                    "options": ["undertake","dominate","negotiate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iz, izlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "trace",
                    "options": ["wire","dispute","layer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dyum",
                    "RightAnswer": "inch",
                    "options": ["trace","wire","dispute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teng ekvivalent",
                    "RightAnswer": "equivalent",
                    "options": ["retail","silver","proof"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mustahkam, qattiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "solid",
                    "options": ["slight","prime","sweet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "korxona, biznes",
                    "RightAnswer": "enterprise",
                    "options": ["zone","framework","publication"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keksa",
                    "RightAnswer": "elderly",
                    "options": ["unknown","minor","intellectual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarz olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "owe",
                    "options": ["restrict","undertake","dominate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gubernator, hokim",
                    "RightAnswer": "governor",
                    "options": ["enterprise","zone","framework"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bir xil, uniforma",
                    "RightAnswer": "uniform",
                    "options": ["elderly","unknown","minor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bandargoh",
                    "RightAnswer": "port",
                    "options": ["inch","trace","wire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mum, ovoz kuchi, maydon",
                    "RightAnswer": "pitch",
                    "options": ["port","inch","trace"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetib kelish",
                    "RightAnswer": "arrival",
                    "options": ["governor","enterprise","zone"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zamonaviy, hozirgi davrga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "contemporary",
                    "options": ["uniform","elderly","unknown"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "darvoza, eshik",
                    "RightAnswer": "gate",
                    "options": ["arrival","governor","enterprise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yengillik, qulaylik",
                    "RightAnswer": "ease",
                    "options": ["pitch","port","inch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pivo",
                    "RightAnswer": "beer",
                    "options": ["gate","arrival","governor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mutaxassis",
                    "RightAnswer": "specialist",
                    "options": ["beer","gate","arrival"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishonch bermoq, kafolatlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "assure",
                    "options": ["owe","restrict","undertake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "profil, tavsif",
                    "RightAnswer": "profile",
                    "options": ["ease","pitch","port"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kayfiyat, holat",
                    "RightAnswer": "mood",
                    "options": ["specialist","beer","gate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "epizod, voqea",
                    "RightAnswer": "episode",
                    "options": ["mood","specialist","beer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoriq",
                    "RightAnswer": "crack",
                    "options": ["hunt","exhibit","spell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'p",
                    "RightAnswer": "numerous",
                    "options": ["unlikely","honest","crucial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "topshirmoq, qabul qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "submit",
                    "options": ["assure","owe","restrict"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "alomat, belgi",
                    "RightAnswer": "symptom",
                    "options": ["episode","mood","specialist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "deyarli, amalda",
                    "RightAnswer": "virtually",
                    "options": ["ultimately","respectively","deeply"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "davr, asr",
                    "RightAnswer": "era",
                    "options": ["symptom","episode","mood"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qamrab olmoq, yoritish",
                    "RightAnswer": "coverage",
                    "options": ["era","symptom","episode"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "siqilish, taranglik",
                    "RightAnswer": "tension",
                    "options": ["coverage","era","symptom"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kabel, sim",
                    "RightAnswer": "cable",
                    "options": ["tension","coverage","era"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasirchan",
                    "RightAnswer": "sensitive",
                    "options": ["numerous","unlikely","honest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asabiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "nervous",
                    "options": ["sensitive","numerous","unlikely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kirish, ma'lumot",
                    "RightAnswer": "input",
                    "options": ["profile","ease","pitch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajratmoq, izolyatsiya qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "isolate",
                    "options": ["submit","assure","owe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maxbus",
                    "RightAnswer": "prisoner",
                    "options": ["cable","tension","coverage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'qotmoq, bartaraf etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "eliminate",
                    "options": ["isolate","submit","assure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tor, qattiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "tight",
                    "options": ["wild","quiet","slow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ho'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "wet",
                    "options": ["calm","empty","dry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ikkinchi, qo'shimcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "secondary",
                    "options": ["contemporary","uniform","elderly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "farovonlik, ijtimoiy ko'mak",
                    "RightAnswer": "welfare",
                    "options": ["prisoner","cable","tension"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishga qabul qilmoq, ro'yxatdan o'tmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "recruit",
                    "options": ["crack","hunt","exhibit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kiritmaslik, chiqarib tashlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exclude",
                    "options": ["eliminate","isolate","submit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ip",
                    "RightAnswer": "string",
                    "options": ["input","profile","ease"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bulut",
                    "RightAnswer": "cloud",
                    "options": ["string","input","profile"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishontirmoq, rag'batlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "persuade",
                    "options": ["exclude","eliminate","isolate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ilhomlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "inspire",
                    "options": ["persuade","exclude","eliminate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "katta, ajoyib",
                    "RightAnswer": "grand",
                    "options": ["secondary","contemporary","uniform"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shuning uchun",
                    "RightAnswer": "hence",
                    "options": ["otherwise","yet","once"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ekipaj, jamoa",
                    "RightAnswer": "crew",
                    "options": ["cloud","string","input"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hodisa, voqea",
                    "RightAnswer": "phenomenon",
                    "options": ["welfare","prisoner","cable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'quvchi, qorachiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pupil",
                    "options": ["phenomenon","welfare","prisoner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noto’g’ri, sohta",
                    "RightAnswer": "false",
                    "options": ["grand","secondary","contemporary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yordam bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "assist",
                    "options": ["inspire","persuade","exclude"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tiklamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "restore",
                    "options": ["assist","inspire","persuade"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "formula",
                    "RightAnswer": "formula",
                    "options": ["pupil","phenomenon","welfare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "alter",
                    "options": ["elect","express","close"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sezmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "perceive",
                    "options": ["restore","assist","inspire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kundalik tartib",
                    "RightAnswer": "routine",
                    "options": ["equivalent","retail","silver"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ho'l yuvish idishi",
                    "RightAnswer": "sink",
                    "options": ["recruit","crack","hunt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qaramoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stare",
                    "options": ["sink","recruit","crack"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "endi",
                    "RightAnswer": "anymore",
                    "options": ["anywhere","there","instead"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qahramon",
                    "RightAnswer": "hero",
                    "options": ["formula","pupil","phenomenon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'llab-quvvatlovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "supporter",
                    "options": ["hero","formula","pupil"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aylantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "convert",
                    "options": ["stare","sink","recruit"]
                }
            ],
            "level 22": [
                {
                    "Question": "barqaror",
                    "RightAnswer": "steady",
                    "options": ["smart","secure","perfect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "metr",
                    "RightAnswer": "meter",
                    "options": ["supporter","hero","formula"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuk mashinasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "truck",
                    "options": ["crew","cloud","string"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "burun",
                    "RightAnswer": "nose",
                    "options": ["truck","crew","cloud"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yonida",
                    "RightAnswer": "beside",
                    "options": ["besides","throughout","beyond"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qayiq yelkasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "sail",
                    "options": ["convert","stare","sink"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "falokat",
                    "RightAnswer": "disaster",
                    "options": ["meter","supporter","hero"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tezlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "pace",
                    "options": ["nose","truck","crew"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "og'irlik bilan",
                    "RightAnswer": "heavily",
                    "options": ["virtually","ultimately","respectively"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bag'ishlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "devote",
                    "options": ["perceive","restore","assist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "terrorchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "terrorist",
                    "options": ["disaster","meter","supporter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asoslamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "justify",
                    "options": ["devote","perceive","restore"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zaruriy",
                    "RightAnswer": "vital",
                    "options": ["false","grand","secondary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayratlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fascinate",
                    "options": ["justify","devote","perceive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashqi",
                    "RightAnswer": "external",
                    "options": ["nervous","sensitive","numerous"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ortiqcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "spare",
                    "options": ["wet","calm","empty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qachonki",
                    "RightAnswer": "whenever",
                    "options": ["nevertheless","therefore","though"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "depressiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "depression",
                    "options": ["terrorist","disaster","meter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aybdor",
                    "RightAnswer": "guilty",
                    "options": ["external","nervous","sensitive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "poydevor bo'lmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "underlie",
                    "options": ["fascinate","justify","devote"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ona",
                    "RightAnswer": "mom",
                    "options": ["depression","terrorist","disaster"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "farq",
                    "RightAnswer": "distinction",
                    "options": ["mom","depression","terrorist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qoniqish",
                    "RightAnswer": "satisfaction",
                    "options": ["distinction","mom","depression"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birlashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "incorporate",
                    "options": ["underlie","fascinate","justify"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'kmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pour",
                    "options": ["sail","convert","stare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chang yutmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sweep",
                    "options": ["pour","sail","convert"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "majburiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "obligation",
                    "options": ["satisfaction","distinction","mom"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "janob",
                    "RightAnswer": "sir",
                    "options": ["outside","tonight","tomorrow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baholamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "evaluate",
                    "options": ["incorporate","underlie","fascinate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'azab",
                    "RightAnswer": "anger",
                    "options": ["obligation","satisfaction","distinction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qovoqxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "pub",
                    "options": ["anger","obligation","satisfaction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qabul qilish",
                    "RightAnswer": "perception",
                    "options": ["pub","anger","obligation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tabiiy ravishda",
                    "RightAnswer": "naturally",
                    "options": ["heavily","virtually","ultimately"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "valuta",
                    "RightAnswer": "currency",
                    "options": ["perception","pub","anger"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma'lumotlar bazasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "database",
                    "options": ["currency","perception","pub"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dastlab",
                    "RightAnswer": "initially",
                    "options": ["naturally","heavily","virtually"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hudud",
                    "RightAnswer": "territory",
                    "options": ["database","currency","perception"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "daryo",
                    "RightAnswer": "stream",
                    "options": ["pace","nose","truck"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamdan-kam",
                    "RightAnswer": "rarely",
                    "options": ["initially","naturally","heavily"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "balandlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "height",
                    "options": ["territory","database","currency"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ravshan",
                    "RightAnswer": "apparent",
                    "options": ["guilty","external","nervous"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'arbiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "western",
                    "options": ["sudden","upper","southern"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kengayish",
                    "RightAnswer": "expansion",
                    "options": ["height","territory","database"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "doimo",
                    "RightAnswer": "constantly",
                    "options": ["rarely","initially","naturally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mushak",
                    "RightAnswer": "muscle",
                    "options": ["expansion","height","territory"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'rqitmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "scare",
                    "options": ["sweep","pour","sail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yomon",
                    "RightAnswer": "badly",
                    "options": ["abroad","apart","ahead"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kundalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "everyday",
                    "options": ["vital","false","grand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chegara",
                    "RightAnswer": "boundary",
                    "options": ["muscle","expansion","height"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nisbat",
                    "RightAnswer": "ratio",
                    "options": ["boundary","muscle","expansion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "insho",
                    "RightAnswer": "essay",
                    "options": ["stream","pace","nose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baqirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "scream",
                    "options": ["scare","sweep","pour"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chekinmoq, chiqarib olmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "withdraw",
                    "options": ["evaluate","incorporate","underlie"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ifloslanish",
                    "RightAnswer": "pollution",
                    "options": ["ratio","boundary","muscle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tartibsizlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "disorder",
                    "options": ["essay","stream","pace"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mebel",
                    "RightAnswer": "furniture",
                    "options": ["pollution","ratio","boundary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ramz",
                    "RightAnswer": "symbol",
                    "options": ["furniture","pollution","ratio"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kvartira",
                    "RightAnswer": "apartment",
                    "options": ["symbol","furniture","pollution"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "namoyish",
                    "RightAnswer": "demonstration",
                    "options": ["apartment","symbol","furniture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tahlilchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "analyst",
                    "options": ["demonstration","apartment","symbol"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "platforma",
                    "RightAnswer": "platform",
                    "options": ["analyst","demonstration","apartment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "po'lat",
                    "RightAnswer": "steel",
                    "options": ["disorder","essay","stream"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tort",
                    "RightAnswer": "cake",
                    "options": ["steel","disorder","essay"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "transform",
                    "options": ["withdraw","evaluate","incorporate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yara, jarohat",
                    "RightAnswer": "wound",
                    "options": ["cake","steel","disorder"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cheklov",
                    "RightAnswer": "restriction",
                    "options": ["platform","analyst","demonstration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "poydevor",
                    "RightAnswer": "foundation",
                    "options": ["restriction","platform","analyst"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dizayner",
                    "RightAnswer": "designer",
                    "options": ["foundation","restriction","platform"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taranglik, bosim",
                    "RightAnswer": "strain",
                    "options": ["wound","cake","steel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "innovatsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "innovation",
                    "options": ["designer","foundation","restriction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "albom",
                    "RightAnswer": "album",
                    "options": ["innovation","designer","foundation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shiqchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "singer",
                    "options": ["album","innovation","designer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iz",
                    "RightAnswer": "trail",
                    "options": ["strain","wound","cake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuzoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "trap",
                    "options": ["trail","strain","wound"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'sh, tarang emas",
                    "RightAnswer": "loose",
                    "options": ["steady","smart","secure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kengayish, kattalashish",
                    "RightAnswer": "extension",
                    "options": ["singer","album","innovation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boylik",
                    "RightAnswer": "wealth",
                    "options": ["extension","singer","album"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asta-sekin",
                    "RightAnswer": "gradually",
                    "options": ["constantly","rarely","initially"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoqilg'i baki",
                    "RightAnswer": "tank",
                    "options": ["trap","trail","strain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yomon, yovuz",
                    "RightAnswer": "evil",
                    "options": ["everyday","vital","false"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajoyib, e'tiborga molik",
                    "RightAnswer": "remarkable",
                    "options": ["apparent","guilty","external"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ohang",
                    "RightAnswer": "tune",
                    "options": ["tank","trap","trail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o't",
                    "RightAnswer": "grass",
                    "options": ["tune","tank","trap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif, taklifnoma",
                    "RightAnswer": "invitation",
                    "options": ["wealth","extension","singer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'tish",
                    "RightAnswer": "transition",
                    "options": ["grass","tune","tank"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'rqitmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "frighten",
                    "options": ["transform","withdraw","evaluate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taklif",
                    "RightAnswer": "bid",
                    "options": ["scream","scare","sweep"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetishtirmoq, zot",
                    "RightAnswer": "breed",
                    "options": ["bid","scream","scare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noodatiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "extraordinary",
                    "options": ["remarkable","apparent","guilty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajoyib",
                    "RightAnswer": "brilliant",
                    "options": ["extraordinary","remarkable","apparent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maslahatchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "adviser",
                    "options": ["invitation","wealth","extension"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayoq, poya",
                    "RightAnswer": "stem",
                    "options": ["transition","grass","tune"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teskari",
                    "RightAnswer": "reverse",
                    "options": ["upset","hurt","grin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rejim",
                    "RightAnswer": "mode",
                    "options": ["stem","transition","grass"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oyna",
                    "RightAnswer": "mirror",
                    "options": ["mode","stem","transition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dahshatli, juda yomon",
                    "RightAnswer": "awful",
                    "options": ["brilliant","extraordinary","remarkable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "poza, holat",
                    "RightAnswer": "pose",
                    "options": ["breed","bid","scream"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moslashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "adjust",
                    "options": ["frighten","transform","withdraw"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ijodiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "creative",
                    "options": ["awful","brilliant","extraordinary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hozirgi kunda",
                    "RightAnswer": "nowadays",
                    "options": ["aside","forth","meanwhile"]
                }
            ],
            "level 23": [
                {
                    "Question": "she'r",
                    "RightAnswer": "poem",
                    "options": ["adviser","invitation","wealth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qishloq xo'jaligiga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "agricultural",
                    "options": ["creative","awful","brilliant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqobatchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "competitor",
                    "options": ["poem","adviser","invitation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "alkogol",
                    "RightAnswer": "alcohol",
                    "options": ["competitor","poem","adviser"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "festival",
                    "RightAnswer": "festival",
                    "options": ["alcohol","competitor","poem"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sabzavot",
                    "RightAnswer": "vegetable",
                    "options": ["festival","alcohol","competitor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "furgon",
                    "RightAnswer": "van",
                    "options": ["vegetable","festival","alcohol"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dadil, o'ziga ishongan",
                    "RightAnswer": "confident",
                    "options": ["agricultural","creative","awful"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sayyora",
                    "RightAnswer": "planet",
                    "options": ["van","vegetable","festival"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "burilmoq, qayrilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "curve",
                    "options": ["mirror","mode","stem"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tizza",
                    "RightAnswer": "knee",
                    "options": ["planet","van","vegetable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yengib o'tmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "overcome",
                    "options": ["adjust","frighten","transform"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'r",
                    "RightAnswer": "web",
                    "options": ["curve","mirror","mode"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chuqurlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "depth",
                    "options": ["knee","planet","van"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "entrance",
                    "options": ["web","curve","mirror"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yozib bormoq, xoda",
                    "RightAnswer": "log",
                    "options": ["entrance","web","curve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ulkan",
                    "RightAnswer": "giant",
                    "options": ["evil","everyday","vital"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xudo",
                    "RightAnswer": "god",
                    "options": ["depth","knee","planet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qism",
                    "RightAnswer": "portion",
                    "options": ["god","depth","knee"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "modda",
                    "RightAnswer": "substance",
                    "options": ["portion","god","depth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keng",
                    "RightAnswer": "extensive",
                    "options": ["confident","agricultural","creative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "talqin qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "interpret",
                    "options": ["overcome","adjust","frighten"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mustaqillik",
                    "RightAnswer": "independence",
                    "options": ["substance","portion","god"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shakar",
                    "RightAnswer": "sugar",
                    "options": ["independence","substance","portion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ichki",
                    "RightAnswer": "inner",
                    "options": ["giant","evil","everyday"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zarar",
                    "RightAnswer": "harm",
                    "options": ["log","entrance","web"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maslahat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "consult",
                    "options": ["pose","breed","bid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pushti",
                    "RightAnswer": "pink",
                    "options": ["inner","giant","evil"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soya",
                    "RightAnswer": "shadow",
                    "options": ["harm","log","entrance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "lenta",
                    "RightAnswer": "strip",
                    "options": ["consult","pose","breed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "silliq",
                    "RightAnswer": "smooth",
                    "options": ["loose","steady","smart"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aralashuv",
                    "RightAnswer": "intervention",
                    "options": ["sugar","independence","substance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taassurot qoldirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "impress",
                    "options": ["interpret","overcome","adjust"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imtihon",
                    "RightAnswer": "exam",
                    "options": ["intervention","sugar","independence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "illat",
                    "RightAnswer": "vice",
                    "options": ["exam","intervention","sugar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keskin",
                    "RightAnswer": "radical",
                    "options": ["pink","inner","giant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shunga o'xshab, shu tarzda",
                    "RightAnswer": "similarly",
                    "options": ["gradually","constantly","rarely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zini tutmoq, ",
                    "RightAnswer": "behave",
                    "options": ["impress","interpret","overcome"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baland",
                    "RightAnswer": "loud",
                    "options": ["thick","nearby","lucky"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'lcham",
                    "RightAnswer": "dimension",
                    "options": ["vice","exam","intervention"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keyingi",
                    "RightAnswer": "subsequent",
                    "options": ["extensive","confident","agricultural"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "infektsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "infection",
                    "options": ["dimension","vice","exam"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kurtka",
                    "RightAnswer": "jacket",
                    "options": ["infection","dimension","vice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "samaradorlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "efficiency",
                    "options": ["jacket","infection","dimension"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iflos",
                    "RightAnswer": "dirty",
                    "options": ["smooth","loose","steady"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "statistika",
                    "RightAnswer": "statistic",
                    "options": ["efficiency","jacket","infection"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muntazam ravishda",
                    "RightAnswer": "regularly",
                    "options": ["similarly","gradually","constantly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kurort, yechim",
                    "RightAnswer": "resort",
                    "options": ["strip","consult","pose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "temir",
                    "RightAnswer": "iron",
                    "options": ["shadow","harm","log"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "efirga uzatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "broadcast",
                    "options": ["resort","strip","consult"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "a'zolik",
                    "RightAnswer": "membership",
                    "options": ["statistic","efficiency","jacket"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "non",
                    "RightAnswer": "bread",
                    "options": ["membership","statistic","efficiency"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'zi ojiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "blind",
                    "options": ["spare","wet","calm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sof",
                    "RightAnswer": "pure",
                    "options": ["subsequent","extensive","confident"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qonli",
                    "RightAnswer": "bloody",
                    "options": ["loud","thick","nearby"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ittifoqchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "ally",
                    "options": ["iron","shadow","harm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "miqdor",
                    "RightAnswer": "quantity",
                    "options": ["bread","membership","statistic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bend",
                    "options": ["broadcast","resort","strip"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pishgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "mature",
                    "options": ["alter","elect","express"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qisqacha",
                    "RightAnswer": "briefly",
                    "options": ["regularly","similarly","gradually"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "signal, ogohlantirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "alarm",
                    "options": ["ally","iron","shadow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bezovta qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "disturb",
                    "options": ["behave","impress","interpret"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saqlab turmoq, ",
                    "RightAnswer": "sustain",
                    "options": ["disturb","behave","impress"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "toshqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "flood",
                    "options": ["alarm","ally","iron"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kambag'allik",
                    "RightAnswer": "poverty",
                    "options": ["quantity","bread","membership"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aqldan ozgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "crazy",
                    "options": ["pure","subsequent","extensive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iqtibos keltirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cite",
                    "options": ["sustain","disturb","behave"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yangicha",
                    "RightAnswer": "newly",
                    "options": ["briefly","regularly","similarly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "parallel",
                    "RightAnswer": "parallel",
                    "options": ["solid","slight","prime"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jins",
                    "RightAnswer": "gender",
                    "options": ["poverty","quantity","bread"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "homiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "sponsor",
                    "options": ["flood","alarm","ally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "etik",
                    "RightAnswer": "boots",
                    "options": ["sponsor","flood","alarm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq",
                    "RightAnswer": "accurate",
                    "options": ["crazy","pure","subsequent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sotuvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "dealer",
                    "options": ["gender","poverty","quantity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tugma",
                    "RightAnswer": "button",
                    "options": ["boots","sponsor","flood"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yuk",
                    "RightAnswer": "burden",
                    "options": ["button","boots","sponsor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cho'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "desert",
                    "options": ["burden","button","boots"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sherik, oshno",
                    "RightAnswer": "mate",
                    "options": ["bend","broadcast","resort"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ba'zida",
                    "RightAnswer": "occasionally",
                    "options": ["newly","briefly","regularly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aktsiyador",
                    "RightAnswer": "shareholder",
                    "options": ["dealer","gender","poverty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kosa",
                    "RightAnswer": "bowl",
                    "options": ["desert","burden","button"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kashfiyot",
                    "RightAnswer": "discovery",
                    "options": ["shareholder","dealer","gender"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarshilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "resistance",
                    "options": ["discovery","shareholder","dealer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vanna",
                    "RightAnswer": "bath",
                    "options": ["bowl","desert","burden"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chastota",
                    "RightAnswer": "frequency",
                    "options": ["resistance","discovery","shareholder"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanqid qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "criticize",
                    "options": ["cite","sustain","disturb"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jumrak, tappilatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "tap",
                    "options": ["mate","bend","broadcast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "falsafa",
                    "RightAnswer": "philosophy",
                    "options": ["frequency","resistance","discovery"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "lab",
                    "RightAnswer": "lip",
                    "options": ["philosophy","frequency","resistance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xususiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "attribute",
                    "options": ["tap","mate","bend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzr so'ramoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "apologize",
                    "options": ["criticize","cite","sustain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasdiqlash",
                    "RightAnswer": "approval",
                    "options": ["lip","philosophy","frequency"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ushlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "grab",
                    "options": ["attribute","tap","mate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ruxsat bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "entitle",
                    "options": ["apologize","criticize","cite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarz bermoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "lend",
                    "options": ["entitle","apologize","criticize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishtirok",
                    "RightAnswer": "involvement",
                    "options": ["approval","lip","philosophy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "namoyish",
                    "RightAnswer": "exposure",
                    "options": ["involvement","approval","lip"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "an'anaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "conventional",
                    "options": ["accurate","crazy","pure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqamli",
                    "RightAnswer": "digital",
                    "options": ["conventional","accurate","crazy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarjima qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "translate",
                    "options": ["lend","entitle","apologize"]
                }
            ],
            "level 24": [
                {
                    "Question": "tahrir qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "edit",
                    "options": ["grab","attribute","tap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shakllanish",
                    "RightAnswer": "formation",
                    "options": ["exposure","involvement","approval"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "omonat",
                    "RightAnswer": "deposit",
                    "options": ["edit","grab","attribute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yoqimli",
                    "RightAnswer": "pleasant",
                    "options": ["digital","conventional","accurate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chet el",
                    "RightAnswer": "overseas",
                    "options": ["bloody","loud","thick"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarafdor",
                    "RightAnswer": "advocate",
                    "options": ["deposit","edit","grab"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muassasa",
                    "RightAnswer": "establishment",
                    "options": ["formation","exposure","involvement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xulosa",
                    "RightAnswer": "summary",
                    "options": ["establishment","formation","exposure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiyin, dag'al, qo'pol",
                    "RightAnswer": "rough",
                    "options": ["soft","fair","rare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ruchka",
                    "RightAnswer": "pen",
                    "options": ["bath","bowl","desert"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tiklanish, tuzalish",
                    "RightAnswer": "recovery",
                    "options": ["summary","establishment","formation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mahkamlamoq, muhr",
                    "RightAnswer": "seal",
                    "options": ["advocate","deposit","edit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "truba",
                    "RightAnswer": "tube",
                    "options": ["recovery","summary","establishment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "minora",
                    "RightAnswer": "tower",
                    "options": ["tube","recovery","summary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ta'riflamoq, ifodalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "characterize",
                    "options": ["translate","lend","entitle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq ko‘rsatmoq, batafsil tushuntirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "specify",
                    "options": ["characterize","translate","lend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exact",
                    "options": ["dirty","smooth","loose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aylantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "spin",
                    "options": ["seal","advocate","deposit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshqaruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "operator",
                    "options": ["tower","tube","recovery"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chaqaloq",
                    "RightAnswer": "infant",
                    "options": ["operator","tower","tube"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qazimoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "dig",
                    "options": ["spin","seal","advocate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tortmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "drag",
                    "options": ["dig","spin","seal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rnatmoq, chiqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "mount",
                    "options": ["drag","dig","spin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'ramoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wrap",
                    "options": ["mount","drag","dig"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kutmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "anticipate",
                    "options": ["specify","characterize","translate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qaram",
                    "RightAnswer": "dependent",
                    "options": ["radical","pink","inner"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ixtisoslashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "specialize",
                    "options": ["anticipate","specify","characterize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "burchak",
                    "RightAnswer": "angle",
                    "options": ["pen","bath","bowl"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tovuq",
                    "RightAnswer": "chicken",
                    "options": ["infant","operator","tower"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashvish, qo'rquv",
                    "RightAnswer": "anxiety",
                    "options": ["chicken","infant","operator"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "virus",
                    "RightAnswer": "virus",
                    "options": ["anxiety","chicken","infant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq",
                    "RightAnswer": "precisely",
                    "options": ["occasionally","newly","briefly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqib",
                    "RightAnswer": "rival",
                    "options": ["angle","pen","bath"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jinoyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "offense",
                    "options": ["virus","anxiety","chicken"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "detect",
                    "options": ["specialize","anticipate","specify"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'smir",
                    "RightAnswer": "teenager",
                    "options": ["offense","virus","anxiety"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hurmat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "admire",
                    "options": ["detect","specialize","anticipate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rtacha",
                    "RightAnswer": "moderate",
                    "options": ["mature","alter","elect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jarrohlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "surgery",
                    "options": ["teenager","offense","virus"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "musiqachi",
                    "RightAnswer": "musician",
                    "options": ["surgery","teenager","offense"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ahamiyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "significance",
                    "options": ["musician","surgery","teenager"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dush",
                    "RightAnswer": "shower",
                    "options": ["rival","angle","pen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noqonuniy",
                    "RightAnswer": "illegal",
                    "options": ["pleasant","digital","conventional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xayriya",
                    "RightAnswer": "charity",
                    "options": ["significance","musician","surgery"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "universal",
                    "RightAnswer": "universal",
                    "options": ["dependent","radical","pink"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sigaret",
                    "RightAnswer": "cigarette",
                    "options": ["charity","significance","musician"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashkil etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "constitute",
                    "options": ["admire","detect","specialize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yetarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "adequate",
                    "options": ["illegal","pleasant","digital"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maslahatchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "consultant",
                    "options": ["cigarette","charity","significance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarixchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "historian",
                    "options": ["consultant","cigarette","charity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "amaki/tog'a/amma/xolavachcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "cousin",
                    "options": ["historian","consultant","cigarette"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rish bilan bog'liq",
                    "RightAnswer": "visual",
                    "options": ["universal","dependent","radical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ahmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stupid",
                    "options": ["adequate","illegal","pleasant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishtiyoqmand",
                    "RightAnswer": "keen",
                    "options": ["exact","dirty","smooth"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "etnik",
                    "RightAnswer": "ethnic",
                    "options": ["stupid","adequate","illegal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egizak",
                    "RightAnswer": "twin",
                    "options": ["routine","equivalent","retail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "klinik",
                    "RightAnswer": "clinical",
                    "options": ["ethnic","stupid","adequate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sharqiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "eastern",
                    "options": ["western","sudden","upper"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bashorat",
                    "RightAnswer": "forecast",
                    "options": ["wrap","mount","drag"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'lim",
                    "RightAnswer": "segment",
                    "options": ["shower","rival","angle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "odat",
                    "RightAnswer": "custom",
                    "options": ["twin","routine","equivalent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moslashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "adapt",
                    "options": ["constitute","admire","detect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qum",
                    "RightAnswer": "sand",
                    "options": ["segment","shower","rival"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qalpoq, kepka",
                    "RightAnswer": "cap",
                    "options": ["sand","segment","shower"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tezkor",
                    "RightAnswer": "prompt",
                    "options": ["reverse","upset","hurt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joziba",
                    "RightAnswer": "charm",
                    "options": ["cap","sand","segment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "reaksiyaga kirishmoq, javob qaytarmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "react",
                    "options": ["adapt","constitute","admire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ma'ruza",
                    "RightAnswer": "lecture",
                    "options": ["charm","cap","sand"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tavakkal qilmoq, sarguzasht",
                    "RightAnswer": "venture",
                    "options": ["forecast","wrap","mount"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "murakkab",
                    "RightAnswer": "compound",
                    "options": ["fat","stone","mass"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qutqarmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rescue",
                    "options": ["venture","forecast","wrap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tartibsizlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "mess",
                    "options": ["rescue","venture","forecast"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "afzal ko'rish",
                    "RightAnswer": "preference",
                    "options": ["cousin","historian","consultant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keng qamrovli",
                    "RightAnswer": "comprehensive",
                    "options": ["clinical","ethnic","stupid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rag'batlantirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "incentive",
                    "options": ["preference","cousin","historian"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "liga, turnir",
                    "RightAnswer": "league",
                    "options": ["incentive","preference","cousin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dialog, suhbat",
                    "RightAnswer": "dialog",
                    "options": ["lecture","charm","cap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "krem",
                    "RightAnswer": "cream",
                    "options": ["dialog","lecture","charm"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tez",
                    "RightAnswer": "rapid",
                    "options": ["visual","universal","dependent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bekor qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cancel",
                    "options": ["react","adapt","constitute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "afsuslanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "regret",
                    "options": ["mess","rescue","venture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishdan bo'shatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "dismiss",
                    "options": ["cancel","react","adapt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chegara",
                    "RightAnswer": "margin",
                    "options": ["league","incentive","preference"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ostida",
                    "RightAnswer": "beneath",
                    "options": ["beside","besides","throughout"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "raqib",
                    "RightAnswer": "opponent",
                    "options": ["margin","league","incentive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarshilik qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "resist",
                    "options": ["dismiss","cancel","react"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qobiliyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "capability",
                    "options": ["opponent","margin","league"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mutlaq",
                    "RightAnswer": "absolute",
                    "options": ["rapid","visual","universal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mos kelmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "correspond",
                    "options": ["resist","dismiss","cancel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "insult",
                    "RightAnswer": "stroke",
                    "options": ["regret","mess","rescue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jasorat qilmoq, haddi sig'moq",
                    "RightAnswer": "dare",
                    "options": ["stroke","regret","mess"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'siq",
                    "RightAnswer": "barrier",
                    "options": ["capability","opponent","margin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tozalamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "rid",
                    "options": ["correspond","resist","dismiss"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajralish",
                    "RightAnswer": "divorce",
                    "options": ["cream","dialog","lecture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vayron qilmoq, vayrona",
                    "RightAnswer": "ruin",
                    "options": ["divorce","cream","dialog"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dafn qilmoq, ko'mmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bury",
                    "options": ["rid","correspond","resist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maslahat",
                    "RightAnswer": "counsel",
                    "options": ["ruin","divorce","cream"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tendensiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "tendency",
                    "options": ["barrier","capability","opponent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tez-tez",
                    "RightAnswer": "frequent",
                    "options": ["keen","exact","dirty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dvigatel",
                    "RightAnswer": "motor",
                    "options": ["custom","twin","routine"]
                }
            ],
            "level 25": [
                {
                    "Question": "omon qolish",
                    "RightAnswer": "survival",
                    "options": ["tendency","barrier","capability"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarshi",
                    "RightAnswer": "counter",
                    "options": ["counsel","ruin","divorce"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egallamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "possess",
                    "options": ["bury","rid","correspond"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ruxsat",
                    "RightAnswer": "permission",
                    "options": ["survival","tendency","barrier"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vodiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "valley",
                    "options": ["permission","survival","tendency"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suzmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "float",
                    "options": ["dare","stroke","regret"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aqldan ozgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "mad",
                    "options": ["overseas","bloody","loud"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "juda",
                    "RightAnswer": "greatly",
                    "options": ["precisely","occasionally","newly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rinadigan",
                    "RightAnswer": "visible",
                    "options": ["comprehensive","clinical","ethnic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "elektr",
                    "RightAnswer": "electric",
                    "options": ["absolute","rapid","visual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taassurot qoldiruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "impressive",
                    "options": ["visible","comprehensive","clinical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rivojlanish, takomillashish",
                    "RightAnswer": "evolution",
                    "options": ["valley","permission","survival"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xabardorlik, ogohlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "awareness",
                    "options": ["evolution","valley","permission"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zo'ravon",
                    "RightAnswer": "violent",
                    "options": ["impressive","visible","comprehensive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qul",
                    "RightAnswer": "slave",
                    "options": ["awareness","evolution","valley"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boy",
                    "RightAnswer": "wealthy",
                    "options": ["violent","impressive","visible"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "arxitektura",
                    "RightAnswer": "architecture",
                    "options": ["slave","awareness","evolution"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to‘g‘ri keladigan, ma'qul",
                    "RightAnswer": "acceptable",
                    "options": ["wealthy","violent","impressive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jurnal",
                    "RightAnswer": "journal",
                    "options": ["architecture","slave","awareness"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'mir",
                    "RightAnswer": "coal",
                    "options": ["journal","architecture","slave"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'lchov",
                    "RightAnswer": "measurement",
                    "options": ["coal","journal","architecture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasodifiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "random",
                    "options": ["electric","absolute","rapid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muvaffaqiyatli",
                    "RightAnswer": "successfully",
                    "options": ["greatly","precisely","occasionally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushkunlikka solmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "depress",
                    "options": ["possess","bury","rid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasvir",
                    "RightAnswer": "illustration",
                    "options": ["measurement","coal","journal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "portlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "burst",
                    "options": ["float","dare","stroke"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "afzallik, ustunlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "privilege",
                    "options": ["counter","counsel","ruin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xaridor",
                    "RightAnswer": "buyer",
                    "options": ["illustration","measurement","coal"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zaro",
                    "RightAnswer": "mutual",
                    "options": ["random","electric","absolute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "temir yo'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "rail",
                    "options": ["privilege","counter","counsel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rag'batlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "motivate",
                    "options": ["depress","possess","bury"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "laboratoriya",
                    "RightAnswer": "laboratory",
                    "options": ["buyer","illustration","measurement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ipoteka",
                    "RightAnswer": "mortgage",
                    "options": ["rail","privilege","counter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'tarilish",
                    "RightAnswer": "promotion",
                    "options": ["laboratory","buyer","illustration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishtiyoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "passion",
                    "options": ["promotion","laboratory","buyer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chempion",
                    "RightAnswer": "champion",
                    "options": ["mortgage","rail","privilege"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bajarmoq, amalga oshirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fulfill",
                    "options": ["motivate","depress","possess"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chang",
                    "RightAnswer": "dust",
                    "options": ["burst","float","dare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bag'ishlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "dedicate",
                    "options": ["fulfill","motivate","depress"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxminan",
                    "RightAnswer": "roughly",
                    "options": ["successfully","greatly","precisely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yubka",
                    "RightAnswer": "skirt",
                    "options": ["dust","burst","float"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "viloyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "province",
                    "options": ["passion","promotion","laboratory"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yurish",
                    "RightAnswer": "march",
                    "options": ["champion","mortgage","rail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baholash",
                    "RightAnswer": "evaluation",
                    "options": ["province","passion","promotion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kompromis",
                    "RightAnswer": "compromise",
                    "options": ["march","champion","mortgage"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uddalamoq, amalga oshirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "accomplish",
                    "options": ["dedicate","fulfill","motivate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zaiflik",
                    "RightAnswer": "weakness",
                    "options": ["evaluation","province","passion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'lon",
                    "RightAnswer": "announcement",
                    "options": ["weakness","evaluation","province"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuz",
                    "RightAnswer": "salt",
                    "options": ["compromise","march","champion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarash",
                    "RightAnswer": "glance",
                    "options": ["skirt","dust","burst"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "opera",
                    "RightAnswer": "opera",
                    "options": ["announcement","weakness","evaluation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "musobaqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "contest",
                    "options": ["salt","compromise","march"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cho'tka",
                    "RightAnswer": "brush",
                    "options": ["glance","skirt","dust"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uyaltirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "embarrass",
                    "options": ["accomplish","dedicate","fulfill"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "galereya",
                    "RightAnswer": "gallery",
                    "options": ["opera","announcement","weakness"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "genetik",
                    "RightAnswer": "genetic",
                    "options": ["acceptable","wealthy","violent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "agressiv",
                    "RightAnswer": "aggressive",
                    "options": ["genetic","acceptable","wealthy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'krak qafasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "chest",
                    "options": ["gallery","opera","announcement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "format, shakl",
                    "RightAnswer": "format",
                    "options": ["contest","salt","compromise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "adabiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "literary",
                    "options": ["aggressive","genetic","acceptable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hukmronlik qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "govern",
                    "options": ["embarrass","accomplish","dedicate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qabul qilmoq, quchoqlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "embrace",
                    "options": ["govern","embarrass","accomplish"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqtamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "praise",
                    "options": ["brush","glance","skirt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jim, tinch",
                    "RightAnswer": "silent",
                    "options": ["literary","aggressive","genetic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nasos",
                    "RightAnswer": "pump",
                    "options": ["praise","brush","glance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nashriyotchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "publisher",
                    "options": ["chest","gallery","opera"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bayram",
                    "RightAnswer": "celebration",
                    "options": ["publisher","chest","gallery"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "golf",
                    "RightAnswer": "golf",
                    "options": ["celebration","publisher","chest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kompensatsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "compensation",
                    "options": ["golf","celebration","publisher"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "klassik",
                    "RightAnswer": "classical",
                    "options": ["silent","literary","aggressive"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "og'irlikni o'lchamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "weigh",
                    "options": ["embrace","govern","embarrass"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarshi",
                    "RightAnswer": "versus",
                    "options": ["to","till","except"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "deficit",
                    "options": ["compensation","golf","celebration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'zgartirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "modify",
                    "options": ["weigh","embrace","govern"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chaqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "flash",
                    "options": ["pump","praise","brush"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "do'stlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "friendship",
                    "options": ["deficit","compensation","golf"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kasb",
                    "RightAnswer": "profession",
                    "options": ["friendship","deficit","compensation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqatdan",
                    "RightAnswer": "literally",
                    "options": ["roughly","successfully","greatly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tenglama",
                    "RightAnswer": "equation",
                    "options": ["profession","friendship","deficit"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imo-ishora",
                    "RightAnswer": "gesture",
                    "options": ["flash","pump","praise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kayfiyatini ko'tarmoq, zavqlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "entertain",
                    "options": ["modify","weigh","embrace"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajoyib",
                    "RightAnswer": "fantastic",
                    "options": ["classical","silent","literary"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tayinlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "assign",
                    "options": ["entertain","modify","weigh"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "inflyatsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "inflation",
                    "options": ["equation","profession","friendship"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarixiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "historic",
                    "options": ["mutual","random","electric"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jarohat yetkazmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "injure",
                    "options": ["assign","entertain","modify"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "masofaviy",
                    "RightAnswer": "remote",
                    "options": ["historic","mutual","random"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "terapiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "therapy",
                    "options": ["inflation","equation","profession"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "apelsin",
                    "RightAnswer": "orange",
                    "options": ["motor","custom","twin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "burmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "twist",
                    "options": ["gesture","flash","pump"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xodimlar",
                    "RightAnswer": "personnel",
                    "options": ["therapy","inflation","equation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tasavvur",
                    "RightAnswer": "imagination",
                    "options": ["personnel","therapy","inflation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rozilik bermaslik",
                    "RightAnswer": "disagree",
                    "options": ["injure","assign","entertain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tomoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "throat",
                    "options": ["imagination","personnel","therapy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tushuncha",
                    "RightAnswer": "insight",
                    "options": ["throat","imagination","personnel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hal qilish",
                    "RightAnswer": "tackle",
                    "options": ["twist","gesture","flash"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "abadiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "forever",
                    "options": ["literally","roughly","successfully"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oshmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exceed",
                    "options": ["disagree","injure","assign"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xarajat",
                    "RightAnswer": "expenditure",
                    "options": ["insight","throat","imagination"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "quvonch",
                    "RightAnswer": "joy",
                    "options": ["expenditure","insight","throat"]
                }
            ],
            "level 26": [
                {
                    "Question": "homilador",
                    "RightAnswer": "pregnant",
                    "options": ["fantastic","classical","silent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishonchli",
                    "RightAnswer": "reliable",
                    "options": ["pregnant","fantastic","classical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jihoz",
                    "RightAnswer": "gear",
                    "options": ["format","contest","salt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bosmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "click",
                    "options": ["tackle","twist","gesture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shoir",
                    "RightAnswer": "poet",
                    "options": ["joy","expenditure","insight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boylik",
                    "RightAnswer": "fortune",
                    "options": ["poet","joy","expenditure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "marosim",
                    "RightAnswer": "ceremony",
                    "options": ["fortune","poet","joy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ustma-ust turgan, to'plam  ",
                    "RightAnswer": "pile",
                    "options": ["gear","format","contest"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cho'chqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "pig",
                    "options": ["pile","gear","format"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aralashma",
                    "RightAnswer": "mixture",
                    "options": ["ceremony","fortune","poet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "avtomatik tarzda",
                    "RightAnswer": "automatically",
                    "options": ["forever","literally","roughly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olim",
                    "RightAnswer": "scholar",
                    "options": ["mixture","ceremony","fortune"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "psixologik",
                    "RightAnswer": "psychological",
                    "options": ["reliable","pregnant","fantastic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dramatik tarzda",
                    "RightAnswer": "dramatically",
                    "options": ["automatically","forever","literally"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ulush, qoziq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stake",
                    "options": ["pig","pile","gear"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jonzot",
                    "RightAnswer": "creature",
                    "options": ["scholar","mixture","ceremony"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamkorlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "partnership",
                    "options": ["creature","scholar","mixture"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishtirok",
                    "RightAnswer": "participation",
                    "options": ["partnership","creature","scholar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "band, bob",
                    "RightAnswer": "clause",
                    "options": ["participation","partnership","creature"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jazo",
                    "RightAnswer": "penalty",
                    "options": ["clause","participation","partnership"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xonadon",
                    "RightAnswer": "chamber",
                    "options": ["penalty","clause","participation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hashamatli",
                    "RightAnswer": "fancy",
                    "options": ["remote","historic","mutual"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "she'riyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "poetry",
                    "options": ["chamber","penalty","clause"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suhbat",
                    "RightAnswer": "chat",
                    "options": ["click","tackle","twist"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kiyim-kechak",
                    "RightAnswer": "clothing",
                    "options": ["poetry","chamber","penalty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rivojlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "evolve",
                    "options": ["exceed","disagree","injure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "maqsadida, uchun",
                    "RightAnswer": "sake",
                    "options": ["clothing","poetry","chamber"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tokcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "shelf",
                    "options": ["stake","pig","pile"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuchaytirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "boost",
                    "options": ["chat","click","tackle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dum",
                    "RightAnswer": "tail",
                    "options": ["shelf","stake","pig"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "possession",
                    "options": ["sake","clothing","poetry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bola oldirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "abortion",
                    "options": ["possession","sake","clothing"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiziqqon, qiziquvchan",
                    "RightAnswer": "curious",
                    "options": ["psychological","reliable","pregnant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yog'ochdan yasalgan",
                    "RightAnswer": "wooden",
                    "options": ["curious","psychological","reliable"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'sish",
                    "RightAnswer": "boom",
                    "options": ["boost","chat","click"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hikoya",
                    "RightAnswer": "tale",
                    "options": ["tail","shelf","stake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "demokratik",
                    "RightAnswer": "democratic",
                    "options": ["wooden","curious","psychological"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "texnik xizmat",
                    "RightAnswer": "maintenance",
                    "options": ["abortion","possession","sake"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "natijada",
                    "RightAnswer": "consequently",
                    "options": ["dramatically","automatically","forever"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "idish",
                    "RightAnswer": "pot",
                    "options": ["tale","tail","shelf"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mol",
                    "RightAnswer": "cow",
                    "options": ["pot","tale","tail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mustahkamlash",
                    "RightAnswer": "strengthen",
                    "options": ["evolve","exceed","disagree"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bir vaqtning o'zida",
                    "RightAnswer": "whilst",
                    "options": ["whenever","nevertheless","therefore"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cheklov",
                    "RightAnswer": "constraint",
                    "options": ["maintenance","abortion","possession"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bukmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fold",
                    "options": ["boom","boost","chat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "quti",
                    "RightAnswer": "bin",
                    "options": ["cow","pot","tale"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshdan kechirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "undergo",
                    "options": ["strengthen","evolve","exceed"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtimoliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "potentially",
                    "options": ["consequently","dramatically","automatically"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "doira, ko'lam",
                    "RightAnswer": "scope",
                    "options": ["bin","cow","pot"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soxta qilish",
                    "RightAnswer": "pretend",
                    "options": ["undergo","strengthen","evolve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xilma-xillik",
                    "RightAnswer": "diversity",
                    "options": ["constraint","maintenance","abortion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "da'vo qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "allege",
                    "options": ["pretend","undergo","strengthen"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faxr",
                    "RightAnswer": "pride",
                    "options": ["diversity","constraint","maintenance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuchli",
                    "RightAnswer": "intense",
                    "options": ["democratic","wooden","curious"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'rov",
                    "RightAnswer": "inquiry",
                    "options": ["pride","diversity","constraint"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishdan ketmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "resign",
                    "options": ["allege","pretend","undergo"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hunarmandchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "craft",
                    "options": ["fold","boom","boost"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qat'iy",
                    "RightAnswer": "strict",
                    "options": ["intense","democratic","wooden"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "beton",
                    "RightAnswer": "concrete",
                    "options": ["parallel","solid","slight"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qobiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "shell",
                    "options": ["scope","bin","cow"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "la'nat",
                    "RightAnswer": "damn",
                    "options": ["prompt","reverse","upset"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ajralib turuvchi, alohida",
                    "RightAnswer": "distinct",
                    "options": ["strict","intense","democratic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hazil",
                    "RightAnswer": "humor",
                    "options": ["inquiry","pride","diversity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "cheklov",
                    "RightAnswer": "limitation",
                    "options": ["humor","inquiry","pride"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rsatkich",
                    "RightAnswer": "indication",
                    "options": ["limitation","humor","inquiry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "barqarorlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "stability",
                    "options": ["indication","limitation","humor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dono",
                    "RightAnswer": "wise",
                    "options": ["eastern","western","sudden"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'tiborsizlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "neglect",
                    "options": ["craft","fold","boom"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaratmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "compose",
                    "options": ["resign","allege","pretend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qamoqxona",
                    "RightAnswer": "jail",
                    "options": ["shell","scope","bin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "boshpana",
                    "RightAnswer": "shelter",
                    "options": ["neglect","craft","fold"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "faqatgina",
                    "RightAnswer": "mere",
                    "options": ["fancy","remote","historic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uglerod",
                    "RightAnswer": "carbon",
                    "options": ["stability","indication","limitation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tartibga solmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "regulate",
                    "options": ["compose","resign","allege"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pishloq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cheese",
                    "options": ["carbon","stability","indication"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tepki",
                    "RightAnswer": "trigger",
                    "options": ["shelter","neglect","craft"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nay, truba",
                    "RightAnswer": "pipe",
                    "options": ["jail","shell","scope"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "vayronagarchilik",
                    "RightAnswer": "destruction",
                    "options": ["cheese","carbon","stability"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gitara",
                    "RightAnswer": "guitar",
                    "options": ["destruction","cheese","carbon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bayroq",
                    "RightAnswer": "flag",
                    "options": ["pipe","jail","shell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pianino",
                    "RightAnswer": "piano",
                    "options": ["guitar","destruction","cheese"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sehr",
                    "RightAnswer": "magic",
                    "options": ["orange","motor","custom"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sir, sinoat",
                    "RightAnswer": "mystery",
                    "options": ["piano","guitar","destruction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chang'i",
                    "RightAnswer": "ski",
                    "options": ["trigger","shelter","neglect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pichirlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "whisper",
                    "options": ["ski","trigger","shelter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "orqa",
                    "RightAnswer": "rear",
                    "options": ["lean","shut","suspect"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "menyu",
                    "RightAnswer": "menu",
                    "options": ["mystery","piano","guitar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tur",
                    "RightAnswer": "species",
                    "options": ["menu","mystery","piano"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oy",
                    "RightAnswer": "moon",
                    "options": ["flag","pipe","jail"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "taxminan",
                    "RightAnswer": "presumably",
                    "options": ["potentially","consequently","dramatically"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "duo qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bless",
                    "options": ["regulate","compose","resign"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aviakompaniya",
                    "RightAnswer": "airline",
                    "options": ["species","menu","mystery"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tuzatish",
                    "RightAnswer": "amendment",
                    "options": ["airline","species","menu"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "buvi",
                    "RightAnswer": "grandmother",
                    "options": ["amendment","airline","species"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hakamlar hay'ati",
                    "RightAnswer": "jury",
                    "options": ["grandmother","amendment","airline"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hamkorlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "cooperation",
                    "options": ["jury","grandmother","amendment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fuqaro",
                    "RightAnswer": "civilian",
                    "options": ["mere","fancy","remote"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarkib",
                    "RightAnswer": "composition",
                    "options": ["cooperation","jury","grandmother"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tanga",
                    "RightAnswer": "coin",
                    "options": ["moon","flag","pipe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "e'tiborsiz, ga qaramasdan",
                    "RightAnswer": "regardless",
                    "options": ["beneath","beside","besides"]
                }
            ],
            "level 27": [
                {
                    "Question": "tekshirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "scan",
                    "options": ["whisper","ski","trigger"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "guruh",
                    "RightAnswer": "bunch",
                    "options": ["coin","moon","flag"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "irqiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "racial",
                    "options": ["civilian","mere","fancy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "salomlashmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "greet",
                    "options": ["bless","regulate","compose"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "umid qilgan holda",
                    "RightAnswer": "hopefully",
                    "options": ["presumably","potentially","consequently"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jazo, sanktsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "sanction",
                    "options": ["scan","whisper","ski"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hiyla",
                    "RightAnswer": "trick",
                    "options": ["sanction","scan","whisper"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "paragraf",
                    "RightAnswer": "paragraph",
                    "options": ["composition","cooperation","jury"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishlab chiqaruvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "maker",
                    "options": ["paragraph","composition","cooperation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shokolad",
                    "RightAnswer": "chocolate",
                    "options": ["maker","paragraph","composition"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rag'batlantirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stimulate",
                    "options": ["greet","bless","regulate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kamar",
                    "RightAnswer": "belt",
                    "options": ["bunch","coin","moon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kartoshka",
                    "RightAnswer": "potato",
                    "options": ["chocolate","maker","paragraph"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hikoya",
                    "RightAnswer": "narrative",
                    "options": ["potato","chocolate","maker"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'qima",
                    "RightAnswer": "tissue",
                    "options": ["narrative","potato","chocolate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bazo'r",
                    "RightAnswer": "barely",
                    "options": ["hopefully","presumably","potentially"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ixtiro qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "invent",
                    "options": ["stimulate","greet","bless"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "turizm",
                    "RightAnswer": "tourism",
                    "options": ["tissue","narrative","potato"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "professional",
                    "RightAnswer": "pro",
                    "options": ["magic","orange","motor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zinapoya",
                    "RightAnswer": "stair",
                    "options": ["tourism","tissue","narrative"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ikkilanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hesitate",
                    "options": ["invent","stimulate","greet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "porlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "shine",
                    "options": ["trick","sanction","scan"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "rag'bat",
                    "RightAnswer": "motivation",
                    "options": ["stair","tourism","tissue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qat'iy",
                    "RightAnswer": "firmly",
                    "options": ["barely","hopefully","presumably"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ichki",
                    "RightAnswer": "interior",
                    "options": ["racial","civilian","mere"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oshqozon",
                    "RightAnswer": "stomach",
                    "options": ["motivation","stair","tourism"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hech qayerda",
                    "RightAnswer": "nowhere",
                    "options": ["anymore","anywhere","there"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ibodat qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "pray",
                    "options": ["hesitate","invent","stimulate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chempionlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "championship",
                    "options": ["stomach","motivation","stair"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xizmatkor",
                    "RightAnswer": "servant",
                    "options": ["championship","stomach","motivation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "immigrant",
                    "RightAnswer": "immigrant",
                    "options": ["servant","championship","stomach"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ortiqcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "excess",
                    "options": ["pro","magic","orange"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "murakkablik",
                    "RightAnswer": "complexity",
                    "options": ["immigrant","servant","championship"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "javobgarlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "liability",
                    "options": ["complexity","immigrant","servant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayratlanarli",
                    "RightAnswer": "surprisingly",
                    "options": ["firmly","barely","hopefully"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiqarib olish",
                    "RightAnswer": "extract",
                    "options": ["shine","trick","sanction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "amalga oshirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "implementation",
                    "options": ["liability","complexity","immigrant"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tarafkashlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "bias",
                    "options": ["belt","bunch","coin"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "farqli tarzda",
                    "RightAnswer": "differently",
                    "options": ["surprisingly","firmly","barely"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "katalog",
                    "RightAnswer": "catalog",
                    "options": ["bias","belt","bunch"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uzluksiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "continuous",
                    "options": ["distinct","strict","intense"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oltin",
                    "RightAnswer": "golden",
                    "options": ["continuous","distinct","strict"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pochta markasi",
                    "RightAnswer": "stamp",
                    "options": ["extract","shine","trick"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'rsatma",
                    "RightAnswer": "guideline",
                    "options": ["implementation","liability","complexity"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "konvert",
                    "RightAnswer": "envelope",
                    "options": ["guideline","implementation","liability"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "pichoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "knife",
                    "options": ["catalog","bias","belt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "biologik",
                    "RightAnswer": "biological",
                    "options": ["golden","continuous","distinct"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "iste'mol qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "consume",
                    "options": ["pray","hesitate","invent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hashamat",
                    "RightAnswer": "luxury",
                    "options": ["envelope","guideline","implementation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haftalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "weekly",
                    "options": ["mad","overseas","bloody"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qayerda bo'lmasin",
                    "RightAnswer": "wherever",
                    "options": ["nowhere","anymore","anywhere"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tishlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bite",
                    "options": ["stamp","extract","shine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "printer",
                    "RightAnswer": "printer",
                    "options": ["luxury","envelope","guideline"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birinchi navbatda",
                    "RightAnswer": "firstly",
                    "options": ["differently","surprisingly","firmly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashvishli",
                    "RightAnswer": "anxious",
                    "options": ["biological","golden","continuous"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sarguzasht",
                    "RightAnswer": "adventure",
                    "options": ["printer","luxury","envelope"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'siq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fence",
                    "options": ["bite","stamp","extract"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chiqarib yubormoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "exhaust",
                    "options": ["fence","bite","stamp"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joziba",
                    "RightAnswer": "attraction",
                    "options": ["adventure","printer","luxury"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "okean",
                    "RightAnswer": "ocean",
                    "options": ["attraction","adventure","printer"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jimjit",
                    "RightAnswer": "quietly",
                    "options": ["firstly","differently","surprisingly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qal'a",
                    "RightAnswer": "castle",
                    "options": ["ocean","attraction","adventure"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'p yillik tajribaga ega",
                    "RightAnswer": "veteran",
                    "options": ["castle","ocean","attraction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aks ettirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "reflection",
                    "options": ["veteran","castle","ocean"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asab",
                    "RightAnswer": "nerve",
                    "options": ["reflection","veteran","castle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qat'iyat",
                    "RightAnswer": "determination",
                    "options": ["nerve","reflection","veteran"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "jami",
                    "RightAnswer": "altogether",
                    "options": ["quietly","firstly","differently"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "adabiy asar",
                    "RightAnswer": "fiction",
                    "options": ["determination","nerve","reflection"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gilam",
                    "RightAnswer": "carpet",
                    "options": ["knife","catalog","bias"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'plam",
                    "RightAnswer": "cluster",
                    "options": ["carpet","knife","catalog"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chalkashlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "confusion",
                    "options": ["fiction","determination","nerve"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shoshilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "hurry",
                    "options": ["exhaust","fence","bite"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mantiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "logic",
                    "options": ["confusion","fiction","determination"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bahsli",
                    "RightAnswer": "controversial",
                    "options": ["anxious","biological","golden"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xom",
                    "RightAnswer": "raw",
                    "options": ["controversial","anxious","biological"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "grammatik qoidalar",
                    "RightAnswer": "grammar",
                    "options": ["logic","confusion","fiction"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qayta ko'rib chiqmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "revise",
                    "options": ["consume","pray","hesitate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ishora",
                    "RightAnswer": "hint",
                    "options": ["hurry","exhaust","fence"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ilgak",
                    "RightAnswer": "hook",
                    "options": ["hint","hurry","exhaust"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'ng'iroq",
                    "RightAnswer": "bell",
                    "options": ["grammar","logic","confusion"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "suyuqlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "liquid",
                    "options": ["excess","pro","magic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashvishlanmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "panic",
                    "options": ["hook","hint","hurry"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "amaki, tog'a",
                    "RightAnswer": "uncle",
                    "options": ["bell","grammar","logic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "guruch",
                    "RightAnswer": "rice",
                    "options": ["uncle","bell","grammar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qiyalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "slope",
                    "options": ["cluster","carpet","knife"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "baxt",
                    "RightAnswer": "happiness",
                    "options": ["rice","uncle","bell"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "haqiqiy",
                    "RightAnswer": "genuine",
                    "options": ["raw","controversial","anxious"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kema, idish",
                    "RightAnswer": "vessel",
                    "options": ["happiness","rice","uncle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "fe'l",
                    "RightAnswer": "verb",
                    "options": ["vessel","happiness","rice"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisoblamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "reckon",
                    "options": ["revise","consume","pray"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ahmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "silly",
                    "options": ["genuine","raw","controversial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashish",
                    "RightAnswer": "transportation",
                    "options": ["verb","vessel","happiness"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "port, bandargoh",
                    "RightAnswer": "harbor",
                    "options": ["slope","cluster","carpet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "komediya",
                    "RightAnswer": "comedy",
                    "options": ["transportation","verb","vessel"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ortidan quvmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "chase",
                    "options": ["panic","hook","hint"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "saqlash joyi",
                    "RightAnswer": "storage",
                    "options": ["comedy","transportation","verb"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "olam",
                    "RightAnswer": "universe",
                    "options": ["storage","comedy","transportation"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yomon",
                    "RightAnswer": "horrible",
                    "options": ["silly","genuine","raw"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'y",
                    "RightAnswer": "sheep",
                    "options": ["universe","storage","comedy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oshiq",
                    "RightAnswer": "lover",
                    "options": ["sheep","universe","storage"]
                }
            ],
            "level 28": [
                {
                    "Question": "kalamush",
                    "RightAnswer": "rat",
                    "options": ["harbor","slope","cluster"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "portret",
                    "RightAnswer": "portrait",
                    "options": ["lover","sheep","universe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "begunoh",
                    "RightAnswer": "innocent",
                    "options": ["horrible","silly","genuine"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "o'rnini bosuvchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "substitute",
                    "options": ["chase","panic","hook"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qo'shimcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "supplement",
                    "options": ["substitute","chase","panic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sozlash",
                    "RightAnswer": "adjustment",
                    "options": ["portrait","lover","sheep"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oqilona",
                    "RightAnswer": "reasonably",
                    "options": ["altogether","quietly","firstly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "filtrlash",
                    "RightAnswer": "filter",
                    "options": ["supplement","substitute","chase"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "moslashuvchan",
                    "RightAnswer": "flexible",
                    "options": ["innocent","horrible","silly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "mavhum",
                    "RightAnswer": "abstract",
                    "options": ["concrete","parallel","solid"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yelkan",
                    "RightAnswer": "tent",
                    "options": ["rat","harbor","slope"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aniq",
                    "RightAnswer": "precise",
                    "options": ["flexible","innocent","horrible"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "masofaviy, uzoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "distant",
                    "options": ["wise","eastern","western"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "begona",
                    "RightAnswer": "stranger",
                    "options": ["liquid","excess","pro"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "soya",
                    "RightAnswer": "shade",
                    "options": ["tent","rat","harbor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "don",
                    "RightAnswer": "grain",
                    "options": ["shade","tent","rat"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "joylashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "situate",
                    "options": ["reckon","revise","consume"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xulosa qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "summarize",
                    "options": ["situate","reckon","revise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sakramoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "leap",
                    "options": ["filter","supplement","substitute"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sindirish",
                    "RightAnswer": "snap",
                    "options": ["leap","filter","supplement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ehtimol",
                    "RightAnswer": "probability",
                    "options": ["adjustment","portrait","lover"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "teri",
                    "RightAnswer": "leather",
                    "options": ["stranger","liquid","excess"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "noaniqlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "uncertainty",
                    "options": ["probability","adjustment","portrait"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'kinmoq, qasam ichmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "swear",
                    "options": ["damn","prompt","reverse"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qochqin",
                    "RightAnswer": "refugee",
                    "options": ["uncertainty","probability","adjustment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qirg'oq",
                    "RightAnswer": "shore",
                    "options": ["grain","shade","tent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "oylik",
                    "RightAnswer": "monthly",
                    "options": ["weekly","mad","overseas"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tashkil etmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "comprise",
                    "options": ["summarize","situate","reckon"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "aralashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "stir",
                    "options": ["snap","leap","filter"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hayajon",
                    "RightAnswer": "excitement",
                    "options": ["refugee","uncertainty","probability"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xo'rsinmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "sigh",
                    "options": ["stir","snap","leap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "homiladorlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "pregnancy",
                    "options": ["excitement","refugee","uncertainty"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tajribaga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "experimental",
                    "options": ["interior","racial","civilian"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "institutga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "institutional",
                    "options": ["precise","flexible","innocent"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bo'lak",
                    "RightAnswer": "slice",
                    "options": ["shore","grain","shade"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sang'imoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wander",
                    "options": ["comprise","summarize","situate"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "imperiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "empire",
                    "options": ["pregnancy","excitement","refugee"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "keyinroq",
                    "RightAnswer": "subsequently",
                    "options": ["reasonably","altogether","quietly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muloyim",
                    "RightAnswer": "gentle",
                    "options": ["institutional","precise","flexible"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qatnashish",
                    "RightAnswer": "attendance",
                    "options": ["empire","pregnancy","excitement"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "egalik",
                    "RightAnswer": "ownership",
                    "options": ["attendance","empire","pregnancy"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "malaka",
                    "RightAnswer": "qualification",
                    "options": ["ownership","attendance","empire"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "to'xtatmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "suspend",
                    "options": ["wander","comprise","summarize"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "amaliy",
                    "RightAnswer": "functional",
                    "options": ["gentle","institutional","precise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ko'ngilli",
                    "RightAnswer": "voluntary",
                    "options": ["experimental","interior","racial"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xira, rangsiz",
                    "RightAnswer": "pale",
                    "options": ["blind","spare","wet"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dog'",
                    "RightAnswer": "stain",
                    "options": ["sigh","stir","snap"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sportchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "athlete",
                    "options": ["qualification","ownership","attendance"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "organik",
                    "RightAnswer": "organic",
                    "options": ["functional","gentle","institutional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "til",
                    "RightAnswer": "tongue",
                    "options": ["athlete","qualification","ownership"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "server, xizmatchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "server",
                    "options": ["tongue","athlete","qualification"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tizimga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "structural",
                    "options": ["organic","functional","gentle"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "veb-sayt",
                    "RightAnswer": "website",
                    "options": ["server","tongue","athlete"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ahmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fool",
                    "options": ["stain","sigh","stir"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yonida",
                    "RightAnswer": "alongside",
                    "options": ["regardless","beneath","beside"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "birlashtirmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "unite",
                    "options": ["suspend","wander","comprise"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muloyimlik bilan",
                    "RightAnswer": "gently",
                    "options": ["subsequently","reasonably","altogether"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "hisoblamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "compute",
                    "options": ["unite","suspend","wander"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "artmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "wipe",
                    "options": ["fool","stain","sigh"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "g'alati",
                    "RightAnswer": "weird",
                    "options": ["structural","organic","functional"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qarash",
                    "RightAnswer": "gaze",
                    "options": ["wipe","fool","stain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "so'nmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "fade",
                    "options": ["gaze","wipe","fool"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yo'tlamoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cough",
                    "options": ["fade","gaze","wipe"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "gipoteza",
                    "RightAnswer": "hypothesis",
                    "options": ["website","server","tongue"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "qirolga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "royal",
                    "options": ["voluntary","experimental","interior"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "nazariy",
                    "RightAnswer": "theoretical",
                    "options": ["weird","structural","organic"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "parda",
                    "RightAnswer": "curtain",
                    "options": ["hypothesis","website","server"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "shahar hokimi",
                    "RightAnswer": "mayor",
                    "options": ["curtain","hypothesis","website"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zulmat",
                    "RightAnswer": "darkness",
                    "options": ["mayor","curtain","hypothesis"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xola, amma",
                    "RightAnswer": "aunt",
                    "options": ["darkness","mayor","curtain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "turnir",
                    "RightAnswer": "tournament",
                    "options": ["aunt","darkness","mayor"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ro'yxatdan o'tish",
                    "RightAnswer": "registration",
                    "options": ["tournament","aunt","darkness"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "parcha",
                    "RightAnswer": "fragment",
                    "options": ["registration","tournament","aunt"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tinglovchi",
                    "RightAnswer": "listener",
                    "options": ["fragment","registration","tournament"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "immigratsiya",
                    "RightAnswer": "immigration",
                    "options": ["listener","fragment","registration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "muloyim",
                    "RightAnswer": "tender",
                    "options": ["pale","blind","spare"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "zichlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "density",
                    "options": ["immigration","listener","fragment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "xunuk",
                    "RightAnswer": "ugly",
                    "options": ["theoretical","weird","structural"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "modul",
                    "RightAnswer": "module",
                    "options": ["density","immigration","listener"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "samimiy ravishda",
                    "RightAnswer": "faithfully",
                    "options": ["gently","subsequently","reasonably"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kuz",
                    "RightAnswer": "autumn",
                    "options": ["module","density","immigration"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yonoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "cheek",
                    "options": ["autumn","module","density"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "bog'lanish",
                    "RightAnswer": "attachment",
                    "options": ["cheek","autumn","module"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "tutgich",
                    "RightAnswer": "holder",
                    "options": ["attachment","cheek","autumn"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "quyoshga oid",
                    "RightAnswer": "solar",
                    "options": ["ugly","theoretical","weird"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "kulish",
                    "RightAnswer": "grin",
                    "options": ["cough","fade","gaze"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "atirgul, o'sdi",
                    "RightAnswer": "rose",
                    "options": ["slice","shore","grain"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ot",
                    "RightAnswer": "noun",
                    "options": ["holder","attachment","cheek"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "omadli",
                    "RightAnswer": "fortunate",
                    "options": ["solar","ugly","theoretical"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "yaxshi",
                    "RightAnswer": "alright",
                    "options": ["okay","monthly","weekly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "dangasa",
                    "RightAnswer": "lazy",
                    "options": ["fortunate","solar","ugly"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "salom",
                    "RightAnswer": "hello",
                    "options": ["hi","each","another"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "ochlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "hunger",
                    "options": ["noun","holder","attachment"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "sug'urta qilmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "insure",
                    "options": ["compute","unite","suspend"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "uyalmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "ashamed",
                    "options": ["lazy","fortunate","solar"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "asos solmoq",
                    "RightAnswer": "found",
                    "options": ["rear","lean","shut"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "blog",
                    "RightAnswer": "blog",
                    "options": ["rose","slice","shore"]
                },
                {
                    "Question": "chanqoqlik",
                    "RightAnswer": "thirst",
                    "options": ["hunger","noun","holder"]
                }
            ]

        }


